["Time in a Bottle" by Yungblud playing]
‘If I could save time in a bottle‘
‘The ﬁrst thing that I'd like to do‘
‘Is to save every day‘
‘Till eternity passes away‘
‘Just to spend them with you‘
[soldier] All right, touchdown in two.
Rules of engagement.
Electric rounds only.
MI6 wants them alive for questioning.
The target's in a metal coffer.
Every agency and terror cell
is looking for it.
‘But there never seems
to be enough time‘
‘To do the things you want to do‘
-‘Once you ﬁnd them‘
-[men shout]
‘Once you ﬁnd them‘
‘I've looked around enough to know‘
‘That you're the one I want to go‘
-‘Through time with‘
-[beeping]
‘Through time with‘
[soldier] Freeze! Down on the ground!
-Drop it! Drop your weapon!
-[grunting]
Don't move! All of you, get down!
[beeping]
[beeps]
Asset secured.
[man] Ml6.
[soldier] Freeze!
Whoa, whoa. I'm a fan.
Fantasticjob, and I think you look
amazing in your matching outfits.
Who the hell are you?
Bad guy.
Get on the ground now!
[beeping]
Nah.
[grunting]
[gun clicks empty]
[engine starts]
[tires squealing]
[panting]
[steady beeping]
[beeping continues faster]
[gaSpS]
[grunting]
[gasping coughing]
[radio beeps]
-[static crackles]
-Bulldog Two.
-The team is down.
-[straining]
We've been betrayed.
-She took the virus.
-[soldier choking]
[static crackles]
One of the soldiers
got away with the virus.
I want her on the run
with no place to turn.
She is a wily one.
Monitor all channels
and make sure she takes the fall for it.
-Understand?
-[man] Yes, sir.
What you want us to do
with these assholes?
Clean it up. Idon't care. No witnesses.
I'm gonna get it back.
Who‘s gonna stop me?
[alarms beeping]
["Better As One“ by The Heavy playing]
[sniffs]
-J‘ If I say it once, I’m-a say it twice J‘
-J‘ Say it J‘
-J‘ Somebody gonna pay the price J‘
-J‘ All right J‘
-J‘ Somebody better lose their head I
-J‘ Hey J‘
J‘ Somebody paying off some debt I
-J‘ Don’t blink, better hold my tongue J‘
-[engines revving]
J‘ Better hold my soul I
If I’m off the coast J‘
-J‘ All right I
-J‘ This mess can't make it up J‘
I But the way I play won’t make you go J‘
I [know that we can do better I
J‘ I know we’re better as one I
-[grunting]
-J‘ / know that we can do better J‘
J‘ Without evil on our tongue I
I [know that we can do better I
J‘ I know we’re better as one I
-[phones ringing]
-J‘ / know that we can do better J‘
J‘ Without evil on our tongue I
-Where?
[engines revving]
-J‘ Owl Can we make it different? I
-J‘ Yeah J‘
-[tires screech]
-J‘ Can we make it better? J‘
-J‘ Yeah I
-J‘ Can we make love reign supreme J‘
-J‘ Can we make it better? I
-J‘ Yeah J‘
-J‘ Can we make it different? I
-J‘ Yeah I
J‘ Can we take the head from the beast J‘
I That insisted we’re all different? I
I [know that we can do better I
J‘ I know we’re better as one I
J‘ Without evil on our tongue I
I [know that we can do better I
J‘ I know we’re better as one I
J‘ Without evil on our tongue I
[indistinct chatter]
J‘Ole‘
J‘ Yeah J‘
Who the hell are you?
Ooh. I'm what you call
"an ice-cold can of whup-ass."
[neck cracks]
[indistinct chatter]
Who the hell are you?
I'm what you might call
"a champagne problem.“
[grunting]
What you got, big man?
[choking]
[grunting]
-[needle buzzing]
-[screaming]
[straining]
-[grunts]
-[women scream]
Really thought that would have broke.
[women screaming]
Uh-uh.
[screams]
I'm gonna kill you!
-You gonna die!
-[grunting]
[women gasping, screaming]
-[groans]
-[inhales sharply] Ooh.
All right, all right. No, no.
That's my favorite jacket. Don't do that.
Hi, sweetheart.
Could you pass me that gun, please?
Thank you very much. Nice tats.
All right, ass-clown. We're gonna play
a little game. It's called hangman.
I'm gonna ask you some questions.
When you give me an answer I don‘t like...
-[need|e buzzes]
-[panting]
Okay, you get the idea.
I've been tracking some
dark web chatter about a super virus
that's coming up on the auction block.
Why don't you tell me about it?
I swear, I don't know.
I don't like that answer.
-[needle buzzing]
-[grunting]
A little bird told me
about a shadow outfit.
Black tech. Blood ops.
Real assholes. Like you.
They're called Eteon.
And you're gonna tell me
where to find them.
You‘re not gonna tell me
because I'm hanging you out of a window.
You‘re gonna tell me because
I'm the guy willing to drop you.
-[screaming]
-[needle buzzing]
[screaming continues]
All right, bonus round.
Where's the virus?
No! No, wait!
Don't leave me out here! Please!
Don‘t leave me! Don't leave me!
I All right, here we go, yeah, yeah J‘
What did he write?
J‘ Yeah J‘
J‘ Money on my mind, so l'rn too paid J‘
J‘ Real all the time, never Kool-Aid J‘
J‘ Sipping on D'USSE, psych J‘
J‘ Came a long way from G-Burg J‘
J‘ Putting in work like Ferg J‘
J‘ What that even mean?
I don 't know what you talking ’bout J‘
J‘ Why nowadays everybody got a palm out? I
J‘ PLP, yeah, that be me
And that be what I rhyme 'bout J“
J‘ l have arrived
All you rappers are in time-out... J‘
"A, A, A." Excellent.
Oh, by the way, your Old Man and the Sea
report from last week?
You did so good, it was awesome.
-Thanks, Daddy.
-Give me some. Yes. Yeah. What's that?
Um... It's a social studies assignment.
It's a family tree.
It's just a sketch.
Oh, yeah.
That's our family tree right there.
It's super easy to read and very clear.
Yeah.
But I was going to use this.
I found it in a garage drawer.
That's you, isn't it?
Who‘s Jonah?
Is that your brother?
Yup. That's my brother.
Why don't you ever talk about Samoa?
Did something happen?
In life, things happen.
You may not want them to, but they do.
You just gotta do your best...
and move on.
And the fact of the matter is
I'm your family.
I'm your people. Me.
-And you're a whole lot.
-Oh, I am a whole lot.
-[chuckles]
-[Hobbs] Look at this. Perfect timing.
Oh, no, this is the mini.
-Yup.
-Thank you so much.
-Cheat day?
-Cheat day. Yeah.
Thank you so much.
Is that really necessary?
Come on! She's 71 years old.
What's the matter with you lot?
Sir, the prisoner will
only be allowed more leniency
when she proves
to be less of a security risk.
If someone leaves a back door open,
it's a bit daft not to try and use it.
What's daft is paying
one of the screws to leave it open
but not paying them enough
to keep their mouth shut.
Yeah, well, my point still stands.
If you can't break out
of a shitty prison like this,
then you're seriously slipping, Mum.
You cheeky bugger.
Speaking of breaking out,
where's my birthday cake?
The one with the ﬁle in it?
They're baking it.
Who wants a bloody ﬁle?
What I want is a nice little bit of C-4.
Listen, if you want out of here,
just say the word. l'll handle it.
Oh, Decks,
I'm just having a bit of fun really.
Being banged up doesn‘t bother me.
I quite enjoy the peace and quiet.
You know, nice walk,
bit of reading, loads of sudoku.
It's like being retired. Love it.
Now listen,
have you spoken with your sister?
You know I haven't, Mum.
-Give me your hand.
-There she goes.
I mean, you and your sister,
you used to be inseparable.
What happened, Decks?
What happened between you?
I remember you, Owen, and Hattie
playing out in the backyard.
Your little games, your little grifts.
Robbing banks.
You used to give
your little scams code names.
Do you remember?
-Oh, what was that one?
-The "Keith Moon."
[Magdalene] Yeah, that’s right. It was
called the "Keith Moon" because it--
It involved lots of explosive percussion
and permanent ear damage.
J‘ Yeah! J‘
[laughs]
That's my boy.
No wonder we left the family business.
She loves you, you know?
All you gotta do
is pick up the phone, Decks.
Look at me. You're her big brother.
She looks up to you.
Used to.
Well, one day, ljust hope
that I walk through that door
and | see the two of you sitting there.
How many years you got left?
Two, with good behavior.
-So how many, really?
-Four.
Well, you know what they say.
"Never say 'never.'"
[guard] Time's up.
You behave yourself.
Will do. Love you, darling. [kisses]
Love you too. [kisses]
[Magdalene laughs]
-All right.
-[man] Lucas Rebecca Hobbs.
I haven't seen you in forever.
-"Rebecca"?
-Do you even age? How long's it been?
-Six months.
-Time ﬂies.
-When we're apart.
-What is your skin care regimen?
Because you look
like a young Shirley Temple.
-Go, go, go, go, go.
-Daddy, who is this guy?
Well, this guy is Locke.
And he works for the CIA.
-Your dad and I are old friends.
-We're not old friends.
Actually, we‘re...
We're best friends. Here's the half heart.
I don't know what that is.
-We got some ink together as well.
-We did not get ink together.
-Oh, we didn't?
-No, we did not.
-Interesting. I seem to remember...
-We never got ink together.
...getting a little something like this
at one point on my body.
-Jesus.
-Christ, I miss our playful banter.
You have one minute
to tell me what you want
before I knock one of your lungs loose.
You and l are after the same thing.
Say hello to the CT-17 virus.
It's a programmable bioweapon
of biblical proportions.
Affectionately code-named "the Snowflake."
What does the Snowflake do?
Oh, nothing much.
Just liquefies your internal organs.
Basically turns your body
into a giant bag of hot soup.
She is nine!
-Seen worse.
-Where?
Game of Thrones. Janet's house.
-I‘ve never heard of it.
-A Lannister always pays his debts.
You're never going over there again.
But there's a new
wrinkle in the case, Rebecca.
The specifics... are all in the brief.
There you go.
-She's ready, Becca.
-She's nine.
This is the only unit of CT-17
in existence,
and this Snowﬂake is now in the hands
of a rogue MI6 operative in London.
Dad, are all spies that pretty?
No. She is unusually attractive.
And deadly.
Last night she was part of an MI6 team
tasked with securing the virus.
She then proceeded to kill
her entire black ops squad.
She stabbed one guy in the chest
using a brick.
Do you know how hard that is?
To stab someone using a brick?
-Get to the point.
-The point is there's no sharp edge.
How did she get an entire brick
into another person's chest?
She either had to be really strong
or the other person had to have been,
like, born without, like, bones.
-Get to the larger point.
-She stole the Snowflake.
-She went totally off-grid.
-Who's this?
That's the scientist
we believe created the virus.
Great. Where do I find him?
He's off-grid too.
Impossible to ﬁnd. Maybe dead.
-You're very helpful, Locke.
-And you're the world's best tracker.
I'm sure you'll figure something out.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm DSS, you're CIA.
I don't work for you.
Your boss loaned you out.
You do now, dickface.
-What'd you just call me?
-Hey, hey, hey!
Let's just settle down. All right?
We've already got
a black site running in London.
There's an operative there.
Top of his game. He'll be your contact.
I don't need anybody else. I work alone.
We got bigger problems
than your fragile ego,
or the fact that a moment ago
I most deﬁnitely shit my pants.
The entire world
is at stake here, all right?
This thing gets out, we're looking at
a lot of liqueﬁed organs,
and I mean, like, everywhere.
And notjust yours and mine.
Uh... He knows I can see him, right?
He knows nothing, Jon Snow.
[Sam chuckles]
So what's it gonna be, Becky?
You gonna partner up?
-I‘m in.
-Of course you are.
Do you remember what I told you in Rwanda?
-"Stop watching me sleep."
-I said:
-"We are not friends at all."
-We're best friends.
-And to watch your back.
-Wash your back, yeah.
-Oh, I remember.
-Watch your back.
Lot of back. I got you.
Hey. Same old Hobbs, huh?
Same old Locke.
All right. Who's on the case?
[man speaking indistinctly over PA]
-Mr. Shaw.
-Whatever it is, I ain't buying it.
You don't know what I'm selling,
or who I am.
CIA.
-How could you--
-Sunglasses, cloudy day, sensible shoes.
I have fallen arches, and I don't have
a lot of choice in what I--
Anyway, I'm Agent Loeb, and I need
to talk to you about our shared interest.
How'd you find me?
I got a tip from an acquaintance of yours:
Mr. Nobody.
Little joke for you, Loeb.
What do CIA operatives
and baseballs have in common?
People cheer when you hit them with a bat.
No.
They are two things
I don't give a toss about.
That works too.
The weapon she‘s stolen
is not like anything we've ever seen.
It‘s a programmable disease
that can target any DNA sequence
with a 100% mortality rate
inside 72 hours.
If MI6 ﬁnds her,
they’re gonna treat her like a traitor.
[man on phone]
We need you to surrender the virus.
What is your location?
What, you think I killed them?
[Loeb] But if you help us ﬁnd her,
if you bring us the virus,
we ’l/ grant her immunity.
We've set up a black site here in London.
You‘ve got everything you could need
at your disposal,
and we're bringing in an asset
from the States to assist you.
I don't need anybody.
Maybe not, Mr. Shaw.
But she does.
-My guy's in.
-My guy's in too.
Is your guy gonna freak out
when he ﬁnds out who my guy is?
Didn't theyjust do a job
together in New York?
Didn't they just destroy
the DSS field office in LA
by throwing each other through it?
I don't know. Look,
I don't know about your guy, but my guy?
He's gonna get this.
He's gonna pull this off. You know why?
We've been best friends
our whole goddamn lives.
Well, my guy beat the shit out of me
at a bar in Krakow 17 years ago,
and he doesn't even remember me.
So we all have our histories.
Anyway, it's the fate of the world here.
It's the fate of the world.
The planet's population is in their hands.
Serious stuff.
You‘d think they'd be able to put aside
any petty rivalries to save the world.
-Mm. Mm.
-[slurping]
-No fucking way.
I'm not working with this guy.
I've been there, done that.
The minute he gets involved,
you can kiss goodbye to any ﬁnesse,
because She-Hulk here
only knows how to smash.
And Mr. Arson here
only knows how to blow shit up.
-The fact is...
-And the fact is...
-no offense...
-oh, no offense...
-this guy's a real asshole.
That's "sumbitch" in your native tongue.
That'd be "wanker“ in your native tongue.
Are you ﬁnished blubbering?
You sound like a giant tattooed baby.
I'm not listening to this horseshit.
I got a job to do.
Tell your mom I said hi.
Actually, I'll tell her myself.
Don‘t you ever talk about my mother.
I'll put your head through that wall.
Secondly, I'll have this job done while
you're still putting on your baby oil.
Good luck, slick.
-[snaps fingers]
-That's it. You just reminded me.
That's exactly why
I hate working with you.
It's your voice.
It‘s your nasally, prepubescent,
Harry Potter voice.
Every time you speak,
just imagine this for a second,
it‘s like dragging my balls
across shattered glass.
-And it hurts.
-Well, for me,
it's not your voice.
It's your face.
Your big, stupid face.
Looking at it makes me feel
like God is projectile vomiting
right in my eyes.
And it burns.
It really burns.
What you gonna do now?
Throw a bit of furniture?
For your information, I was gonna
take this chair and turn it sideways
and shove it right down your throat.
Of course you are,
'cause that's your answer to everything.
Smash a hole through every problem
in a massive truck.
-That's not gonna work here.
-I think it'll work fine.
Guys, why don't you two take a seat
and we'll talk through this?
Me and you? Us? I've been down this road.
It's a total waste of time.
For once, I couldn't agree with you more.
Yeah? Well, I'm doing this my way.
If anyone's got a problem with that,
I suggest you come out here and stop me.
I'm not going in there.
Well, I'm not going in there.
Smart lads.
All right, now that we got rid of
that fun sponge, we can get to work.
I want you to pull up every CCTV camera
around central London.
We already have two dozen agents
scouring footage.
Don't you talk back to me, Opie. Uh-uh.
I just care about the coverage.
I ain't gonna ask you again. Pull it up.
Now zoom in on the area of the heist.
Now invert it. Highlight the areas
that the cameras don't cover.
She's smart.
She just killed her entire team
and stole a deadly virus.
She ain't waiting around for no picture.
J‘ l'rn on the next level J‘
J‘ Yeah, I know you heard about it J‘
J‘ You know I’m 'bout it, 'bout itJ‘
J‘ And don't you ever doubt it J‘
J‘ I 'rn incomparable J‘
J‘ That's why they starin', though J‘
J‘ Turn up the stereo, check it out J‘
J‘ Check it out, check it out I
J‘ Ooh-whee J‘
J‘ I'm hot just like a sauna J‘
J‘ New York to California I
J‘ Too hot, too hot I
J‘ Ooh-whee J‘
J‘ You ain't seen nothin’ like this J‘
J‘ Nobody do it like this
This, this, this J‘
J‘ l'rn on the next level J‘
J‘ Next, next, next level I
J‘ On the next level I
I They all tryin' to catch up to my J‘
J‘ Next level J‘
J‘ Check it out, check it out
Check it out J‘
J‘ La-la la-la la la J‘
-J‘ La-la la-la la la J‘
-[sighs heavily]
J‘LalalalalaJ‘
J‘ You like that old-school J‘
J‘ Back in the musee J‘
J‘ That-That is old news I
J‘ I 'rn poppin' through the ceiling J‘
J‘ That's my motto, that’s my motto J‘
J‘ I lead, they follow J‘
J‘ Ooh-whee J‘
J‘ You ain't seen nothin’ like this J‘
J‘ Nobody do it like this, oh! I
J‘ l'rn on the next level J‘
I They all tryin' to catch up to my J‘
J‘ Next level J‘
J‘ Next, next, next level I
J‘ Check it out, check it out
Check it out J‘
Got a lot of nasty people looking for you.
Are you nasty?
Well, it all depends on what happens
in the next 30 seconds.
Promises, promises.
[door opens]
So here's how it's gonna go down.
We do this the hard way or the easy way.
-[scoffs] Are you serious?
-I am.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Hmm. Well, it's a tough decision.
-No, it's really not.
You want me to freeze?
Let me see your hands.
Fine.
But you're not gonna like what's in 'em.
-Think I made up my mind.
-You seem like a smart woman.
lam.
The hard way.
[grunting, groaning]
Look-- Hold on!
[yells, groans]
[grunting]
Stop!
Jeez.
[grunting]
[groaning]
-Hey! No.
-[grunts]
-[shouts]
-Oh! [groans]
-[glass shatters]
-[panting]
-Are you taking it easy on me?
-For the moment.
[metallic ringing]
[screams]
[grunting]
Bet you wish
you didn't take it easy on me now.
I wish a lot of things right now.
You're going to go to sleep now.
It's all gonna seem like a bad dream.
It's more like a nightmare.
This whole thing is a nightmare.
All right,
let‘s me and you have a little chat.
[growls]
[grunting, shouting]
-[beeping]
-[panting]
[woman] The director called.
He ordered a new baseline for you.
He has everything ready for you
in medical.
[director]
Perfection is a painful process, Brixton,
in ourselves
and in the pursuit of a perfect world.
Humanity must evolve
before it destroys itself.
Eteon will carve out all human weakness
and replace it with mechanical perfection.
And you will lead the way.
I'm gonna ask you a question.
It's not what you think it is.
Do you like to dance?
What, the Electric Slide?
The Macarena? No, I don't.
No, no, no,
I was thinking about... the tango.
-Where it takes two.
-Yeah, don't know that one.
Must be different generations.
[laughs]
Yeah, well, either way, the music started,
so let's see what kind of rhythm you have.
-Where‘s the virus?
-Look, I told you,
-I‘ve no idea what you're talking about.
-Okay, that hurt.
You just stepped on my toes,
that didn't feel good.
Let's try it again.
I think you're better than that.
-Where's the virus?
-I didn't ask to dance.
And why should I talk to you?
You're not CIA.
No? How do you know that?
Where shall I start?
There's two types of CIA agents.
Intelligence and espionage.
Those guys over there
can barely lift a pencil.
That's what intelligence agents look like.
You look like you could
pick up a building.
But espionage is about blending in
and about being subtle,
and there is nothing subtle about you.
Yeah.
That's good.
-I‘m impressed.
-I didn't kill anybody.
I know you didn't.
How do you know that, then?
Because you can learn a lot about somebody
when you fight them.
And when we fought,
you weren't fighting to kill me.
You were fighting to run away.
But either way, the world thinks that
you're a murderer and a thief,
so you're not going anywhere
or getting any goddamn phone call
until you give me some real answers.
You have no idea what is happening here.
-Then tell me. Help me understand.
-I can't.
-You're wasting my time.
-I can't either-- You're wasting time!
Virus gets in the wrong hands, that's it.
It's game over.
[alarm ringing]
[chuckles]
Does that mean it's time for curls?
Just like the CIA,
always flexing the wrong muscle.
You know, the mind
is the strongest muscle in the body.
Maybe you should try
exercising that a little bit more.
“There's more wisdom in your body
than in your deepest philosophies.“
Let me guess. That Bruce Lee?
[chuckles] No, Nietzsche.
'Cause I'm flexing this.
And all of that.
Come here.
If she moves, I want you to shoot her.
Yeah, he can't shoot me.
-Yeah, not allowed.
-In the face.
You can‘t. You'd go to prison.
-You can shoot her right in the face.
-No, you can't. You'd go to prison. Sorry.
I want you to shoot her
two times right in that face.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
[Sam on phone] Hi, Dad.
Did you catch the hot spy lady?
Come on. It's me.
I catch everybody I hunt.
How long have you been doing this?
'Cause you seem... new.
[groaning]
She's actually quite annoying.
You know, Dad,
sometimes people annoy each other
when they're actually, like, ﬂirting.
Where'd you hear that from?
Okay, look, me and the spy lady,
we're not flirting, all right?
Zero chemistry.
[groaning]
[tires screech]
[engine revs, shuts off]
I don't know.
When you saw her photo,
you definitely gave the eyebrow.
What eyebrow?
-You know, Dad, that thing that you do.
-What thing?
-I don't do that.
-Yes, you do.
No, I definitely don't do that.
I don't even know what you're doing.
That’s the silliest thing I've ever seen.
Let me get going,
I got business to take care of.
I‘ll see you when I get home, okay?
I love you.
Love you.
Hey, one more thing.
-[Sam laughs]
-[chuckles]
[choking]
Goddamn it.
[grunting]
This is not the dance
you wanna do with me, woman.
-Oh, really?
-I eat bullets all day long.
Oh, for breakfast and lunch?
'Cause it's dinnertime.
I‘ll count down for you. Three...
-Two...
-[Shaw] Hobbs.
-[analyst] Freeze.
-Put that down.
Get your greasy
sausage fingers off of her.
-What are you doing here?
-Saving you.
I don't need to be saved.
No, no. This is my house and your
goddamn girlfriend ain‘t going anywhere.
-That's disgusting.
-[Shaw] "Girlfriend"?
That is my sister.
Bullshit. She's too good-looking
to be your sister.
Very funny.
Hat, there are people after you.
Believe me, I know that.
It's gonna stay that way
unless you tell me where that virus is.
Listen to me, pinhead. She's gonna die
if I don't get her out of here right now!
We're all gonna die if
she doesn't tell us where that weapon is.
Actually, everyone's gonna die
'cause I am the virus!
It's embedded in capsules.
I need to find a way to get them out.
[groaning]
[gunfire]
Bag the asset.
[beeping]
-Now or never.
-I‘m more of a now type of guy.
-On my three.
-Sure.
One, two, three.
No one tells me what to do.
[mouthing]
[shouts]
[people screaming]
[beeps]
Now I take you to school, son.
[whirring]
[gunfire]
[Brixton]
Deckard Shaw. It‘s been a long time.
Good to see you, Brixton.
-I think you're out of bullets there, son.
-Lucky for you, I am.
Yeah.
-Nice suit.
-[Brixton] Bulletproof.
-State of the art.
-[Shaw] Could've done with that
the last time I put a bullet in ya.
No, actually, it was three bullets.
Two to the chest, one to the head.
Just like they taught us. Do you remember?
It's a shame you didn't join Eteon.
You could‘ve had all this, my friend.
-"Friend"?
-Yeah.
-You're not the man I knew.
-No. I am way better.
I'm the future of mankind.
[whirring]
[beeping]
[engine revving]
Stop!
Hattie, get in the car.
We're all going.
Not you.
Just the girl.
-I said, we're all going.
-[sirens approaching]
[grunts]
Disable the car. I need the girl alive.
J‘ Going for mine, running out of time J‘
J‘ If you're coming for me
You better get in line J‘
J‘ Hit you with the Force like SkywalkerJ‘
J‘ Creeping through the dark
Like a night stalker J‘
I Put you in the earth
Say a prayer soon J‘
J‘ Tension in the room, let me break it J‘
J‘ With a boom of a shotgun J‘
What the hell did you do, Hattie?
A big brother lecture now, really? Huh?
I injected myself. I didn't have a choice.
He was gonna take it.
J‘ I got a good side, I got a bad side J‘
J‘ I got a monkey on my back
And I call it pride I
J‘ I got a mean streak
/ don’t care to hide I
J‘ And I will ﬁght for my cause
Even if I die, yeah J‘
[horn honking, tires squealing]
Program intercepting vector.
[beeping]
J‘ Time for some action J‘
I Come on! J‘
J‘HalJ‘
[people screaming]
J‘ I am the evolution of man J‘
J‘ And I will win any way that I can J‘
J‘ I go to war anywhere that I am J‘
J‘ [90 to warlJ‘
-You might wanna--
-[Hobbs] Ah!
[tires squealing]
[woman screams]
Might be time for some curls.
[grunting frantically] Let go!
[screaming]
Very good.
You wanna tell me just what in the
fresh turkey hell we're dealing with here?
Long story.
He's a ghost. Supposed to be dead.
Eight years ago,
I put a bullet through his brain.
Great, so we're being chased
by the Terminator.
[truck horn honking]
I don't think he's gonna make it.
I don't think he can see
over the steering wheel.
Buckle up, fat boy,
I'm gonna save your life again.
[gaSpSI
[shouts]
[panting]
You want a war, then?
Okay.
[metallic rattling]
Okay, ride's over.
We gotta lose this car.
Update.
I've hacked the mainframe
of every news agency and outlet.
How many do we control?
Hundred and seventy-four broadcasts,
2,000 odd.
Double it.
I want 100% control of this story.
-Standard frame job.
-No, standard will not do.
I need something special for these guys.
So listen up. Narrative:
Hobbs, Shaw, big guy, little guy,
have been ID'd.
They've been blamed
for the recent attacks on the CIA.
They shared a prison cell
where they hatched a plan
to start their reign of terror.
Just got real.
-[Hattie] Who the hell are these guys?
-[Shaw] Eteon.
They're a secret tech cult, with
a mercenary army and plenty of dark money.
And delusions of saving the world
by augmenting the human race.
That's it.
Apparently they control the media as well.
Heard rumors about these people.
Everybody thinks they're a myth.
[Shaw] I've seen it firsthand
how real they are.
If you don't fit into their plans,
you've already dug your own grave.
All right, let's get to
the nearest lockdown facility--
Hey, no. You don't get it, do you?
Brixton's a tier-one assassin.
Best I've ever seen. I know him.
He ain't never gonna stop
until he gets that virus.
And besides, that's my sister.
Family business.
Is your name Shaw? No.
Then she's going nowhere with you.
When it comes to the fate of the world,
it becomes my business.
I don't care if she's your sister,
that woman ain't going anywhere--
-Where are you going?
-I‘m going away.
I don't have time for your alpha male shit
right now. You're both idiots.
You clearly can't work together
and so you're absolutely useless to me.
So I'm gonna go find the man who can
help me get this thing out of my system.
-See ya.
-[Hobbs] You mean this man?
I was tracking him before the attack.
He's hard to find,
but I think I got a hell of a lead.
Russian newspaper.
Not just any old paper.
There 's only one place
in London that sells that.
[indistinct newscast playing]
[in Russian]
[grunting]
Call the director.
[line ringing]
[director] Well, well, Deckard Shaw.
How complicated for you.
Not really.
He's also working with DSS, Luke Hobbs.
Hobbs. We have a history.
They're formidable.
Small fry.
I'll eliminate the two of them.
Get the asset back ASAP.
You get the girl,
extract the virus
and reprogram it for phase one.
We use that weapon to eliminate the weak
and anyone who would get in our way.
We ’re building
the perfect system, Brixton.
Turn them.
"Turn 'em"?
Sorry, I don't follow.
I want them turned.
I want them working for the cause.
Understood?
They can't be turned.
What makes you so certain?
The last time we asked,
I got shot in the face.
That makes me very certain.
So, I suggest that
we take another approach.
-Which is why--
-l'm not asking, Brixton.
You show them the consequences of refusal.
Or perhaps I'll show them to you.
Is that a threat?
I'd remember who you're reliant on
for your survival.
All for the cause.
Look, honey, I have to talk to you about
something. It's very important right now.
Remember how we spoke about
what would happen if things went sideways?
We called it a "code red."
Well, it's happening.
Is there anything I can do?
You need to stay home.
You're gonna be safe there.
As a matter of fact, we've got the CIA
listening in on this call right now.
Watch this. Hi, Locke.
Everybody's safe, everybody‘s great.
I'm actually at our old diner here.
It's super weird being here
without you guys.
Think it's closed.
Thank you, brother.
Honey, I've already talked to Aunt Lisa.
She knows exactly what to do.
I’m gonna be home as soon as I can.
-Love you.
-I love you back.
Goodbye.
Luke Hobbs and Deckard Shaw.
While Hobbs is an agent in the American--
Tell us everything you know about this.
My God.
-When were you exposed?
-[Hattie] About 30 hours ago.
Then the capsules containing
the virus are still intact.
So we need to neutralize it.
No, it is not that easy.
It's not programmed to any DNA sequence.
It's fatal to everyone.
In 42 hours, the capsules will dissolve,
and she will be infected.
Then the virus will go airborne.
We are talking global contamination
within a week.
Why in the hell
would you create something like that?
-Because I thought I was one of them.
-Eteon.
They told me they wanted
to save the world through science.
I believed in their cause.
I developed the Snowflake
to be a carrier for vaccines,
a panacea for the whole world.
But they redeveloped it
into a programmable apocalypse.
To attack the weakest of us. Those not
worthy of Eteon's vision of the future.
For a scientist,
you seem incredibly stupid.
Well, I'm a two-times Nobel Prize winner,
but who's counting?
All right, you said the virus is
programmable. So... reprogram it.
I can't reprogram it in a host.
Just tell us how to
get this thing out from me.
Well, there are two options.
And the first is easy.
-Go.
-Finally.
-You kill her.
-Excuse me?
And burn the body, of course.
-Of course.
No, I mean really burn it.
-Really burn it.
-To ash.
-To ash?
-Beyond all recognition.
Let's assume that that's not an option,
shall we, genius?
Yeah, it doesn't work for us.
Option number two.
There is a machine that could
preserve her life and extract the virus.
That should've been option number one.
Because it's impossible to get to.
We'll decide what's impossible.
Where is it?
A secret dark-tech complex
fortiﬁed by an army
in the most godforsaken
part of the planet.
But if you go there,
all three of you will die.
So basically what you're saying is:
she dies no matter what.
Well, who needs a drink?
I know just the place.
J‘ I'll keep you alive J‘
I Keep you alive I
J‘ They’ll be talking about you
Long after you die J‘
Wow, look at all these.
[Hobbs]
Somebody's overcompensating.
If anything, I'm under-compensating.
And a teeny-tiny one. Just your size.
[Shaw] Used it for a job over in Italy.
Shame we didn't need
a weightlifting bus driver.
Would've given you a call.
[chuckles]
I I'll keep you alive, keep you alive J‘
J‘ They’ll be talking about you
Long after you die... J‘
Drink?
Yeah, I'll take a little one.
I Keep you alive I
J‘ They’ll be talking about you J‘
J‘ Long after you die I
I'll write to someone in Moscow.
An old friend.
Yeah, we have a long history.
She and her crew are paying a visit
to some locals.
Particular Russian criminal element.
-They have things that we're gonna need.
-Considering your history with friends,
how many bullets you put
in this one's head?
They can set us up with gear,
and I don't hear any other ideas.
We know getting out of this country
is gonna be extremely difficult.
We have every major intelligence agency
already hunting us down.
And there's the fact that you disgraced
MI6 when you betrayed your team.
Don‘t believe everything they tell you.
Smile.
[camera shutter clicks]
No, regular back channels
aren‘t gonna work this time.
We're gonna have to
do our best to blend in.
[Hattie] Hide in plain sight.
-That's why we'll be flying commercial.
-Commercial?
-We‘re gonna get spotted too easy at--
-[camera shutter clicks]
Don't worry that pea-sized brain.
I handled it.
Cloned our cell phone signals
around the world.
Should buy us at least 48 hours.
We'll pick up new gear
when we get to Moscow.
Should get us past the wandering eyes
at the airport.
This is probably the only thing
that's gonna fit.
Fit what, a Smurf?
I think that's one of my old ones.
I apologize in advance
if it's a little loose around the balls.
Okay. What do we got, tough guy? Come on.
[Shaw] I've created new identities
and altered your biometric profiles
so the airport scanners don't recognize
your faces or your ﬁngerprints.
You're Sarah Atkins.
You work in insurance.
Hello.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
[Shaw] I'm Franz Gruber.
I'm a freelance architect,
avid mountain climber,
and a part-time ski instructor.
-Thank you.
-And you, you're Michael Oxmaul.
"Mike Oxmaul."
I go by Michael.
-[officer] Freeze! Stop, sir! Stop there!
-[officer 2] Stay right where you are!
-Stay there!
-lt's Mike. It's Mike Oxmaul.
It's not small. And my name's Michael.
They've stopped him for what, exactly?
Whatever it is, it's gonna involve
rubber gloves and a body cavity search.
Let's go.
[dog barking]
Hands on your head, Oxmaul.
[Hattie] Can't believe you did that.
He was gonna slow us down.
We can't pull this off. We both know it.
It's bad enough
I got this thing in my blood
that's gonna kill me and everyone else,
but were you seriously gonna break
this mysterious machine
out of some
high-security death virus complex
and magically get it to work?
-Frankly, that sounds completely--
-You still wear that silly thing?
Didn't know you still had that.
Put the pin back in.
You haven't changed.
Wish I could say the same about you.
Hey, you're gonna be okay.
We're gonna make this work.
It's what we do.
And what if we don't?
-What if the only option is for you to--
-It's not happening.
Hi, I'm here. I'm Michael.
Hi, yeah.
Hello. All right.
Oh, yeah, let's see. Where's my seat?
F-one, F-two...
F you.
Hey.
You are an asshole.
You were quicker than I thought.
Yup. Because I have
a secret weapon.
People actually like me.
You wouldn‘t understand that
because you don't have any friends.
I love your babushka.
[dog barking in distance]
[gaSpSI
Couldn't have booked an emergency row
for a little bit more legroom?
Not everybody has hobbit legs like you.
Hey, look, in case you didn‘t realize,
I couldn't give a damn about your comfort.
So why don't you be a good elephant,
suck up another kilo of peanuts,
put your chair back and relax?
Listen, don't ever tell me to relax.
Don't tell me to do anything.
Any time you ever say anything,
it makes me want to take my boot
and shove it so far up your ass,
you're gonna be
spitting out Shoelaces all week.
Hey, you know what the problem is?
I‘ll tell you the problem. This job.
This job requires stealth.
And you... look at you.
I mean, granted, it's not yourfault.
But you're too obvious.
You stick out. Like balls on a bulldog.
Dangling down in all the wrong places.
Seemingly harmless.
And the next thing you know,
they're trying to impregnate your sister.
[chuckles] What?
-Impregnate your sister?
-You heard.
Oh...
Now I get it.
You do? Good. I'm glad. Yeah, I'm glad.
-I‘m very glad.
-You actually think that
I'm going through all this effort,
on this mission,
trying to save the world,
by the way, for a fourth time,
because I'm really good at it.
You think I‘m going through all of this
just so I can do the horizontal-hula,
sexy, sexy time with your sister?
Not all. Most.
Let me break it down for you, Frodo.
This ain't 1955 anymore, all right?
Despite the fact that that girl sleeping
right there is related to you,
she‘s still one of the toughest,
baddest, most capable women
I've ever encountered in my entire life.
And if she chooses to look the way
of this big, brown,
well-endowed, tattooed
mountain of a man, then guess what.
I'm gonna let her climb this mountain
over and over and over again.
You stay away from her.
I see what you're doing.
You think I‘m stupid?
Of course I think you‘re stupid.
But you know what? I'll do you a favor.
I'll knock that dumb right out of
your skull. You just say the word, jack.
You know what I wanna do?
I wanna do an Irish jig
on your arse-ugly face at 30,000 feet.
-Oh, 30,000 feet.
-Yeah.
-So you wanna dance right now?
The only thing holding you back
is air and opportunity.
[inhales deeply] And there goes the air.
-Bring it on, Don Ho.
-"Don Ho"?
That's enough! Hey, cut it out.
Both of y‘all, cut it out.
Oh, see? You woke up the air marshal.
You woke the air marshal.
-How‘d you know I was the air marshal?
-Unaccompanied.
-Late boarding the plane.
-Aisle seat.
-Golf shirt.
Let's just call that an educated guess.
Air Marshal Dinkley, at your service.
I'm sorry, did you just say "Dinkley"?
What's the problem? Dinkley.
I understand this big fella,
because it's myjob to observe.
Thick neck, your head's been on a swivel
since you‘ve been on this damn plane.
Every passenger that's got on here
you been checking out.
You're a lawman.
And you, Mr. Armani pants, you're a spy.
-He's pretty good.
-Not bad.
I get it. We're all big guys.
The three of us. Alphas.
Three apex predators cooped up in the sky.
Tensions get high.
What you throwing up on the bench?
Three, four hundred pounds?
-Little less.
-Yeah, light work.
I'm doing the same thing. Slagging weight.
Clanging and banging.
What you into?
Hot yoga? Pilates?
Probably mess around in the Octagon.
Yeah, you wanna know what I do?
I sit in a can of farts all day long.
That's what I'm dealing with.
It's an occasional terrorist
and a lot of recycled ass.
I would give anything
to be on the front line again
"Again"?
-What?
-I was a compartmented element for JSOC.
You were in Delta?
Sabre Squad Echo, 24/7, baby.
"Echo"? Those guys were the warlocks
because of the magic they could do.
-That's right.
-If that‘s the case,
then Imma say "abracadabra," bitches.
You're looking at the magic.
You know what your problem is?
Your balance is off.
You need a third squaddie.
-No, no, we're good.
-No.
I know the game.
[deep voice] You hear me? I know the game.
-[Hobbs] What are you doing?
-What do you mean, “What am I doing?“
-Don't talk like that.
-[Shaw] You sound different.
-Do I?
-That's not your voice.
Use your regular voice.
This is my regular voice.
I'm talking like the warlocks talk, baby.
They don't talk like that.
[normal voice] I'm just showing you.
That's all, guys. Look...
all I'm saying is I could complete
this holy trinity that you guys have.
Three would be too much.
Here's my résumé. This is my card.
'Cause if you need stuff, I'm the guy
that you call to get what you need.
You want a Citation X? You want a GV?
You want a Boeing 747?
You want a helicopter?
You want something stealth?
I'm an air marshal. I'm your guy.
-[machine whirring]
-[chain clinking]
-[whirring stops]
-[loud clank]
Please. Please let me go.
[screams, sobbing]
What do you want?
I want our property
out of that girl's blood.
No, the virus is too dangerous. I can't!
[Brixton]
Humans must evolve, Professor.
Without Eteon's upgrades,
the human body's
really not worth that much.
Maybe 11 pence worth of magnesium,
couple of pence worth of calcium,
little bit of iron.
Not worth much.
I'd say, all in all,
probably about three pound.
Three pound fifty, max.
The entirety of a man's worth,
small change.
You're gonna reprogram that virus for me.
I won't.
[screams]
J‘ Shut your mouth for a minute J‘
J‘ Eyes red, tight chest
Lips that won 't quit it J‘
I I'm sick to death of this business I
J‘ Who are you to tell me I'm ﬁnished... J‘
[mufﬂed grunting]
[bottle shatters]
I That I’m gonna give you
The satisfaction J‘
J‘ I left my conscience burning
In the tarmac J‘
[Hobbs]
Ah, yourfriend's a Russian mobster.
[Shaw]
This girl steals from Russian mobsters.
Actually, she steals from everyone.
It's kind of her thing.
Deckard Shaw.
Margarita.
Oh, I did not see that coming.
I wish I didn't see that at all.
Me too.
[Margarita] I got your list.
-It's long.
-[crash, screams in distance]
I asked for a house on a runway.
Not sure a dozen Russians in duct tape
were on the list.
Well, give me more
than three-hour notice,
and I wouldn't have to
resort to such extremes.
Not sure three hours has anything to do
with your extremes, Margarita.
-[beeping]
-[Margarita] Qué mierda, Deckard.
Eteon. Could you pick
a harder place to break into?
We need to find the C-17 viral
extraction machine. Could be anywhere.
That facility is
three square miles of research labs.
Yeah. And it's a powder keg
packed with munitions.
We've gotta pull a Mick Jagger.
This sounds like a fun game.
We're not getting you on the inside. No.
When Deck and l were kids,
we'd spend our time coming up with grifts.
A "Mick Jagger“ was a job
that required one person to showboat
to draw all the eyes
while the others made the music.
A typical inside job.
Guys, you heard Andreiko.
They have to use the extraction machine.
So they'll take me right to it.
No, I can do it.
We can do it.
So now the only question is
how to ring Eteon‘s dinner bell.
Oh, I can handle that part.
But ﬁrst, let's get you geared up.
These are your HALO parachutes.
Earbuds for encrypted communication.
Scorpion EVO 3 with optical sights.
Ultra-thin bullet-resisting Kevlar.
Infrared cameras for seeing through walls.
And last but not least,
compact hydrogen detonator.
Put it in the right spot,
it'll blow the place sky-high.
How do I look?
Looks a little tight.
How you holding up?
You know, if things go south in there,
you can‘t leave me alive.
We're gonna get you out of there.
Let me tell you something else.
"The key to immortality
is first living a life worth remembering.“
-Is that more Nietzsche?
-Nah.
That's Bruce Lee.
[Hattie chuckles]
Come on.
[Brixton] How'd you ﬁnd her?
[Margarita]
You've heard about me. I'm good at my job.
[Brixton] Was she alone?
Yeah.
If you're lying to me,
I will cut your heart out.
Do you understand?
I'd be afraid if I had one.
[jet engine idling]
Now that's a ride.
What a ride.
I got shotgun.
-I got shotgun.
-No, no, no. Don't start. I got shotgun.
We're entering the drop zone!
-Are you ready?
-Yeah, I'm ready.
-On my three!
-Okay.
-One!
-Uh-huh.
[Shaw] Ah! You asshole!
Whoo!
J‘ You're messing with the boss now I
[Hobbs] Nobody tells me what to do.
[alarm buzzes]
[man speaking Russian over PA]
[rapid gunfire in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
[man continues speaking Russian over PA]
So, I‘m intrigued,
do you wash the blood off your hands
before you count your money
or is it afterwards?
Dismissed.
You don't get it, do you?
You know, the weak deal with money.
We deal with evolutionary change.
Change that sometimes require
acts of violence.
Like killing innocent people with viruses?
Only the weak ones.
We're dealing with the future of
the planet. Things that money cannot buy.
Oh, like your soul back?
My soul?
Your brother took my soul.
The boys in the lab made me a new one.
Now, that's progress.
[man grunts]
[helicopter passing overhead]
[Brixton]
Welcome to the extraction room, Miss Shaw.
Get her ready.
It won‘t be long.
[Hobbs] I tell you, we ain't gonna want
to be here when this thing goes off.
[beeps]
Looks like she's 400 yards through there.
Looks like they're holding her
in some sort of medical pod.
Timer‘s set for 45 minutes.
We get in and get out.
Blow this death factory to pieces.
Remember the hallway.
-No guns.
-Right. Those guys have to be alive.
Because at the end of the hallway,
the retinal scanner needs a match
to open the door.
-Pick a door.
-I‘m right there.
Nope, that's my door.
What's the matter with you?
[beeping]
I made a mistake. This is your door.
Oh, no. No backsies. What's the matter?
You got a lot of bad guys
behind that door?
Watch this. You might learn something.
[all shouting]
[grunting]
[growls]
[groaning]
[mouthing] Watch this.
[laughs]
[guard shouts]
[grunting]
[yawns]
Eh.
[guard grunts]
[electricity crackles]
[beeps]
[automated voice]
Enter corresponding match.
-[buzzes]
-Access denied.
Access denied.
-[guard grunts]
-Access denied.
Access denied.
[whispers] You come and do it!
-[chimes]
-Access granted.
Doors opening.
Very good. Well done, boys.
I'm impressed that you even got in here.
[both groan]
[in Russian]
[guards scream]
[both groan]
That-- That's... That‘s not possible.
-No. What are you doing?
-Having to extract it myself.
Wait!
[engine rumbling]
-[chains clink]
-[grunts]
[panting]
There he is. Nice and rested?
Get your full eight hours?
I was gonna order some room service.
What do you fancy?
French toast? I'll get the order in.
I just dreamt they killed you
before I woke up.
Pretty disappointed right now.
It's a little elaborate, I must admit.
Old-school interrogation technique
we picked up in black ops.
Shock will kill a man in three.
Do you remember that, Deck?
Yeah, I remember
a lot of things from back then.
I reckon you've only got
four shocks in you, boys.
Yeah? I think we could take ﬁve.
"Five"? Well, all right.
-[electricity buzzing]
-[Hobbs, Shaw straining]
-[buzzing stops]
-[both panting]
You had to open your big mouth, didn't ya?
I thought it was a cool thing
to say in the moment.
[grunting]
Do you remember
when we were real brothers?
Task Force Black.
Do you remember that, Deck?
Man, we ended up
seeing the worst in people.
Worst in our countries, our leaders,
our enemies, our friends.
You don't know
the meaning of that word anymore.
But don't worry about it, neither does he.
He shoots them right in the head,
but in your case,
I thought it was a hell of a good idea.
Big man, you still talking?
I said I thought it was a hell of a good--
[electricity buzzing]
[both grunting]
Shit.
[laughs] You know, it's funny
how humanity's hate for each other
is stronger
than its own self-preservation,
which is why we're here.
Remember eight years ago, Deck,
when Eteon asked us tojoin their mission?
Oh, you mean their death cult.
-They're lunatics.
-Visionaries.
Visionaries of a future.
A bigger future. A brighter future.
You remember the data they gave us, man.
What with environmental damage,
capitalism, terrorism,
humanity wipes itself out by 2096.
Now, that is scary to me.
But if we fulﬁll Eteon's vision,
-you save their world.
-You don't save the world with genocide.
Genocide, schmenocide.
You know what this virus is?
This virus is a necessary
shock to the system.
-[electricity buzzing]
-[grunts]
[Shaw shouts in distance]
-[electricity buzzing]
-[strained grunting]
-[electricity stops]
-[both panting]
Whoo! That's three.
[chuckles] I love this thing.
Told you then, I'm telling you now,
your metrics are off.
One good reason:
You assume the worst in people.
People cannot be trusted to do
the right thing. Look at the two of you.
The fate of the world is in your hands,
and you can't even get along.
But you know all about doing
the right thing, don't you, Shaw?
Little souvenir, huh, bro?
You come to kill me,
I'll do the same every time.
What'd you expect? A shiatsu?
[laughs]
Anyone talking to you?
Your mama.
-[electricity buzzing]
-[both grunting]
-Yeah!
-[both grunt]
[laughs] I get it. You‘re still mad.
You're upset because,
hey, when you wouldn‘t turn,
they asked me to come and kill you,
and, of course, I had to
because you knew too much.
But I think about that night a lot.
I think about it.
Because what I realize now
that I did not realize then
is that when you shot me,
you gave me a gift.
Look at me. I'm black Superman.
Bulletproof, new spine,
and the more machine I become,
the more humane I am.
This is what you wanna fight for.
I'm giving you another
chance to join us, Deckard.
And the boss wants big mouth as well.
If not, I kill you both.
Which, honestly, I'd love to do.
You know Eteon.
You know what they're capable of.
They rebuilt me. Dismantled him.
Made it look he killed his own team.
Even your own sister... disowned you.
[sighs]
Just say the word, bro.
Say the word and all of this goes away.
Your sister lives. His daughter lives.
We get you some upgrades,
and we go on to saving the world.
[chuckles]
What's it to be?
Join the evolution of man,
or die with the weak?
Just get it done.
I told the boss you wouldn't
change your mind.
See you later.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait!
[panting]
I think we should join.
Join?
You said some really compelling things.
I mean, that black Superman thing,
that really got me. I love that.
What are you, deaf, stupid, or both?
We ain't joining.
There you go again, you're just thinking
about yourself. You're such a diva.
What about my feelings, for once?
Let me tell you something,
if we were a band, you know who you'd be?
You‘d be Mick Jagger.
"Mick Jagger"?
Mick Jagger.
[Brixton] Oi, what's it to be?
In or out?
-We‘re not gonna join.
-We're not gonna join.
But since you're standing there,
here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna rip the arm off this chair.
I'm gonna smash him right in the face.
Stab him right in the neck
for looking that way.
Kill all 13 guys in seven seconds.
And here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna slip out of these chains
and dropkick him,
him and him right in the throat.
No, not him, that's my guy.
You gotta pick another guy.
What do you mean that's your guy?
That‘s my guy.
No, no. That's face-smash guy.
You gotta find another dropkick guy.
You want a face-smash guy?
I'm gonna find you one.
See that guy over there?
The big one. The big one.
-That's face-smash guy.
-No, he's way too big.
Let 'em go.
All right, boys, stay calm.
We need her alive.
Let them go, or what?
Or you're gonna get a nice new breeze
there at the center of your forehead.
You're not gonna shoot me.
[gun buzzes]
Because you need
an activation chip to fire that gun.
Sorry.
Try this gun!
[Brixton screams]
I'm not small change.
-[grunts]
-[shouting]
[screaming]
-Let's roll.
-You think?
Dick.
[gun beeps]
[rapid gunfire continues]
[Hobbs] There she is.
-Hattie, where's the machine?
-lt's in the second truck.
-On it.
-[bullets ricocheting]
Mick Jagger.
Never fails.
-[alarm blaring]
-[shouting]
[rapid gunfire continues]
We're not out of this yet, Hattie.
Got the machine.
[Shaw] Get a move on!
Train's leaving the station!
-[shouting]
-[bullets ricocheting]
[beeping]
That sumbitch really is black Superman.
[rapid ticking]
Engage drones.
We're running out of road.
Hold on!
Route to intercept.
[beeping]
[grunts]
[grunts] Whoo!
On your left.
Brace yourself.
[both grunt]
[engine sputtering]
Hobbs, this ain‘t gonna make it.
Bringing her to ya.
You thinking what I'm thinking, Shaw?
Let’s trade some paint.
Trade some paint.
Hattie.
-Huh?
-You trust me?
[beeping, whirring]
Gonna need a ride.
I know what you're thinking.
Just keep driving. I‘ll make it.
Take the wheel.
Ah, there he is.
[grunts]
-I got him.
-No, I got him.
[rumbling]
[grunts]
I thought you were strong.
[shouting]
[panting]
[engine sputtering, knocking]
[engine stops]
[Hobbs] I‘m sorry, brother.
This thing is really damaged.
[Hattie] Well, there goes option two.
-That only leaves the first one.
-Come on. Stop it, Hat.
I'm tired, Deck. lam done running.
-We still got time.
-"Time“?
Time for what? The machine's destroyed.
-Yeah, well, we'll ﬁx it.
-How?
We need to find a place
to get off the grid.
Where? We're wanted all over the world,
and Brixton won't stop.
We can't risk millions of people.
I told you on the plane,
we should've gone with option one.
-It is done now, Deck.
-It's not done.
-It's done.
-It's not done!
It's not done.
Look at me.
Remember that thing you used to say to me
when we were kids? Huh?
Used to look at me and say,
"Deck, it's never over till it's over."
We used to laugh. Remember that?
No, Deck, it went,
"It's never over till I say it‘s over.“
Yeah, that was it.
[chuckles softly]
So say it now. Say it.
Remember who we are.
We're the Shaw family.
We never, never, never give up.
We've got a day.
More than a day.
[Hattie]
We don't even know where we'd go.
I know a place.
Where?
It's the last place on earth
I ever wanna go.
Home.
["Taku uo Pele" by Te Vaka playing]
J‘ Fakafetai mo to alofa J‘
J‘ Te gall ona taimi J‘
J‘ Heoli lahi te ﬁaﬁa J‘
-J‘ Kiki ki luga ve he matagi J‘
-[line ringing]
J‘ Meake ve he lalolagi a tatou... J‘
[Dinkley on phone] Abracadabra, bitches.
I told you that I could get you anything.
And listen to me, from Moscow to Samoa,
that is not an easy flight to charter,
but I got it done.
Well, that's why
we're calling you, Dinkley.
We just wanted to say thank you
for getting us that bird to Samoa.
Warriors help out warriors.
So all you need to know
is that you got a third squaddie over here
that is ready to go
whenever you need me to.
-I‘m just sitting in my lair.
-[toilet flushes]
You in a bathroom?
[Dinkley] Potato, potah-to.
Wherever I am is where the magic happens.
We ain‘t gotta get into specifics.
Just to make sure
you got all the contacts.
You got the cell, you got my e-mail.
-Got 'em all.
-lmma shoot you
my mom number too.
Imma make sure you got that,
'cause if you can't get me, she can.
Igot a Hotmail address
that’s still active. Hit me on that.
Linkedln. That's my profile.
-...account thing I've been doing.
-[imitates static]
-l'm just making sure you got everything--
-We‘re losing ya.
That was my phone.
I hope this brother of yours
is as good a mechanic as you say he is.
Jonah is the best mechanic I know.
And he's gonna help us.
That is, if he doesn't kill me first.
-[birds squawking]
-[dog barking]
[sighs]
[Shaw] Yeah, take your time.
It's only my sister's life and
the fate of the world we're waiting on!
[exhales sharply]
[Hattie] Oh, here we go.
Bet you a bullseye 50 quid
he punches him in the face.
Deal.
[sighs] Jonah.
You know what comes next?
Yup.
-[grunts]
-[others exclaiming]
See? Notjust me.
[speaking Samoan]
Your face,
it's all over the bloody news, boy.
You‘re not welcome here, police.
You got a bloody cheek.
Coming here after 25 years.
Bringing your problems here to this house.
You betrayed our family,
bring shame on our house.
You betrayed your own blood!
[shouts in Samoan]
Jonah, I hear you.
But we ain't kids anymore.
You better watch how you talk to me.
It's not the size of the dog
in the fight, boy.
It's the size of the fight in the dog.
No, it's always the size of the dog.
[woman]
Hey! No fighting under this roof, huh?
Is that my Luke? Oka...
My baby's home.
Hey, Mama.
Oka, I miss my baby boy.
But look at you, all skin and bones.
-Come over here and eat.
-No, no, no, Mama.
There's no time.
I'm sorry. I didn't want
to bring trouble here.
You should've stayed away.
What did you bring here?
-I brought the truth here.
-What truth?
The truth is we were set up.
We were framed by people
who created a deadly virus.
-Oh, come on.
-It could go global if it's not stopped.
We could all die. All of us.
Everybody here in this fale,
everybody on the island.
And everybody around the world.
Jonah, I need you
to help ﬁx this machine.
I need you to help my friends,
and I need us
to build defenses around here, now!
You think you can just come back in here
and we're gonna help you
-after everything you did?
-Yes!
-Not gonna happen!
-It's bigger than you and I!
-I don't care!
-It's bigger than you and I! We could die.
Good, because I would rather die
than help you, polo head!
Listen, I know your brother's
hard to be around, believe me.
But I trust him, and he brought us here
because this place has something
that nowhere else on the planet does: you.
You don't know me! I don't know you, okay?
Time for you all to go.
Take your machine with you. Go, now!
-Go!
-Jonah Hobbs! [speaking Samoan]
You have some respect for your use.
If he needs anything,
we gonna give it to him.
The food off our tables,
the clothes off our backs,
even the mana of the islands.
And you boys, all you boys,
you show our guests here fa'aaloalo,
or so help me God,
I'm gonna take this here slipper
and I'm gonna sasa your big, fat heads!
You boys hear me?
I'm sorry to bring this here, Mama.
Luke, this is your home.
We Samoans. We can handle troubles.
[whirring]
-[whooshing, crackling]
-[screams]
[director] You were right.
You don 't turn soldiers like them.
Do what I built you to do.
You're a one-of-a-kind war machine.
Bring us back my virus.
No handcuffs this time.
You can have your revenge.
I will.
We found 'em.
They hopped an unregistered cargo plane.
-To where?
-Samoa.
Gentlemen!
This is where you earn your upgrades.
Bring me back my virus.
["l'm Comin' Home"
by Aloe Blacc x AG playing]
J‘ I done burned all the bridges J‘
J‘ On this lonely road J‘
J‘ It's too late for forgiveness J‘
J‘ Pearly gates done closed J‘
Yeah.
[singer vocalizing]
J‘HeyJ‘
J‘ So, darlin', if you see the devil... J‘
[Hattie] It's quite the operation.
[Hobbs] Yeah, for a chop shop.
Your dad was a car thief, then?
No. My dad actually stole everything.
Drugs. Guns...
Sounds just like my family.
[Hobbs]
Mama raised us till we were teenagers,
and my old man
started coming around again.
Taking a real interest in his sons.
The truth is,
he was just looking for a new crew.
And I was the only one
to see through those lies.
So the jobs my dad pulled
me and my brothers into
just got bigger and more dangerous.
Then eventually he knew,
and he was okay with,
getting me and my brothers killed.
So I turned him in.
Or you protected your family.
So after I put him away,
I left Samoa and I never came back.
Well, at least one good thing came out
of me jamming that thing into my hand.
Yeah, what's that?
Got to bring you home, didn't I?
[sighs] Lucky me.
You went legit.
Yeah, 100% clean now.
Custom shop, international clients.
See those bikes? Going to Tokyo.
And that car? New York.
That one over there‘s going to London.
Turns out people like our stuff.
I needed to do something
to hold our family together.
After you abandoned us.
Hey, good news. Change of clothes. Hats.
Your mum said you might like to wear this.
Must be your favorite size. Spray on.
Why don't you throw another jacket on?
It's 110 degrees out there.
Hey, look, down to business.
We got any weapons?
Oh, we got weapons.
Mama, where's all our guns?
I get rid of 'em.
Very noble, Mrs. Hobbs.
We're in serious trouble.
That is an understatement.
These guns, they kill all my family.
So we gonna ﬁght.
Gonna fight with this
and we gonna fight with this.
'Cause no take a real man
for pull one trigger.
All right, we're going to war
with the family heirlooms.
Got it. We're gonna need a lot more.
We're never gonna survive their ﬁrepower.
It doesn't take a man to pull a trigger,
but for Eteon,
it does take an activation chip.
You still got that glove?
You‘re thinking closed-system hack.
It'll level the playing ﬁeld if you can.
Certainly buy us some time.
[Hobbs] Shut their guns down.
I'm on it.
You ready?
War is what I do.
Let's go old-school.
[Hobbs] Take a look around.
This is where we draw the line.
Who would've thought this is where
we're gonna save the world?
We need to make 'em play by our rules.
Tomorrow morning there I] be a storm
raging on the north cliffs.
We'll build a no-man’s-land there.
And if all else fails,
that'll be our last stand.
How many more of these we gotta do?
Just keep digging, brother.
[Shaw]
When we were in Kandahar running raids,
Brixton would always strike
just before dawn.
It's when the enemy's most tired,
still under the cover of night.
When the battle shifts into high gear,
you got the sun at your back.
We let ‘em all in.
And we make sure they never leave.
Kill box. I like it.
Not like we got a ton of resources.
But the island will provide, brother.
J‘ I done been around the world
Ain't nobody else J‘
I That can do it like us
With nobody help J‘
J‘ When the chips about to fall J‘
J‘ And our back against the wall J‘
I Know it’s only one place I call J‘
I All roads lead home J‘
-J‘ Oh J‘
-J‘ Oh, Oh I
-J‘ Yeah I
-J‘ All roads lead home J‘
-J‘ Oh J‘
-J‘ Oh, Oh I
I All roads lead home J‘
J‘ Back home and I’m tryin’ to stay J‘
J‘ Same crew, I don 't like to change I
J‘ Anything that we 've been through J‘
I We got through it all
Like no time to waste J‘
J‘ We go right back to the ﬁner things J‘
J‘ New goals that we had to chase J‘
J‘ Come together, this last foreverJ‘
J‘ I wouldn’t be here without the gang J‘
J‘ Been around the world
Everybody looking at me J“
I Like I know the path to take J‘
J‘ I don 't know it all
But I know the homeys J‘
J‘ Looking at me like I have the way J‘
I So I tell 'em all what I see I
J‘ Then I tell ’em all what I hope to see J‘
I Tell ’em all when I’m home I
J‘ I'll be bringing
All of that home with me I
J‘ I done been around the world
Ain't nobody else J‘
I That can do it like us
With nobody help J‘
J‘ When the chips about to fall J‘
J‘ And our back against the wall J‘
I Know it’s only one place I call J‘
I All roads lead home J‘
J‘OhJ‘
J‘ Welcome to my city
Welcome, welcome to my city J‘
J‘OhJ‘
J‘ The only place I know J‘
I All roads lead home J‘
J‘OhJ‘
J‘ Welcome to my city
Welcome, welcome to my city J‘
J‘OhJ‘
J‘ The only place I know J‘
I All roads lead home J‘
-Give me the good news, Hat.
-I‘m in.
The only thing is, I could only block
the signal repeaters on the satellite
for six minutes.
Six minutes might be all the time we need.
Better than a sharp stick in the eye.
Which is basically
all we've got to fight them with anyway.
Done more with less, haven't we?
[chuckles]
[Hobbs] Hi.
-Drink?
-Sure. Thank you.
[bottles clink]
Just taking it all in,
in case it's the last sunset we see.
I shouldn't have believed
that Deckard went dark.
Wasted so much time. I'm...
I've spent my whole life running away.
-Me too.
-Yeah?
Yeah.
I haven't been back here in 25 years.
I mean, my own daughter
doesn't even know her family.
Well... you can change that.
Yeah.
So can you.
I got an idea. Why don‘t you and I
make a promise right here, right now?
That when we see tomorrow's sunset,
we begin to fix the mistakes we've made.
That's just sealed it
so you can't back out. That‘s all.
I don't think there's any chance in hell
I would back out.
You wanna seal it again or...
-[Hattie] Deﬁnitely not.
-[Hobbs] Okay.
[Hattie] Maybe tomorrow, if I survive.
-[Hobbs] Jonah.
-[Jonah] Look, don't rush me.
[Hobbs]
It's almost dawn. He'll be here soon.
-Make it happen now! Now!
-[Jonah speaking Samoan]
Hey, don't rush me.
That's how mistakes are made.
And how long does this process take?
It's 30 minutes and 33 till I go viral.
Deck, I think we need to
seriously consider option one.
Don‘t strike a match just yet, Hats.
We are seriously gonna miss this window.
-Let's do this. Come on!
-Jonah, now!
Fine, fine, okay. Here goes nothing.
-[beeps]
-Brace yourself, Hats.
-It ain't gonna be pleasant.
-No, it's gonna be fine. [groans]
[groans]
[beeping]
It's working. It's working.
-Yeah.
-[cheering]
[Jonah] Yeah!
[man] Hey. They triggered the alarm!
That's him.
-As we planned?
-As we planned.
Usos!
It's time.
Jonah.
Just wanna say that...
if this thing goes sideways and...
and this is it...
I'm sorry.
I may have had my reasons,
but the fact is...
I left you and I left our 'aiga.
I should've come home.
If we make it through this,
you have my word
I'll never let that happen again.
I love you, uso.
I love you too, uso.
[Shaw] Okay, you're mobile.
Do you think I need to be so close
to the front line?
Yeah, we keep you close.
Keep an eye on you
in case we need to make a quick getaway.
Hey, this is what we do, right?
It is what we do.
Deck...
I overheard what Brixton said.
That you stayed away to protect us.
I never should've believed all that stuff,
I know it now.
-I don't know why I did. I'm so sorry.
-Don't be.
Don't be. Hey, look, I've done things,
done things I'm not proud of.
Things I... have to make amends for.
All thanks to what that bastard
put me through.
But right now,
the most important thing to me
is getting my little sister home safely.
-[chuckles]
-[explosion in distance]
-[gunfire]
-[men shouting]
Eteon, hold!
[in Samoan]
[all shout ﬁercely]
-Do it.
-Light 'em up.
-[gunsb '
“Uh? eeprng]
-What‘s going on?
-[guns beeping]
[all shout]
How long before the guns get back online?
I‘ve no idea.
[in Samoan]
[all shout]
Shaw.
[shouting, clamoring]
Air command.
Bring me the chopper.
[shouting]
[grunting, clamoring]
[both shouting]
[shouts]
[grunting]
Deck!
Do it quick, Hats.
-It's in, it‘s in, it's in. Is it working?
-Machine's on.
-[beeping]
-[panting]
-We‘re good.
Let's go.
[shouting continues]
[both shouting ﬁercely]
-[distorted panting]
-[heartbeat slowing]
[gasroing]
[spits]
Hobbs!
[Hobbs] Go, go!
Let's go fishing, Shaw.
You catch him, I'll gut him.
Hold on!
-Welcome to my island, you--
-Take it up!
[engine revving]
You get us close and I'll get her.
I‘ll keep his nose down. You reel him in.
Take it up! Take it up!
[chokes, screams]
Have a day off.
[alarms beeping, blaring]
[grunting]
What are you doing?
We're going for a ride.
Shit.
[Jonah] We're coming, usosl [whoops]
-[laughs]
-[engine revving]
-Let's go, Jonah.
-Come on, brother.
The axle, the axle!
[grunts]
Timo, you got this!
Ah!
We're gonna need more weight.
[laughing] Yeah!
Bring it in nice and easy, clean.
Hell yeah, usosl
-[pilot] It‘s too much weight!
-All right, drop 'em.
[laughing]
[soldier] Stay there!
[shouting]
Hit 'em with the moonshine! Now!
[beeping, whirring]
-[engine roaring]
-[grunts]
-[beeping]
[grunting]
Hang me off a cliff, huh? My turn.
-[beeping]
-[engine roaring]
-[gun beeps]
-[soldier] Sir, the weapons
-are back online.
-Let's go, let's go!
[panting]
-Goodbye.
-[beeps]
Incoming!
We got a little trouble back here, Shaw.
We'll lose 'em in no-man's-Iand.
-[rapid gunfire]
-[bullets ricocheting]
Let's get this up!
All right, now hit that stake.
We're losing the rotor!
Shit.
[shouts]
What the--
[shouting]
I got you, Hobbs.
[grunts]
Hey!
-The rotor!
-Losing power.
-[grunts]
-Guys!
Hattie! Jump!
[shouts]
[Hobbs shouts]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crashes]
-[electrical buzzing]
-[grunting, panting]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[rapid beeping]
Hey, get up. Get up!
Hey! Get up!
You don't die until I tell you to die.
You see the extraction timer?
When it hits zero, empty this clip
into her heart, do you understand?
[grunting]
[thunder rumbling]
Hattie!
[coughing]
[Brixton] This doesn't end your way, boys.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
The numbers don't add up for you.
The evolution of man is coming,
whether you like it or not.
[Shaw]
You know, I almost feel bad for you.
'Cause it's not just metal
they ﬁlled your head with.
It's bullshit.
l was beginning to like you two,
you know that?
Oh, well.
[shouts]
[groaning]
[groaning panting]
What's the problem, boys? Does it hurt?
Must be hard being so... human.
[shouts]
[grunts, groans]
-Did you see that?
-Yeah.
-We work together, we can hurt him.
-You're right.
-Time to work as a team.
-There's two of us and one of him.
-I‘ll take a punch and let you land one.
-I‘ll do the same.
I got your back, brother.
And I got yours.
Let's go unplug this sumbitch.
[all shout]
[rapid beeping]
[electrical crackling]
[groans]
[grunting, groaning]
[both shout]
[grunting, panting]
[distorted beeping, whirring]
[groans]
[grunting]
[Brixton groans]
[rapid beeping]
[grunting, groaning]
-[gunshots]
-[both straining]
Here comes the kryptonite.
[beeping]
[groaning]
I got it.
You did it, Hat.
Never had a doubt.
[Hobbs]
Let's get it into safe hands.
You set me up as a traitor.
Turned my own sister against me.
Forced me to kill my own brother. You.
And here we are again. Come on!
Shaw, compared to the cause...
one life doesn't mean anything.
I don't know what
happened to you, Brixton.
But you made me kill you once.
I ain't doing it again.
Brother, you may believe in machines...
but we believe in people.
[whooping, cheering]
[thunder rumbling]
You may have all the technology
in the world.
We have heart.
No machine will ever beat that.
[laughs]
You boys, you're gonna get
one Samoan ass-whupping.
[whooping, cheering]
[director] Shut Brixton down.
So that‘s how it is?
It's a hell of a business, boys.
[electrical whirring]
[director] Brixton never really lived up
to our expectations.
But you three,
you outperformed your analytics.
You don't remember me, do you, Hobbs?
You will.
It's gonna be a hell of a reunion.
You’re on our radar now.
And you're on ours.
-[static crackles]
-[electronics power down]
Hey, thanks for being my sidekick
through this whole thing, brother.
You were great.
Hey, how 'bout l side-kick
that stupid look off your face?
Yeah? How 'bout you show me right now?
Okay, guys.
Let's go home.
-Yeah.
-All right.
[Hobbs, Shaw laugh]
Look, Batman had Robin.
Dr. Evil had Mini-Me. You're my Mini-Me.
[Shaw] Han Solo had Chewbacca.
Kermit had Miss Piggy.
[Hobbs] That's a low blow. Don't say that.
Don't argue with me on my island.
You're my sidekick.
‘There never seems to be time‘
‘To do the things you want
Once you ﬁnd them‘
‘Once you ﬁnd them‘
‘I've looked around enough to know‘
‘That you're the one I want
To go through time with‘
‘Through time with‘
‘There never seems to be enough time‘
‘To do the things you want to do
Once you ﬁnd them‘
‘Once you ﬁnd them‘
‘I've looked around enough to know‘
‘That you're the one I want to go‘
‘Through time with, through time with‘
‘We're now running out of time‘
‘We're now running out of‘
-‘Time‘
-‘Ah, ah, ah, ah‘
‘Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh‘
I'm so happy you‘re back.
[Shaw] Brought you that cake you wanted.
I wouldn't eat it.
Let's get out of here.
[chuckles]
How long have you been working here?
Sam, this is your grandma.
[speaking Samoan]
[Sam sobs] I love you.
Good to have you home, uso.
It's good to be home, uso.
-[alarm wailing]
-[rapid gunfire in distance]
[grunting]
[panting]
Hobbs. I hope you're sitting down,
buddy, because we got big problems.
God. I feel immediately better
just talking to you.
Is that weird?
Anyway, look.
The Snowﬂake virus, totally ﬁne.
On lockdown. In a secure asset vault.
But what we're dealing with
right now... is another virus.
The last one, well, that melted
your insides, but this one...
melts your outsides. Literally.
Your skin drips off. It's like removing
a silk kimono in a hurricane.
It's so gross. The point is
we need to get on this, like, now.
I need both of you.
What do you say, Becky?
[Sam on phone] Hey, Locke. This is Sam.
-Sam?
-You must wanna talk to my dad.
Oh, my God. Sam.
Wow! You sound exactly like your dad.
It's freaking me out right now.
It's like listening to a mirror.
-Can you put Hobbs on?
-I‘m on.
I know, but I need
to speak to Hobbs, sweetie.
I'm on. What do you want?
I mean, seriously, record yourself
side by-- It's crazy.
Before you say another word,
tell me you took care of the Snowflake.
I got it. It's done. We're good, okay?
'Cause I care about people.
-I care about our family.
-You are not family.
I know. What we have is so much deeper.
Listen, hey, real talk...
Can you believe
that Game of Thrones ending?
I didn't see it.
You watched the shit out of it,
you dirty little liar.
What's the problem?
You said there was a problem.
My problem is that Jon Snow
had sex with his aunt, then killed her,
and nobody wants to talk about it.
That's what my problem is.
-[rapid gunﬁre]
-Jesus. Hang on a second here.
‘No one defeats us‘
‘'Cause we are a spirit‘
‘One as a body‘
‘It's the new controversy‘
‘Flesh is a gambler‘
‘Spirit man is an investor‘
‘No time for losing‘
‘You're the greatest treasure‘
‘No‘
‘One‘
‘Defeats‘
‘Us‘
-‘Go, go, go‘
-‘Hey, hey‘
‘Hey, hey‘
-‘No slow, slow down‘
-'Hey, hey‘
‘Hey, hey‘
-‘We are all heading‘
-'Hey, hey‘
‘Hey, hey‘
-‘Towards the same heaven‘
-'Hey, hey‘
‘Hey, hey‘
-‘Stand by your brother‘
-‘Hey, hey‘
‘Hey, hey‘
-‘Be good to others‘
-'Hey, hey‘
‘Hey, hey‘
-‘Help out the homeless‘
-'Hey, hey‘
‘Hey, hey‘
-‘Show love to your neighbor‘
-‘Hey, hey‘
-‘Hey, hey, hey, hey‘
-‘Ba, ba, ba, ba‘
‘No one defeats us‘
-‘No one defeats us‘
‘Hey, hey‘
‘No‘
[cell phone ringing]
[phone clicks]
Let me guess.
You have a mission to save the world.
You just can't do it without me.
[laughs] No, man.
l was just checking in on you.
Seeing how my good friend is doing.
And I...
I really wanted to hear this.
[man on megaphone]
Police! Come out with your hands up!
We know you’re in there, Hugh Janus.
You bastard.
[sighs heavily]
I warned you, you bald-headed sumbitch.
When you least expect it... expect it.
You have no idea what you've just started.
Well, I'm pretty sure it involves
rubber gloves and a body cavity search.
Not a chance.
-Police!
-Get on the ground, Hugh Janus!
This ain't gonna go down
how you boys expect.
[sirens wailing in distance]
I‘ll be seeing you, Hobbs.
Looking forward to it, Shaw.
[laughs]
‘I'm just getting started‘
‘I been making moves before the dawn‘
‘Cutting through the darkness‘
‘Can 't nobody say I don ’t belong‘
‘I'll be the ﬁrst shot heard
Make you run for cover J‘
‘I Take my word, ain't no other‘
‘I Now I’m just getting started‘
‘And I can go on and on
And on and on and on‘
:Amm:
‘I'm-a drink from my winner cup‘
‘Mixing hard work with beginner’s luck‘
‘l'll fall ﬁrst, then lift me up‘
‘Never call curtains, common courtesy‘
‘Curiosity, it killed the kitty
But it got to work for me‘
‘Inadvertently I manifested
Something great‘
‘I But it still don't determine the fate‘
‘I'm-a turn the tables
From the cradle to the grave‘
‘Heavy weight, leg day, steady pray‘
‘Heavy head wears crown
Weighed down every day‘
‘I Here now, make a way
Clear foul, lane change‘
‘Breaking out the crazy house‘
‘So whatever them people
Was saying 'bout me‘
‘Hit the lever, you not on my level‘
‘The engine is revving
I'm ready, I’m ready“
‘I swear you gon’ hear about me‘
‘I'm just getting started‘
‘I been making moves before the dawn‘
‘Cutting through the darkness‘
‘Can't nobody say I don’t belong‘
‘I'll be the ﬁrst shot heard‘
-‘Make you run for cover‘
-‘Run for cover‘
‘Take my word, ain't no other‘
‘Know that I'm just getting started‘
‘Just getting started‘
‘And I can go on and on
And on and on and on‘
‘I can see the future
It ain't no mystery‘
‘l'm on the throne
Looking down, making history‘
‘While you were smelling roses
I was putting work in‘
‘I was putting work in‘
‘I'm just getting started‘
‘I been making moves before the dawn‘
‘Cutting through the darkness‘
‘Can't nobody say I don’t belong‘
‘I'll be the ﬁrst shot heard‘
-‘Make you run for cover‘
-‘Run for cover‘
‘Take my word, ain't no other‘
‘Know that I'm just getting started‘
‘Just getting started‘
‘And I can go on and on
And on and on and on‘
["Even if I Die" by Idris Elba
featuring Cypress Hill playing]
‘I... I-I-I-I will go to war‘
‘Going for mine, running out of time‘
‘If you're coming for me
You better get in line‘
‘Hit you with the Force like Skywalker‘
‘Creeping through the dark
Like a night stalker‘
‘Put you in the earth
Say a prayer soon‘
‘Tension in the room, let me break it‘
‘With the boom of a shotgun‘
‘I got a good side, I got a bad side‘
‘I got a monkey on my back
And I call it pride‘
‘I got a mean streak‘
‘I don’t care to hide‘
I And I will ﬁght for my cause
‘Even if I die‘
‘Yeah‘
‘Time for some action‘
‘Come on‘
‘Even if I die‘
‘I am the evolution of man‘
‘And I will win any way that I can‘
‘I go to war anywhere that I am‘
‘I go to war‘
Are you okay?
[groans] Okay.
I'm definitely wounded now, so...
I'm gonna really need
that extraction, Big Papa.
I‘ll tell you what, sit tight.
I‘m coming to get you.
Also, if you didn't mind, you could
bring a couple of pints of blood as well.
-Locke--
-Don't you wanna know my blood type?
What's your blood type?
It‘s B-positive.
Just like my life outlook.
-[chuckles] Imagine that.
-Locke.
-Locke?
-Jesus, I'm bleeding a lot.
God. I'm bleeding so, so much right now.
Oh, no. Actually, wait,
hold on a second. That's not my blood.
That's not my blood.
Oh, God, I thought that was me!
By the way,
I stabbed a guy with a brick.
How crazy is that?
Turns out, it's not that hard.
[sighs]