Re-Sync & Improved By: FidelPerez
Subtitle By: explosiveskull
Sub Upload Date: November 10, 2018
File 82-712.
Agent Rick Dicker
interrogating.
State your name, please.
Uh, Tony. Tony Rydinger.
Tell me about the incident.
Well, there's this girl,
um, in my class.
I saw her at the track meet.
- You're, uh, Violet, right?
- That's me.
TONY: I sort of knew her,
but she'd changed.
Relaxed.
She was more sure of herself.
Cool, cute.
I asked her out to a movie.
So, Friday?
- Friday.
TONY: And I went to watch
the track meet.
Not long after, this thing
happened in the parking lot.
(RUMBLING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(PANTING)
UNDERMINER:
Behold! The Underminer!
I am always beneath you,
but nothing is beneath me!
TONY: As if things aren't
weird enough,
I look over
and I see these boots.
MR. INCREDIBLE:
You two, stay here.
ELASTIGIRL: Wait.
Should we be doing this?
It is still illegal.
TONY:
They looked like superheroes.
- We're gonna lose him.
- Oh, all right.
One of you patrol
the perimeter,
keep the crowds
back and safe.
The other,
watch after Jack-Jack.
But I thought we were
gonna go with...
You heard your mother.
Trampoline me.
(ELASTIGIRL GRUNTS)
I call perimeter!
VIOLET:
You're not going anywhere,
you little
maggoty creep!
TONY: I see my chance
to get out of there.
But there's something familiar
about one of the kids' voices.
- (VIOLET SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
- TONY: The girl, she's upset
and she throws down
her mask...
and it's her!
VIOLET: Oh. Tony!
Hi.
VIOLET: Uh, this isn't
what you think it is.
TONY: It was just getting
too freaky.
I couldn't handle it
and ran off.
I feel kinda bad about it.
Maybe I should've said
"hi" or something?
It's not her fault
superheroes are illegal.
And it's not like
I don't like strong girls.
I'm pretty secure
manhood-wise.
What is that?
Have you told anyone else
about this? Your parents?
No, they'd only think
I was hiding something.
- You know what I mean?
- Sure, kid.
I like this girl, Mr. Dicker.
I'm supposed to go out
with her Friday night.
Now, things are just
gonna be weird.
(SIGHS) I wish I could forget
I ever saw her in that suit.
You will, kid.
You will.
(MR. INCREDIBLE GRUNTING)
Come on!
(GRUNTING AND SCREAMING)
(COUGHS)
Consider yourself undermined!
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(UNDERMINER CONTINUES
LAUGHING)
UNDERMINER: Ooh.
(LAUGHS)
- Underminer!
- We meet again... Huh?
(MR. INCREDIBLE GRUNTING)
Oh, great!
Now, he's on the agenda.
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
- (POUNDING)
- (GASPS)
- Incredible!
- (GROANS)
Meet Jack Hammer!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Buh-bye! (CHUCKLES)
(ALARMS BLARING)
(GRUNTS)
No, no, no! No, no, no!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Everybody, stay back!
Okay? Stay back!
You're not sticking me
with babysitting!
I can't steer it or stop it.
And the Underminer's escaped!
We'll have to stop it...
Bob! The monorail!
Frozone! Yeah!
We have to stop
this thing
before it gets
to the overpass!
I'll try to keep it away
from the buildings!
- (PEOPLE CONTINUE SCREAMING)
- (MR. INCREDIBLE GRUNTING)
- DASH: Hey, lady!
- (WOMAN YELPS)
Thank you so much,
young man!
(JACK-JACK COOING)
- (JACK-JACK GIGGLING)
- What?
Violet!
(GRUNTING) Ahh!
(STRAINING)
- Stop!
- (BRAKES SCREECHING)
- Everybody, stop!
(STRAINING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(PANICKED CHATTER)
(PEOPLE GASPS)
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
- DASH: Heads up, Dad!
- Dash!
Violet!
Who's watching Jack-Jack?
Dash is watching him!
- Violet, here, you take him!
- (JACK-JACK GIGGLES)
It's headed for City Hall!
- DASH: Mom needs help!
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
They're out in public again!
This is our chance!
Follow them,
follow Frozone!
(STRAINING)
Bob! Help me
with the boiler!
(GRUNTS)
That should do it! (GASPS)
What are you kids doing?
Get out of here!
This thing's gonna blow!
There's no time!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
We did it!
- (GUNS COCKING)
- OFFICER: Freeze, Supers!
Oh, what did we do?
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
TOMMY: Excuse me, Mr. Zone?
FROZONE: Sorry, but I'm not
really supposed to be here.
TOMMY: Which seems wrong...
doesn't it?
Perhaps you'd be interested
in changing that law?
Superheroes including Frozone,
Mr. Incredible,
and Elastigirl...
caused further damage
to the city.
The Underminer
remains at large.
We didn't start
this fight.
Well, you didn't
finish it either!
Did you stop the Underminer
from inflicting more damage?
No.
Did you stop him
from robbing the banks?
- No.
- Did you catch him?
- The banks were insured.
We have infrastructure
in place
to deal
with these matters.
If you had simply
done nothing...
everything would now be
proceeding
in an orderly fashion.
You'd have preferred
we do nothing?
Without a doubt.
You weren't much help.
Do you want
out of the hole?
First you gotta
put down the shovel.
Well, that went poorly.
Dad, this is probably
not the best time
to tell you about this...
but something else
happened today with a kid...
and my mask.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Oh, hey, Rick.
Violet thinks a friend
of hers, a kid named Tony...
might have seen her in the
outfit, without her mask.
- Talkative type?
- Don't know.
Last name is Rydinger.
Tony Rydinger.
I'll check it out.
Bob, Helen...
a word
if you don't mind.
Uh, the program's been
shut down.
What?
Politicians don't
understand people...
who do good simply
because it's right.
It makes 'em nervous.
DICKER: They've been gunning
for Supers for years.
Today was all they needed.
Anyway...
I'm done.
I'm afraid two more
weeks in the motel
is the best
I can do for ya.
It ain't much.
You've done plenty, Rick.
We won't forget.
Well, it has been
a great honor
working with
you good people.
Thanks for everything,
and good luck.
Yeah. You, too.
(JACK-JACK COOING)
Did you wash your hands?
- (WATER RUNNING)
- With soap?
VIOLET: Did you dry them?
What? Is this all vegetables?
Who ordered all vegetables?
I did. They're good and
you're going to have some.
(GROANS)
Are we going to
talk about it?
- What?
- The elephant in the room.
- What elephant?
- I guess not then.
You're referring
to today.
Yeah, what's the deal
with today?
We all made mistakes.
For example,
you kids were supposed
to watch Jack-Jack.
Babysitting, while you guys
did the important stuff.
We talked about this.
You're not old enough to
decide about these things.
We are old enough
to help out.
Yeah!
Isn't that what
you tell us, Dad?
Yeah, well, "help out" can
mean many different things.
But we're supposed to help,
if there's trouble.
- Well, yeah, but...
- Aren't you
- glad we helped today?
- Yeah, I know but...
You said that you were
proud of us.
Well, yeah, I was. Am!
We wanna fight
bad guys!
- (BABBLING)
- No, you don't!
You said things
were different now.
And they were,
on the island.
But I didn't mean
that from now on...
So now, we've gotta go back
to never using our powers.
It defines who I am.
We're not saying
you have...
- What?
- Someone on TV said it.
Can we just eat?
The dinner, while it's hot?
Did we do
something wrong?
- Yes.
- BOB: No.
We didn't do
anything wrong.
Superheroes are illegal.
Whether it's fair or not,
that's the law.
The law should be fair. What
are we teaching our kids?
To respect the law!
Even when the law
is disrespectful?
If laws are unjust, there
are laws to change them!
Otherwise, it's chaos!
Which is exactly
what we have!
I just thought
it was kinda cool.
- What was?
- Fighting crime as a family.
(SIGHS) It was cool.
ELASTIGIRL: But it's over.
The world is what it is.
We have to adapt.
Are things bad?
Things are fine.
May I be excused?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING
ON TV)
How much longer
in the motel, Dad?
- Uh...
- Not much longer, honey.
HELEN:
What are we gonna do?
BOB: I don't know.
Maybe Dicker
will find something?
Dicker is done, Bob.
Any thought we had about being
Supers again is fantasy.
One of us
has gotta get a job.
One of us?
You did a long stint
at Insuricare.
Hated every minute of it.
I know
it was hard on you.
Maybe it's my turn
in the private sector
and you take care
of the kids...
No, I'm doing this.
I need to do this.
You know where my suit
and ties are?
Burned up when...
BOTH:
The jet destroyed our house.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
We can't count
on anyone else now, Bob.
It's just us.
- We can't wait for...
- (DOOR BANGS)
LUCIUS:
No lifeguard on duty!
Swim at your own risk.
Oh, where'd you go today?
I noticed
you missed all the fun.
LUCIUS: Don't be mad because
I know when to leave a party.
I'm just as illegal
as you guys.
Besides, I knew the cops
would let you go.
Yeah, in spite
of Bob's best efforts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I heard
the program shut down.
How much longer
are you in this motel?
Two weeks.
Now, you know
the offer still stands.
You're very generous,
but there are five of us.
We wouldn't do that
to you and Honey.
Well, door's always open.
You know,
the news isn't all bad.
While you guys
were being detained...
I was approached by a dude
who represents this tycoon.
- BOB: Winston Deavor.
- LUCIUS: Wants to talk...
with me, with you two,
about hero stuff.
LUCIUS:
I checked him out.
He's legit.
Trained under Dicker.
He wants to meet.
Ah, jeez!
More superhero trouble.
We just came from
the police station, Lucius.
- When?
- Tonight. I'm going there now.
You enjoy,
I'm sitting this one out.
He wants
all three of us.
Honey, let's just at least
hear what he has to say.
You got the address,
I'll meet you guys there.
Go in our Supersuits?
Yeah.
Might wanna wear
the old Supersuits.
Got a feeling
he's nostalgic.
Where are you going?
The fresh air
is especially good tonight.
If Jack-Jack
wakes up...
I know the drill.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Your security badges.
Please, this way.
Hey, listen,
you're my biggest fan.
- Good to see you.
- (STAMMERING)
I'm your biggest fan.
Shoot!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
WINSTON: I love superheroes!
The powers, the costumes...
the mythic struggles.
Winston Deavor.
You can call me Win.
Genuine pleasure
to meet you.
- Frozone!
- It's good to see you.
- Elastigirl.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mr. Incredible!
- Hello.
♪ Mr. Incredible,
Incredible ♪
BOTH:
♪ Incredible ♪
♪ Catching the bad guys
Pow, pow, pow ♪
(BOTH LAUGHS)
♪ Who's the cat
Who's always chill ♪
♪ When survival odds
Are close to nil ♪
♪ Frozone
Frozone ♪
BOTH:
♪ Frozone ♪
- Yeah!
- (ALL LAUGHS)
Can't tell you what a thrill this is.
And this...
Oh, hello there, superheroes.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
...is my tardy sister,
Evelyn.
And I'm scolding myself so
you don't have to, Winston!
Spectacular.
My father was so proud
that I was even remotely
connected to you guys.
He used to call you
the last line of defense.
He was
your top supporter.
He donated
to superhero causes.
He raised money
for the Dynaguy statue
in Avery Park.
He got to know
many Supers personally.
Even installed a phone
with direct lines
to Gazerbeam and Fironic...
in case of emergencies.
He loved that,
showed it off to everyone.
He was heartbroken
when you were all forced
to go underground.
Father believed
the world
would become more dangerous
without you.
He didn't know
how right he was.
There was a break-in.
(BOTH GASPS)
WINSTON:
My father called Gazerbeam.
The direct line.
- (LINE BEEPS)
- No answer.
He called Fironic, no answer.
Superheroes had just been
made illegal...
The robbers discovered him
on the phone...
- and shot him.
- (GUNSHOT)
So...
ELASTIGIRL:
It must've been hard.
EVELYN:
Especially for Mother.
She died a few months later.
Heartbreak.
If superheroes had not been
forced underground...
it never would've happened.
Or Dad could've taken
Mom to the safe room
as soon as he knew
there was trouble.
I disagree strongly!
But we're not going
into it right now.
The point is...
nobody expected us
to be able to actually
run Dad's company.
But with Evelyn as designer,
and myself as operator...
uh, we threw ourselves
into building DEVTECH
into what it is today.
FROZONE: A world-class
telecommunications company.
Bigger than ever.
Perfectly positioned to make
some wrong things right.
Hence, this meeting.
Let me
ask you something.
What is the main reason
you were all
forced underground?
- Ignorance.
- Perception.
Take today for example,
with the Underminer.
Difficult situation.
You were faced with a
lot of hard decisions.
Oh, tell me about it.
WINSTON: I can't.
Because I didn't see it...
neither did anyone else.
So, when you fight bad
guys like today...
people don't see the fight
or what led up to it.
They see what politicians
tell them to see.
They see destruction
and they see you.
So, if we wanna change
people's perceptions
about superheroes...
we need you
to share your perceptions
with the world.
- How do we do that?
- EVELYN: With cameras.
We need you to share your
perceptions with the world.
ELASTIGIRL:
How do we do that?
EVELYN:
We embed tiny cameras, like those,
into your Supersuits.
Wow, so small.
And the picture
is outstanding.
Thanks!
Designed 'em myself.
WINSTON:
We've got resources, lobbyists,
worldwide connections...
and very important,
insurance.
Insurance is key.
All we need now are the
super-est superheroes.
It needs you three.
Come on!
Help me make all Supers
legal again.
This sounds great!
Let's get this going.
What's my first assignment?
That enthusiasm is golden.
(CHUCKLING)
Now hold on to it.
But for our first move...
Well, Elastigirl
is our best play.
- Better than me?
- (CLEARS THROAT)
I mean, she's good.
(STAMMERING)
Really, a credit to her...
You know. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
You know.
With great respect...
let's not test the whole
"insurance-will-pay-
for-everything" idea...
- on the first go 'round, okay?
- (FROZONE CHUCKLES)
Wait a minute. You're saying what?
I'm messy?
Well, Evelyn did
a cost-benefit analysis...
comparing all your last
five years of crime fighting
before going underground.
And Elastigirl's numbers
are self-explanatory.
Well, it's not
a fair comparison!
Heavyweight problems
need heavyweight solutions.
Of course!
We're gonna solve
all kinds
of problems together.
After the perfect launch
with Elastigirl!
So, what do you say?
What do I say?
(CHUCKLES)
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
A few hours ago, you were
saying it was over...
and being a superhero
was a fantasy.
Now, you get the offer
of a lifetime
and you don't know?
It's not that simple, Bob.
I wanna protect the kids!
So do I.
From jail, Bob!
- (SPITS)
- BOB: And how do you do that?
By turning down a chance
to change the law
that forces them to hide
what they are?
They haven't decided what they are.
They're still kids.
Kids with powers,
which makes them Supers...
whether they decide to
use those powers or not.
This will benefit them.
It's not a good time
to be away.
Dash is having trouble
with homework...
Vi is worried
about her first date
with that boy she likes,
Tony...
and Jack-Jack...
Jack-Jack?
What's wrong with him?
Okay, nothing's wrong
with Jack-Jack.
But even a normal baby
needs a lot of attention.
I'm just not sure
I can leave.
Of course you can leave.
You've got to.
So that I...
we can be Supers again,
so our kids can have
that choice.
(SCOFFS)
So you can have that choice.
All right, yes!
So I can have
that choice.
And I would do a great job!
Regardless of what Deavor's
pie charts say or whatever...
But they want you.
(STRAINED)
And you'll do a great...
job...
too.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Well, that was excruciating to watch.
- (CHUCKLES)
- I can't lie to you.
It's nice to be wanted.
Flattering, you know, but...
But what's the choice?
One, do this right,
get well paid,
we're out of the motel...
and things get better
for all Supers,
including our kids.
Or two...
I find a job in two weeks
or we're homeless.
You know
it's crazy, right?
To help my family,
I gotta leave it.
To fix the law,
I gotta break it.
You'll be great.
I know I will.
But what about you?
We have kids.
I'll watch the kids,
no problem.
- Easy.
- Easy, huh?
You're adorable.
Well, if there is
a problem,
I'll drop this thing
and come right back.
You won't need to.
I got it,
you go do this thing.
Do it so...
I can do it better. (GRUNTS)
- (PHONE RINGS)
- Deavor here.
This is Elastigirl.
I'm in.
Mr. Deavor,
it's wonderful...
but it's too generous.
Nonsense! That's the
least we can do.
We're partners now!
Can't have my partners
living in a motel.
(STAMMERS) But whose house?
Is it a house?
WINSTON: It's my house.
I have several.
I'm not using that one.
Stay as long as you need.
I don't know
what to say.
How about "thanks"?
This is our new house?
(CHUCKLES) Okay, easy, tiger.
It's being loaned to us.
(GROANS) This is homey.
BOB: Look at this place.
Deavor bought it from
an eccentric billionaire...
who liked to come and go
without being seen...
so the house has
multiple hidden exits.
Good thing
we won't stand out.
Wouldn't want to attract
any unnecessary attention.
DASH:
It's got a big yard!
Isn't this a bit much?
Near a forest!
Would you rather be
at the motel?
DASH: And a pool!
(SPLASHES)
What exactly
is Mom's new job?
The important thing is
we're out of the motel.
I like Mom's new job!
(GASPS) Oh, ho, ho!
- BOB: Whoa.
- (BOTH CHUCKLES)
Whoa.
Well, check out
the water features.
(HELEN CHUCKLES)
- (CHUCKLES) Oh!
- Wow.
Wicked cool!
(BOB CHUCKLES)
- Hey! Dash! Stop it!
- (GROANS)
- ELASTIGIRL: Not the couch! Stop it!
- No! Dash!
- (GRUNTING)
- BOB: Stop!
- Don't touch the buttons!
- DASH: The couch!
- HELEN: Dash!
- BOB: No!
- (WHIMPERS)
- BOB: No, no!
HELEN: Oh, no. Oh, boy.
- ELASTIGIRL: This isn't me. (STAMMERING)
- (JACK-JACK COOING)
I'm not all dark
and angsty.
I'm Elastigirl.
I'm, you know,
flexible.
E designed this?
No, some guy named
Alexander Galbaki.
(CHUCKLING)
Glad it's you and not me,
'cause you're gonna
hear from her.
This note came with it.
What?
(DOOR BEEPS)
(GASPS)
A new Elasticycle.
Elasticycle? I didn't
know you had a bike.
Hey, I had a mohawk.
There's a lot about me
you don't know.
Yeah, but...
A mohawk?
Ah, you didn't miss anything.
(POWERING UP)
Oh, yeah!
This one's electric.
- What's that mean?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
(GROANS)
Means it's torque-y.
I'll get the hang of it.
You will be great.
I will be great.
And you will, too.
We will both be great.
Bye, sweetie.
(ELASTIGIRL WHOOPS)
(LAUGHING IN DELIGHT)
(WHOOPING)
Wait a minute!
- Is that Elastigirl?
- I think that's Elastigirl.
- Hey! Elastigirl!
- (ALL CHEERING)
MAN: Marry me, Elastigirl!
WINSTON:
♪ Here comes Elastigirl ♪
♪ Stretching her ♪
(LAUGHS) No theme songs
or I'll turn this bus
right around!
Look at that.
New Urbem.
You wanna make a big
crime fighting statement...
you go where
the crime is big.
Strange thing to be
excited about, Winston.
It's like
a superhero's playground!
(DASH GASPS)
BOB: No Sugar Bombs
on my watch.
- (DASH GROANS)
- (JACK-JACK GIGGLES)
Where's Mom?
She's up and out.
She's at her new job
doing hero work.
But I thought superheroes
were still illegal.
They are, for now.
So Mom is getting paid
to break the law?
She's not breaking...
She's an advocate
for superheroes.
It's a new job.
So, Mom is going out
illegally...
to explain why
she shouldn't be illegal.
Hey... Hey!
- The bus is here!
- (BUS HORN HONKING)
Whoa! Grab your stuff quickly!
Go on, get on the...
Put your homework
in your pack!
Bye-bye!
(EXHALES)
(JACK-JACK GIGGLING)
We're gonna get along
just fine...
- 'cause you don't ask any hard questions.
- (STOMACH GROWLING)
(THUDS)
- (GIGGLES)
- (SIGHS)
OFFICER #1:
All right. All locations,
we need to know
where you want us.
OFFICER #2: Stand by.
Seems strange
to wait for crime.
WINSTON: Relax.
You're smack in the middle...
of the worst crime area
in the city. It's perfect.
It's a superhero's
playground.
"It's a superhero's
playground." Right.
You know,
after we went underground...
my husband used to listen
to a police scanner...
waiting for something
to happen.
And I got mad at him
for it.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Oh, I'm such a hypocrite.
- DISPATCHER: All units.
- Something's up.
We've been picking up
some chatter about
potential disruptions to the
hovertrain's opening ceremony.
- OFFICER: Disruption or threat?
- DISPATCHER: Both.
Station's at Fifty-Fourth
and Nottingham.
(GASPS) A potential threat!
Perfect!
Fifty-fourth and Nottingham.
Go, go, go!
Hey, Vi! I want you
back here by 10:30.
11-ish?
10-ish,
heading for 9:30-ish.
10:30-ish it is. (SIGHS)
Enjoy the movie.
"In the county of Noddoff...
"the Frubbers of Freep...
"are all giving in to
the sweet succor of sleep."
(SIGHS)
VIC PERRIN: (ON TV)
We will control the horizontal...
we will control the vertical.
That's not the way you're
supposed to do it, Dad.
They want us
to do it this way.
I don't know that way!
Why would they change math?
- It's okay, Dad.
- Math is math!
I'll just wait for Mom
to get back.
What?
She won't understand it
any better than I do...
VIC PERRIN: (ON TV)
The Outer Limits.
(JACK-JACK GIGGLES)
"All over Doozle-Dorf,
"the Fribbers of Frupp
are going to sleep...
"'cause they just
can't keep up.
"All over Doozle-Dorf,
Doozles are dozing.
"Eyelids so heavy,
they're drooping.
(BOB SNORES)
"Closing! The point is:
"Everyone,
everyone's hitting the sack!
"Everyone's getting the sleep
that they lack."
Mayors often brag
about their cities...
(CHUCKLES)
and I'm no exception.
And I'm willing to admit
that New Urbem
is not the only city...
Are you sure the police are
gonna be okay with this?
EVELYN: Sure. You're making
life easy for them.
They still haven't
forgiven us
for the last time we made
life easy for them.
I know the Chief of Police.
There won't be a problem.
With all due respect...
if you alone had handled
the Underminer...
things would have
been different.
I'm just saying.
MAYOR: ...on budget
and ahead of schedule...
to launch our magnificent
new hovertrain.
It can get you
where you need to go
at ridiculous speeds.
The future is open
for business!
- (MARCHING BAND PLAYING)
- (PEOPLE CHEERING)
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Wait. The train has stopped.
(PEOPLE GASPS)
It's going
the wrong direction.
It's going the wrong way.
I'm going after it.
- (PEOPLE CLAMORING)
- This thing's really moving.
100 and climbing.
How much track is built?
EVELYN: About 25 miles.
(GRUNTS) No one can shut
this thing down?
EVELYN: They've tried. No-go.
Is that Elastigirl?
- (SIRENS WAILING)
- (BOTH GASPS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Overrides?
They're locked out
of the system.
(ELASTIGIRL GRUNTING)
- What about a fail-safe?
- EVELYN: Not enough time.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Someone's calling!
Switching over.
DASH: Hey, Mom.
I can't find my high-tops
and Dad
can't find them either.
But he won't call you
and ask, so I am.
BOB:
Do not call your mother!
Dash, honey.
Can't talk right now.
Look under your bed, okay.
How much time?
EVELYN:
Less than two minutes!
There's a shortcut. Cut
through the culvert up ahead.
I don't know
if I can stay with it.
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GASPS)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS AND GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLES)
(ALL GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
- MAN: What the heck was that?
Is everybody all right?
Is anybody injured?
Are you all right?
Your story better be good.
- Hey. Hey!
- (GRUNTS)
What happened?
(BEEPING)
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
Honey, why are you...
Don't say anything.
It's Dad.
Are you okay?
VIOLET: I'm fine.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Tony didn't even call?
VIOLET:
I don't wanna talk about it.
- Oh, honey...
- VIOLET: Dad!
If you want me to feel
better, then leave me alone.
Please?
ROMAN: (ON TV)
See, there's nothing
a cop hates worse
than a missing child.
My kid brother's son.
Today is his first birthday.
WOMAN: Oh, but if anybody
can find that child,
it's you, Roman.
Because you're
a wonderful policeman.
- ROBBER #1: This is a holdup.
- (BOB SNORING)
All right, get your hands up,
turn your back.
ROBBER #2:
Put your hands behind
your heads
and keep them there!
Don't move!
Drop that.
All right, now get over there.
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
- Watch the door.
ROBBER #1:
You think I'm kiddin'?
Now.
(SIRENS WAILING)
I said now!
ROBBER #1: I got it!
Come on, I tell you, come on!
(SQUEALS)
ROBBER #2:
You wanna get killed?
(STRAINS)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTING)
(SNARLS)
(CHITTERING)
(JACK-JACK GRUNTS)
- (GROWLING)
- (GRUNTING)
(BOB SNORING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (GASPS)
- (JACK-JACK YELLING)
(RACCOON CHITTERING)
(JACK-JACK COUGHS)
- Uh-oh.
- (JACK-JACK GIGGLING)
- (SQUEAKS)
(YELPS)
(RACCOON GROWLS)
- (RACCOON SHRIEKING)
- (JACK-JACK COOING)
- (JACK-JACK SQUEALING)
- (CRASHING)
(GASPING)
(BOB GRUNTING)
- BOB: No, no, no!
- (JACK-JACK SNARLING)
(RACCOON GROWLING)
- No!
- (ALL COOING)
BOB: No, no, no.
No, no, no.
- No, no, no!
- (SNARLING)
(RACCOON GROWLING)
(SHOUTING GIBBERISH)
(GIGGLING)
You have powers!
Yeah, baby,
and there's not
a scratch on you!
Did you go through
the locked door?
- Are those your powers?
- (CHUCKLES)
Who can multiply
like rabbits
and go right through
any solid...
- (SNEEZES)
- (YELPS)
- Oh, my God!
- (GIGGLING)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
- HELEN: Hey, honey.
- You weren't gonna call me?
- BOB: Oh, hey!
(STAMMERING)
No. I mean, yes, yeah...
- I just didn't wanna wake you.
- (JACK-JACK BABBLING)
The strangest thing just
happened out in the yard.
Sounds like I just
woke you up.
No, no.
- It's just, Jack-Jack...
- He had an accident!
I knew it!
I'm coming home right now!
I never should have...
No accident. Stay there
and finish your mission.
You never should...
What? You don't think
I can do this?
No, no.
Sorry. I misspoke.
Do you need me
to come back?
No, no. No, I've got this.
Everything's great.
What happened
with Jack-Jack?
Nothing.
He's in excellent health.
- Well, that's good.
- (VIOLET SOBBING)
- How was Violet's date?
- BOB: Uh...
HELEN:
That was tonight, right?
BOB: (STAMMERING)
Yes. Good.
All fine and good.
And Jack-Jack went down
with no trouble?
- (JACK-JACK COOING)
- Fine, yes, no trouble.
And Dash got
his homework done?
BOB: All done.
So, things haven't
spiraled out
of control
the moment I left?
Amazing as it may seem,
it has been
quite uneventful in fact.
How about you?
I saved a runaway train!
(LAUGHING IN DELIGHT)
It was so great!
The mayor was there to cut
the ribbon on this new train.
REPORTER #1:
Elastigirl pursued the train
and was able
to successfully activate...
Blah, blah, blah. He says a
few words, cuts the ribbon...
and the train starts pulling
out of the station
backwards...
REPORTER #2:
...track of its brand new hovertrain...
...malfunctioned...
...thanking Elastigirl...
REPORTER #3:
Superhero Elastigirl...
REPORTER #4: Elastigirl...
Boom! No casualties!
(SQUEALS)
REPORTER #5:
...specialized motorbike,
saving all of
the passengers...
HELEN:
One thing leads to another
and suddenly,
I go after it!
I'm telling you, honey,
it was a saga!
That's fantastic, honey!
And on your first night!
I am so proud of you, really.
I'm proud of you, honey.
I know you want to get out
there and you will soon.
And you'll be amazing.
I couldn't have done this
if you hadn't
taken over so well.
Thanks for handling
everything.
It's nothing.
(SIGHS) I love you, honey.
I'll be back soon.
- Sweet dreams.
- Sweet dreams, honey.
(SIGHS)
(SNORING)
(BOB MUMBLING)
(IMITATES DASH)
"Hey, Dad, it's okay.
"I'll just wait for Mom
to get home."
As if she could...
I know how to...
I can do math.
(GROANS)
Oh, brother...
(MUMBLING)
(IMITATES DASH)
Wait for Mom!
What am I,
a substitute parent?
It's not my fault
they changed math.
Come on, buddy.
Come on.
I think I understand
your math assignment.
We still have some time
to finish it before your test.
So first, you wanna put
all the numbers
by themselves on one side.
...you change the sign.
That means a plus becomes
a minus and a minus...
You got it?
Yeah, baby!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Oh. Uh, hello.
We're in a new house.
I did write my address
on your locker...
in permanent ink.
Oh, is that what that is?
Did you forget?
Forget what?
(CHUCKLING) That's funny.
Points for funny.
Oh, was it
the weird outfit?
- (CHUCKLES)
- Because there's a reason.
I'm in a drama class...
and they just wanna do
Shakespeare...
but they're like, "Try to make
it relevant for the kids."
So, like, "Oh, superheroes!
Kids love superheroes."
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You wanna wear
one kind of tights...
and then they're like,
"No, wear these
other kind of tights."
(STAMMERS) Do I know you?
Many say your speech
today is critical.
Both sides just want the
best for their people.
We are so close to finally
getting peace in the region.
I haven't done this
in a while.
This is good. The train
gives us momentum.
Just go out there and
be your charming self...
and capitalize on it.
Ms. Elastigirl,
they're ready for you.
Hey, stretch a leg.
Thank you, Chad.
It was fun.
Ambassador, your documents.
We're moving to the rooftop.
Oh, Madame Ambassador,
hello!
Oh, you are Elastigirl!
This is why now
I'm shaking your hand.
It was so sad
when you went underground.
I am glad to see you back
in your shiny outfit.
That means so much
coming from you.
Good luck
with your speech.
This way, Ambassador.
(STAMMERS)
Bring lasting peace!
I will,
when you defeat evil.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
Three, two...
For over 15 years,
superheroes have been
in hiding.
Forced into it
by a society
no longer willing
to support them.
That may soon be changing...
due to a growing movement
to bring the Supers back.
Here, fresh on the heels
of her own
heroic save
of a runaway train...
and sporting a new look,
is the superhero, Elastigirl.
- Welcome!
- Hello, Chad.
All the polls are going
in your direction.
That's true.
Things are good...
Hello.
Uh, hello?
Do I have your attention?
Yes, Chad.
Of course I do.
I'm appearing
on your screen.
Reading the words I'm saying
off of another screen.
Screens are everywhere.
We are controlled by screens.
(ELASTIGIRL WHIMPERING)
And screens
are controlled by me...
Screenslaver.
Hey!
SCREENSLAVER:
I control this broadcast...
and this idiotic anchorman
you see before you.
WOMAN:
What's wrong with him?
The signal's been hijacked.
I'll check it out.
Don't look at any monitors.
I could hijack
the ambassador's aerocade...
while it's still airborne.
Right, Elastigirl?
Nearest window!
Where's the nearest window?
- Oh, what's going on?
- Where's Elastigirl?
(GROANS) Which one?
(ELASTIGIRL GRUNTING)
Elastigirl!
What are you doing here?
The ambassador is in danger.
Which chopper is she...
Look out!
Follow them
and get me close!
Get out of the sky,
and touch down safely!
- (GRUNTS)
- Stand down! It's Elastigirl.
Stay in your seat, ma'am!
- (GROANS, GASPS)
- We're under attack!
Quick, go!
Protect the ambassador!
Open the door!
Do as she says!
Can you all swim?
- ALL: Yeah.
- No!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(AMBASSADOR GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
ELASTIGIRL: We're gonna have
to slingshot! Hang on!
- (ELASTIGIRL GRUNTING)
- (AMBASSADOR SCREAMING)
- (PANTING)
- Are you all right, ma'am?
I'm perfectly fine...
BOB: Ah! Ooh! Ah! Oh!
Boys are jerks
and superheroes suck.
Good morning!
He takes one look
at me in that suit...
and decides to pretend
he doesn't even know me.
He's protecting himself.
If he really did see you,
it's best that he forget.
It's better for you, too.
I can't tell you
how many memories
Dicker's had to erase
over the years...
(SNIFFS)
when someone figured out
your mother's
or my identity.
- (GASPS)
- It was Dicker!
- You told him about Tony!
- Honey...
You had me erased
from Tony's mind!
(DOOR SLAMS)
- (JACK-JACK GIGGLING)
- (DOOR OPENS)
I hate superheroes!
And I renounce them!
(WHIRRING)
I renounce them!
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(FOOTSTEPS RETREATING)
Is she having adolescence?
(DOOR SLAMS)
REPORTER:
A new report out today shows that,
when it comes
to decision-making...
people have more trust
in a monkey
throwing darts than Congress.
What's going on, Tommy?
A protest?
- (PROTESTERS CHANTING)
- They're here in support.
Support? Support of what?
TOMMY:
Well, in support of you.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Wow. Oh, hey...
Thanks for coming out. Hi.
Oh, my goodness.
Thanks so much.
Oh, hello.
What does your sign say?
ALL: (CHANTING)
Ka-boom! Ka-pow!
Supers should be legal now!
Talk to ya.
Oh, what do ya know!
Ellenwood.
Oh, now you wanna
return my calls
about superheroes, huh?
Oh. I'll have to
call you back.
Oh, that felt good.
Felicia, hold my calls,
please.
Hey!
It's working!
Hey, the ambassador
made a big speech
about superheroes today.
Turns out
saving someone's life
makes a good impression
on them. Who knew, huh?
I'm getting calls
from all over the world.
Media awareness
is up 72%.
The push
for superhero legalization
is becoming
a worldwide movement!
I have big plans
for our next move.
We're gonna have
a summit at sea.
We'll use our ship...
we'll gather leaders
and Supers...
- from all over the world.
- That's great.
I'm happy.
I'm happy
the numbers are up.
I'm happy the ambassador
is pro-superhero...
and I'm happy
you're happy.
I'm hearing that you're happy,
but why am I not feeling it?
Because I didn't get him!
Screenslaver
is still out there.
All I did was play his game
and win this round.
He's gonna want more
and as long as
he gets to play, he wins.
One thing
I've learned in business?
Smell the flowers.
They don't bloom that often.
What do you want
on your tombstone?
"She worried a lot"?
EVELYN:
All right, stop talking.
Show her.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This is just so exciting, isn't it?
Huh?
(CHATTER STOPS)
Oh, wow. Uh...
Wow! Elastigirl,
there you are.
- Hello.
- (STAMMERS) I didn't...
Wow!
Come on, get yourself
together, Karen.
Hi, my superhero name
is Voyd.
I just wanna thank you,
for, like, for being you!
(STAMMERING)
Okay, what I can do,
um, is this.
(ALL GASPS)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Yeah.
That is impressive.
Very interdimensional.
I felt like
an outcast before.
But now, with you being
you, I feel like...
(SIGHS)
Yay, me.
I flew them in
from all over.
They've all been
in hiding.
They have powers,
secret identities...
and names
they've given themselves.
I'm Screech.
It's a pleasure.
I've always considered you
the gold standard
for superheroes.
Well, thanks.
You're too nice.
I am called Brick.
Nice to meet you, Brick.
Uh, where are you from?
Wisconsin.
Oh. Elastigirl.
I assume your powers are...
You know,
zapping things electrically...
charging things, bolts of
lightning, that kind of stuff.
Name's Reflux.
Medical condition or
superpower, you decide.
(CHUCKLES)
That's a little line
I say just to put
people at ease.
Hope I don't offend.
Oh, no, no, no.
Reflux. Love it.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Well, I do look forward
to working with you.
Yes, that is impressive.
Keep practicing.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- Ow!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SNORING)
Well, I'm beat. Congratulations.
Big day.
Good night, ladies.
I will see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Must be nice for you,
being out front
after all this time.
Out front?
Well, it's been a while
since your superhero days...
and even then,
you were kind of
in Mr. Incredible's
shadow.
Nah, I beg to differ.
I'm not... I'm not
saying you weren't big.
No, you were,
and are, a superstar...
but you have the stage
to yourself now.
And people have
to pay attention.
Oh, you mean, "It's a man's
world" and all that?
Well, what world
do you live in?
Your brother runs DEVTECH.
I don't want his job.
I invent, he sells.
I ask you, which of us
has the greater influence?
Which side of me
are you asking?
The believer or the cynic?
The cynic...
Would say selling
is more important
because the best sellers
have the most buyers.
Doesn't matter
what you're selling.
It only matters
what people buy.
This is true.
If I discovered the
origin of the universe...
my brother
would find a way
to market it as a,
uh, foot massager.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
So, what would
the believer say?
The believer would tell you
to make your mark.
Don't wait for permission,
assert yourself
and impose your will
on the status quo.
- Sounds like my brother.
- What?
You sound like my brother.
Well, he's not wrong.
There is an art
to getting a reaction...
(GASPS)
Oh! I know how to get him.
- My brother?
- No. Screenslaver!
You're tech-savvy. I need
to lock onto a signal...
and trace its origin.
How fast can you
slap something together
and meet me
at the airport?
Airport?
Need to go
out of town, pronto.
I can get your contraption
together by 5:00 a.m.
I need to get on TV.
Chad!
I'll get my brother to set up
an exclusive with him
tonight on the newscast.
Finish our interview
by phone!
Promote the hell out of it.
Independence
from Screenslavery!
- Chad tonight.
- BOTH: Boom! (LAUGHING)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Dicker.
- BOB: Yeah, hey, Rick.
You remember that kid
I mentioned to you?
Tony Rydinger.
Mind wipe? Yeah, nice kid.
Well, you also wiped out
the Friday night date
my daughter had with him.
In fact,
you wiped out my daughter.
Oops.
Not an exact science, Bob.
Rick, you gotta help me here.
Violet hates me, and you,
and superheroes.
I gotta fix this.
What do you know about Tony?
Um...
Not much.
Seems like a good kid.
Popular,
plays sports, music.
Parents own The Happy Platter,
kid works there part time.
Happy Platter?
Why did we drive
all the way across town
for The Happy Platter?
We'd like a booth over there,
near the philodendron.
Good, right?
Near the philodendron.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This platter doesn't look
all that happy to me.
It looks bored.
Ha-ha! The Bored Platter!
I thought Vi would want
a change of pace
from drive-in food.
I like drive-in food.
Does this mean vegetables?
A balanced diet
means vegetables, kiddo.
Get used to it.
TONY:
Good evening, everyone.
- BOB: Oh, no!
- (COUGHING)
- Is she all right?
- Violet, are you okay?
- (COUGHING)
- Nothing to see here.
Yeah, more napkins
would be good.
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- It happens all the time here.
Mops it right up.
Normally, she doesn't
ever drip like this.
- Would you like water, sir?
- BOB: Yes.
Yes, I would.
This is my daughter...
- who you must know, right?
- God. Stop.
- Hello.
- Violet.
Hello, Violet.
(BOB CHUCKLING)
Hey, Vi, say hi to...
Don't push it, Dad.
I'm Dash,
her little brother.
Hello.
Mmm. This is
really good water.
It's very refreshing.
Spring water, is it?
I don't know, sir.
I think it's tap.
Well, it is very good.
Excellent tap.
Excuse me.
Well, nice to meet you.
- Where'd she go?
- DASH: Mmm.
To find a good place
to be angry?
Tonight, we go now to
a special remote interview...
with Elastigirl.
ELASTIGIRL:
How you feeling, Chad?
You doing all right?
I'm fine.
The doctors checked me out.
(STAMMERS)
I have no memory of the event.
I gotta tell you,
it's pretty strange
to see a recording...
of yourself the night before
and have no recollection.
I don't think
anyone needs to worry.
We've taken many precautions
tonight though.
Where are you right now?
On a case, in a secure
undisclosed location.
CHAD:
I wanna talk about you...
starting with your save
of a runaway train.
Here's an exclusive
unedited clip
from your own suit cam.
Roll the clip.
ELASTIGIRL:
This thing's really moving.
100 and climbing.
How much track is built?
EVELYN: About 25 miles.
SCREENSLAVER: The Screenslaver
interrupts this program...
for an important announcement.
I'll be damned. She knew.
Let's see
if your gadget works.
Don't bother
watching the rest.
Gotcha!
Elastigirl doesn't
save the day.
She only postpones her defeat.
And while she postpones
her defeat...
you eat chips and watch
her confront problems...
that you are too lazy
to deal with.
Superheroes are part
of your brainless desire...
to replace true experience
with simulation.
You don't talk,
you watch talk shows.
You don't play games,
you watch game shows.
Travel, relationships, risk...
every meaningful experience
must be packaged...
and delivered to you
to watch at a distance.
So that you can remain
ever sheltered...
ever passive...
ever ravenous consumers...
who can't bring themselves
to rise from their couches...
break a sweat
and participate in life.
You want superheroes
to protect you...
and make yourselves ever more
powerless in the process.
While you tell yourselves
you're being looked after.
That your interests
are being served.
And your rights
are being upheld.
So that the system can
keep stealing from you...
smiling at you all the while.
Go ahead,
send your Supers to stop me.
Grab your snacks,
watch your screens,
and see what happens.
You are no longer in control.
I am.
(MACHINES BEEPING)
(CLOCK CHIMING)
SCREENSLAVER: Find anything?
(GROANING)
(YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALARM RINGING)
- (GRUNTS)
- Sorry!
(ELASTIGIRL GROANS)
(BEEPS)
(EXPLOSION)
(GRUNTING)
(STAMMERS) What happened?
What happened is
you destroyed my evidence.
What's going on?
What did I do?
What did you guys do to me?
That's right, punk.
Blame the system.
Your tracker worked
like a charm, Evelyn.
You're a genius.
Aw, shucks!
I'm just the genius
behind the genius.
- (TV PLAYING)
- DASH: Hey, Dad.
We're doing fractions
and denismals and percentages
and I don't get 'em.
Aren't you...
Didn't we get all caught up?
Yeah, we were caught up...
and now we're doing fractions
and percentages and demicels.
Decimals.
NEWS ANCHOR: (ON TV)
...the addition of the Incredibile,
the super car...
once driven by superhero,
Mr. Incredible.
It's the kind of thing you buy
when you have everything else.
They said it was
beyond repair.
VICTOR CATCHET:
Hey, it was in perfect condition.
You used to
drive that?
They said it was destroyed.
Long thought lost
or destroyed,
the famous car
turned up at private auction.
They said it was...
That's my car!
- (TV CONTINUES PLAYING)
- (GRUNTS)
(COUGHING)
Stupid water feature!
This car is just loaded
with amazing gadgets.
Care to demonstrate?
I'd love to,
but we haven't figured out
how to make them work yet.
(BOTH GASPS)
- Wow! It works?
- (PEOPLE ON TV SCREAMING)
Huh?
What are you doing?
This is not a toy!
That's a rocket launcher!
Sweet! Which one launches
the rocket?
Hey!
This is not your car!
It's not your car,
either!
It is so!
It's the Incredibile.
- Why's that guy have it?
- He shouldn't!
Launch the rockets!
- I'm not launching anything!
- I wanna blow it up!
Do you think I want
an angry rich guy...
coming after me right now...
- when I'm trying not to...
- I'm not sure
- what's happened here, Mark.
- ...distract your mother.
But everyone here
has scattered
and I'm afraid I'll need
to move at any minute.
(GROANS)
Rich guy got my car.
So, you're not gonna
steal your car
back from the rich guy?
- (SNEEZES)
- (BOB GASPS)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(VIOLET SCREAMING)
What the heck is that?
(GROWLING)
- (LAUGHING)
- (SIGHS)
Jack-Jack has powers?
Well, yeah, but...
- You knew about this?
- Yeah.
- VIOLET: Why didn't you tell us?
- I don't know.
We're your kids. We need
to know these things.
- Did you tell Mom?
- No.
- Why not?
- Your mother is not...
You'd want us to tell you,
wouldn't you?
- Why would you not tell Mom?
- Because I didn't wanna...
What?
- Come on, man.
- Because it's not the time.
- Why?
- Because...
So uncool!
Because I'm formulating, okay?
I'm taking in information,
I'm processing!
I'm doing the math,
I'm fixing the boyfriend...
and keeping the baby
from turning into
a flaming monster!
How do I do it?
By rolling with
the punches, baby!
I eat thunder
and crap lightning, okay?
'Cause I'm Mr. Incredible!
Not Mr. So-So
or Mr. Mediocre-Guy.
Mr. Incredible!
(JACK-JACK CHUCKLES)
We should call Lucius.
No. I can handle it.
- There's no way I'm gonna...
- (SNEEZES)
(BOB GASPS)
(YELLING)
(JACK-JACK SCREAMING)
Dada.
I'm calling Lucius.
- (TV PLAYING)
- (LAUGHING)
Looks normal to me. When
did this start happening?
Since Helen got the job.
- I assume she knows?
- Are you kidding?
I can't tell her
about this,
not while she's doing
hero work!
Mama!
ELASTIGIRL: (ON TV)
Girls, come on.
Leave the saving the world
to the men?
- I don't think so.
- Mama!
I've got to succeed!
So she can succeed.
- So we can succeed!
- I get it, Bob!
I get it. When was the
last time you slept?
Who keeps track of that?
Besides, he's a baby.
I can handle it,
I got this handled.
So, you good then?
You got everything
under control? Right?
(JACK-JACK GURGLING)
What the...?
(JACK-JACK GURGLING
FROM OTHER DIMENSION)
Cookie! Cha Cha want a cookie?
Num-num cookie?
Cha Cha wanna num-num?
Num-num cookie! Cookie!
- You're not...
- Cookie!
- Oh, my God!
- Dada! Dada. Dada.
- LUCIUS: Whoa.
Okay! Okay.
So, he can still
hear you from the...
From the other
dimension, yeah.
That is freaky.
I mean, that's not like...
Not like our other kids.
No, it is not.
- Full powers, totally random.
- (GURGLING)
So now, he's what?
Is he good?
Yeah, you'd think so,
right?
Obviously, I can't keep
giving him cookies!
- Uh-uh?
- But if I stop...
(GROWLING)
Ahhh! He is freaking!
Again, he is freaking!
No biting the daddy!
- What the...?
- No biting!
- (CRYING)
- Okay.
I think I just need
a little bit of me time.
Then I'll be good to go.
Oh, you need
more than me time, Bob.
You need
major life realignment
on a number of levels.
Starting with
baby superfreak here!
You need some solid
outside-the-box thinking.
Galbaki?
Elastigirl's supersuit
is by Galbaki?
Explain yourself!
(JACK-JACK CRYING)
Oh, my God.
You're worse than I thought.
It's the baby.
I brought the baby.
(JACK-JACK SQUEALS)
Oh, highly unusual.
You look ghastly, Robert.
I haven't been sleeping.
I broke my daughter,
they keep changing math...
we needed double-A batteries,
but I got triple-A's...
and now we still need
double-A batteries.
I put one red thing
in a load of whites
and now
everything's pink.
And I think
we need eggs.
Done properly,
parenting is a heroic act.
Done properly.
I am fortunate that it has
never afflicted me.
But you do not come to me
for eggs and batteries,
Robert.
I design herowear
and Elastigirl
must have a new suit.
(SIGHS)
Actually, it's Jack-Jack.
You also wish
a new suit for the baby?
I would hardly classify
this as an emergency.
Well, he's a special case.
Worth studying.
If I could just leave him
with you for a while...
Leave him? Here?
I am not a baby person,
Robert.
I have no baby facilities.
I am an artist.
I do not involve myself in
the prosaic day-to-day to...
day.
(CHUCKLES)
Fascinating!
Are you seeing this, Robert?
Dada.
(SNEEZES)
(SCREAMING)
- (GIGGLING)
- Oh, my God.
Yes!
Of course you can leave
the baby overnight.
I'm sure filling in
for Helen is challenging,
and you are very tired...
and the other children
need you
and miss you,
and you must go to them.
Auntie Edna will take care
of everything...
so, drive safely and goodbye.
I enjoy our visits.
"Auntie Edna"?
- (UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (GLASS CLINKING)
- WINSTON: Attention. Attention.
I wanna thank everyone
that came out tonight...
in support of superheroes...
and bringing them
back into society!
- (ALL APPLAUDING)
- You all made it happen.
The need for this
has been made
crystal clear
in recent days...
with bad actors
like the self-proclaimed
Screenslaver
threatening our peace.
His reign was short, huh?
- (ALL CHEER)
- And thanks to this woman...
a great super. You love her.
You missed her.
- Welcome back, Elastigirl.
- (ALL CHEERING)
Come on up here.
Don't be bashful.
- Come on. Get up here.
- (GLASSES CLINKING)
I want you to have this.
A memento.
Thanks, Winston, Evelyn,
and everyone at DEVTECH.
I am forever in your debt.
And thanks to all of you,
your pressure
changed all the right minds.
We've made amazing headway
in a very short time...
which leads me to an
important announcement.
Just now,
at a worldwide summit...
leaders from
more than a hundred
of the world's
top countries...
have agreed to make
superheroes legal again!
(ALL CHEERING)
We'll gather superheroes
and leaders
from all over
the planet...
on our boat,
the Everjust...
for a televised
signing ceremony at sea.
Now if you'll excuse us,
we got a ship to catch!
(ALL CHEERING)
WINSTON: So good to see you.
Thanks for coming out.
Hey.
Hi, it's me, again.
Um, there's, uh, something
I've always wanted to ask you.
Yeah, how do you balance
the superhero stuff
with the life stuff?
I know I can handle
the superhero stuff.
(CONVERSATION FADES)
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Oh.
Would you please
excuse me a moment?
Oh. Yeah, okay, see you later!
Good talk!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- BOB: Hey, Vi.
- Hey.
Where's Jack-Jack?
BOB: E's taking him
for a little bit.
- Edna is babysitting?
- Yeah.
And you're okay with this?
Yeah. I don't know why,
but yeah.
(BOB SIGHS)
I wanted to say
something to you.
Sorry about Tony.
I didn't think about Dicker
erasing his memory...
or about you having to pay
the price for a choice...
you never made.
It's not fair, I know.
And then, I made it worse
at the restaurant
by trying to...
Anyway. Anyway...
I'm sorry.
I'm used to knowing
what the right thing
to do is...
but now,
I'm not sure anymore.
I just wanna be...
(SIGHS)
a good dad.
VIOLET: You're not good.
You're super.
(BOB SNORING)
Are superheroes allowed
to drink on duty?
I'm definitely not on duty.
Ignore the costume.
I know
I should be up there...
but I had to step away from
the grip and grins, you know?
Gotta get away to keep it pure.
I know I do.
What are you getting
away from?
Eh, you know, company stuff.
My brother, mostly.
But you love him,
you two are this company.
Yin and yang.
Yeah, I invent the stuff,
he's good at people.
Pleasing them, engaging them,
figuring out what they want.
I never know
what people want.
What do you think
they want?
Ease.
People will trade quality
for ease every time.
It may be crap,
but hey, it's convenient.
Yeah. Kind of
like this case.
What?
The Screenslaver?
Yeah, something's not
sitting right.
It was too easy.
That was too easy?
(CHUCKLES) Wow.
- Funny.
- What?
Look at that.
One of Screenslaver's monitors
is tuned into my suit cam.
What?
Isn't the suit cam
closed circuit?
It is.
Then how come
Screenslaver has it?
Maybe he hacked it?
So, he's sophisticated enough
to do that...
but he has simple locks
on his doors?
Maybe he wanted you
to find him.
He wanted to get caught?
He wanted you to win.
That makes no sense.
He's a brilliant guy.
If he's smart enough
to conceive
of technology like this...
he's smart enough to think
of something to do with it.
The guy we put in jail
delivered pizzas.
So?
Einstein was
a patent clerk.
Look, you won.
You got the guy who...
Wait. All Screenslaver
needs to do
to hypnotize someone...
is get a screen
in front of their eyes.
But what if the screen
doesn't look like a screen?
What if the pizza guy
is really a pizza guy...
but he was controlled
by the screens
built into his glasses...
You are good.
JONNY QUEST: (ON TV)
Look, the robot!
It's taking off.
DR. QUEST:
I'm not getting a reading yet.
- RACE: Press "fire"?
- DR. QUEST: Now!
(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
More power.
JONNY QUEST:
Oh, I hope this works, Dad.
I thought it was best
to just let you sleep.
Seventeen hours.
- How do you feel?
- (CHUCKLES)
Super.
- You got it, Dad.
- Hurray!
BOB: I can't tell you
how much I appreciate
you watching
Jack-Jack for me, E.
Yes, I'm sure your gratitude
is quite inexpressible.
Don't ask me
to do it again, darling.
My rates are far too high.
Oh, uh...
I am joking, Robert.
I enjoyed the assignment.
He is bright
and I am stimulating.
We deserve each other.
Your child is a polymorph.
Like all babies,
he has enormous potential.
It is not unknown
for supers
to have more than one
power when young...
- but this little one has many.
- (BABBLING)
Yes, you have many powers.
(BABBLING)
EDNA: I understand
your lack of sleep
and coherency, Robert.
Babies can be anything,
and your child
is no exception.
He has pure,
unlimited potential, Robert.
He slept while I worked
in a creative fever.
Auntie Edna stayed up
all night...
making sure you look
fabulous in your many forms.
What are you... You're
putting him in the...
In the chamber, Robert.
He is part
of the demonstration
and will be fine.
Your challenge
is to manage a baby
who has
multiple powers...
and no control
over them, yes?
Huh. That sums it up.
I often work to music
and I noticed the baby
responds to it as well.
Specifically, Mozart.
- (CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- I blended Kevlar
with carbyne for
durability under duress...
and cotton for comfort.
Interwoven with these fabrics
are a mesh of tiny sensors...
that monitor the baby's
physical properties.
Oh, Lord! (STAMMERS)
What is he doing?
Well, it's Mozart, Robert.
Can you blame him?
The important thing is that
the suit and tracker...
anticipated the change
and alerted you.
Oh, no. Cookies.
I gotta get cookies!
You do not need cookies.
As I learned quite painfully
last night...
any solution involving cookies
will inevitably result
in the demon baby.
(GROWLING)
"Combustion imminent"?
What does that mean?
(YELPS)
It means fire, Robert,
for which the suit
has countermeasures.
I suggest you extinguish
the baby's flames
before he trips
the sprinkler system.
- (BOB EXHALES)
- The flame retardant
is blackberry lavender,
darling.
Effective, edible,
and delicious.
Well, what do you know?
That is useful.
Although, I have doubtlessly
exceeded your expectations
for a single night's work...
the suit
and device contain
a few more features
we need to discuss.
Thanks again, E,
for everything.
How much
do I owe you for...
Pish-posh, darling. Your bill
will be covered by my fee...
for being Mr. Incredible,
Elastigirl,
and Frozone's
exclusive designer...
throughout the known universe
and until the end of time.
But babysitting this one...
I do for free, darling.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
EVELYN: (ON SPEAKERS)
I would resist
the temptation to stretch.
The temperature around you
is well below freezing.
Try to stretch
and you'll break.
So, you're
the Screenslaver.
Yes and no.
Let's say,
I created the character
and pre-recorded
the messages.
- Does Winston know?
- (SCOFFS)
That I'm the Screenslaver?
Of course not.
Can you imagine
what Mr. Free Enterprise
would do
with my hypnosis technology?
Worse than
what you're doing?
Hey, I'm using
the technology
to destroy
people's trust in it.
Like I'm using superheroes.
Who did I put in jail?
Pizza delivery guy.
Seemed the right height,
build.
He gave you
a pretty good fight.
I should say I gave you
a pretty good fight
through him.
(SHIVERING)
But it doesn't bother you
that an innocent man
is in jail?
Eh, he was surly
and the pizza was cold.
I counted on you.
That's why you failed.
What?
Why would you count on me?
Because I built you a bike?
Because my brother
knows the words
to your theme song?
We don't know each other.
But you can
count on me anyway.
I am supposed to,
aren't I?
Because you have
some strange abilities
and a shiny costume...
the rest of us are supposed
to put our lives
into your gloved hands.
That's what
my father believed.
When our home was broken into,
my mother wanted to hide.
Begged my father
to use the safe room.
But Father insisted they call
his superhero friends.
He died,
pointlessly, stupidly...
waiting for heroes
to save the day.
But why would you...
- Your brother...
- Is a child!
He remembers the time
when we had parents
and superheroes.
So, like a child,
Winston conflates the two.
Mommy and Daddy went away
because supers went away.
Our sweet parents
were fools
to put their lives
in anybody else's hands.
Superheroes keep us weak.
Are you gonna kill me?
Nah.
Using you is better.
You're gonna help me make
supers illegal...
forever.
(GRUNTING)
Dada. Dada.
Ready?
Laser eyes.
Stop.
- Wow!
- Yeah!
- Yay, Jack-Jack!
- Yeah, baby!
And that's not all.
Watch this.
Jack-Jack, blaster ready?
(IMITATES BLASTER FIRING)
- DASH: No way.
- That is crazy cool.
My turn.
I get to blast him first!
- Let me try. I want him.
- Give him to me.
Hey, I'm just demonstrating.
No firing the baby around
the house, you understand?
This is potentially
dangerous...
and we're trying to teach him
to control his powers, okay?
- (BEEPING)
- Stop. See the screen.
He vanished!
That's really cool!
(JACK-JACK BABBLING
FROM OTHER DIMENSION)
Okay, good. Use the thing.
That's the current readout.
Click it. See the readout?
Dimension four.
See the shape?
That's the room.
See where he is in relation?
So, where is he?
He's... there!
Okay. Come out.
Num-num cookie?
- Yay, Jack-Jack!
- Yeah, Jack-Jack!
- That's really cool.
- (ALARM BEEPING)
- Hello?
- Elastigirl's in trouble.
What? What happened to her?
Sorry to tell you
on the phone.
Meet me on our ship
at DEVTECH.
The ship at DEVTECH.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
VIOLET: What's at the ship
at DEVTECH?
Lucius? Bob.
Helen's in trouble.
I need someone
to watch the kids.
Suit up. It might get weird.
I'll be there.
ASAP. Fifteen tops.
HONEY: Where are you
going ASAP?
You better be back ASAP!
And leaving that suit.
I gotta go.
I'll be home soon.
Lucius will be here sooner.
No firing the baby
around the house, okay?
What's at the ship
at DEVTECH?
And why are you
in your Supersuit?
(TYRES SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
Is that Mom's supersuit?
She may need it.
You never know.
What's going on?
I don't know,
but Dad called Lucius
after getting a call
about Mom...
and then left.
I thought you renounced
superheroes.
Yeah, well,
I renounce my renunciation.
Put that on.
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
Hello there, little fella.
Hello.
You kids aren't safe.
The Deavors sent us
to take you...
FROZONE:
Well, isn't that redundant?
The Deavors just sent me here
to guard the house.
'Cause the kids aren't safe.
I get it,
managerial screw-up.
Tell Winston
I handled it.
You understand,
Ms...
Voyd.
Ms. Voyd.
Drive safely.
(BEEPS)
(BOTH GASPS)
The thing is, he wants us
to bring you, too.
Hey.
(ALL GRUNTS)
That isn't gonna
hold them long.
Dash, grab the baby!
(ALL STRAINING)
(VIOLET SCREAMS)
Spread out!
- Whoa!
- FROZONE: Oh!
(GRUNTS)
Dash!
We gotta get to my car.
(ROARS)
What? What's going on?
Little fella!
(SCREECHING)
(STRAINING)
- (GROWLS)
- (GASPS)
(GROANING)
(VIOLET SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
It worked!
(FROZONE GRUNTING)
Incredibile, windows down!
Dive in!
- (CHUCKLES)
- (GRUNTS)
Incredibile,
set voice identification.
Loudly, say your names.
- Violet Parr.
- Dashiell Robert Parr.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Lucius!
- (YELLS)
- Incredibile, escape!
Fill me in!
Good news and bad news.
We found her.
She seems physically fine
but she's had an encounter
with Screenslaver...
and she's acting
kind of strange. In here.
Strange how?
(GROANING)
Helen? (GROANS)
Helen, what are you...
(CHOKING)
Helen, it's me.
(GASPS)
(GROANING)
(EXHALES)
Incredibile, pull over.
(SIGHS)
We can't go to E's.
You saw those goggles
they put on Lucius.
They were
wearing them, too.
They're all under
someone's control.
They've probably done
the same to Mom.
Okay. Bad guys after us.
No Mom, no Dad.
No Lucius.
But we have our powers,
this car...
and... what?
- (JACK-JACK COOING)
- (RUMBLING)
(BOTH GASPING)
Incredibile,
take us to DEVTECH.
The kids have escaped
in a tricked-out car,
but we got Frozone.
Bring him to the ship
at DEVTECH immediately.
Aw, we missed 'em!
Oh, I wish the Incredibile
could follow that boat.
- What did you do?
- I don't know.
- I didn't do anything!
(DASH SCREAMING)
Wow, this car does
anything I say.
We didn't plan this well.
What do you mean?
We're here, aren't we?
Yes, we're here.
We need to be up there.
Hey...
What if the Incredibile
has ejector seats?
VIOLET: Wait, what? No.
- Yeah, baby!
- No, don't say any more...
Max power! Launch!
(BOTH SCREAMS)
(JACK-JACK LAUGHING)
Come on.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hello!
Glad you could come.
Welcome to the conference.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Our stars, where are they?
The event's about to start.
They didn't want to upstage
the others.
They'll join for the signing.
Welcome, guests!
You're in for a treat.
This ship is the largest
hydrofoil on the planet.
So, hold onto something...
because we're going
to open her up!
(ALL GASPING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
We need to find Mom and Dad.
Stay here.
I'm gonna search for them.
Wait! Who's gonna
watch Jack-Jack?
Suck it up.
I won't be long.
Wait. Wait, but, but wait!
This is important.
They are in trouble.
It's up to us.
To us, understand?
Keep him amused but quiet!
Ugh.
- (CRYING)
- Shh! Quiet!
Huh?
(LAUGHING)
Jack-Jack?
(VIOLET GRUNTS)
Jack-Jack!
(GASPS)
(YELPS)
(VIOLET GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
Jack-Jack!
The mesmerized supers
know we're here...
but I found Mom and Dad...
Where's Jack-Jack?
You lost him?
I gave you one thing to do!
The tracker.
Use the tracker.
(BEEPING)
He's going up?
- He's in an elevator.
- Let's go!
Hey, little baby.
Where are your parents?
(GROWLING)
And here they are, folks!
The supers who started
this whole thing.
EVELYN: I told you
they'd be there in time.
Hey, did you make them
new masks?
Yeah. Night vision,
et cetera...
They look good, right?
WOMAN: (ON TV)
So simple, even he can do it.
And we're back live in
three, two, one...
This is
a momentous occasion.
We've all managed
to accomplish
something extraordinarily rare
in today's world.
We agree on something.
(ALL LAUGHING)
We agree to undo
a bad decision.
To make sure
a few extraordinarily
gifted members...
of the world's many countries
are treated fairly.
To invite them once again
to use their gifts...
to benefit the world.
I thank all of you
for representing your nation's
commitment to superheroes.
With special thanks
to Ambassador Selick.
Yeah, it's okay.
Let her hear you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
WINSTON:
Thank you, Ambassador,
for your early
and very crucial support.
I can't think of anyone
more deserving than you...
to be the first signature
on the International
Superhero Accord.
- There it is!
- (ALL CHEERING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(MUZAK PLAYING)
(JACK-JACK WHINING)
(GASPS) Holy cow!
I know he's on fire.
Just put him out.
(GIGGLING)
(GASPS) They're coming.
Is it okay
to give him that?
I wasn't hearing
any better ideas.
(GIGGLING)
(WHINING)
No!
- (CRYING)
- Come on, Jack-Jack.
We have to go.
Cookie num-num?
(GRUNTS)
(JACK-JACK BABBLING)
- Mama, Mama.
- I see him. He's getting away!
Stand back.
- Darn it!
- He's heading for Mom.
It is done.
The world is super again.
(ALL CHEERING)
Group photo. Come on.
Group photo, everyone.
Squeeze in. That's it.
Historic occasion.
Everyone, smile.
Go on phase two.
Years of mandated
hiding and silence
have made us bitter.
You bring us out
into the light...
only to clean up the messes
your lack
of discipline creates.
Your bodies
and your character are weak.
Your promises are empty,
and you will pay for it.
We no longer serve you.
We serve only us.
May the fittest survive.
Well, we, um...
Some very alarming
moments there...
before the, uh,
technical difficulties.
Please bear with us.
(SCREAMS)
What?
Mayday! Mayday!
Mayday!
Hold! Let him talk.
Superheroes have forcibly
taken the bridge. Repeat.
Now.
- (SCREAMS)
- (GROANS)
A little further.
Little further. Stop.
(JACK-JACK COOING)
What the... A baby?
Mom and Dad.
Uncle Lucius?
- My mama.
- Jack-Jack, no!
(BABBLING)
A super baby?
(GROWLS)
No, no, no!
Put him down!
(GASPS)
- Grab her!
- No!
Hold Jack-Jack.
(ALL GRUNTING)
No!
- (GASPS)
- ELASTIGIRL: Hey, it's me!
Yeah, that's what
I thought last time.
- (JACK-JACK CALLING OUT)
- Kids, what are you...
You came for us?
Don't be mad.
Oh, sweetie,
how could I be mad?
I'm proud.
Not to break up
a tender moment,
but where are we?
Is this DEVTECH's ship?
Evelyn Deavor
controls the Screenslaver...
and until a second ago, us.
- (RUMBLES)
- Where's the crew?
AUTOMATED VOICE: Collision detected.
Correct course.
Uh-oh.
Did I do that?
Mom, the suit?
Try this.
Phase Three.
Go on Phase Three!
Why are the kids here?
You didn't go to the house?
I went to the house.
You didn't escape?
How did you not escape?
BOTH: Hey!
We just saved you!
Escape? Escape from who?
- (GROWLS)
- (GRUNTS)
Those guys!
(YELLING)
What the...?
Jack-Jack has powers?
We know.
Fight now, talk later.
(ALL GRUNTING)
- (GROWLING)
- (GROANING)
- (VIOLET GASPS)
- (SCREECHES)
- (YELPS)
- (GROWLING)
- Jack-Jack.
Laser eyes!
(VIOLET IMITATES LASER FIRING)
- (SCREECHES)
- (YELPS)
Ah-ha!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Ugh.
Come with me, Winston.
- Did I faint?
- You'll be safe here.
Safe? Safe from what?
Where are the diplomats?
The supers?
Still hypnotized.
(SIGHS)
What have you done?
Evelyn, she's escaping.
Well, go after her.
Finish your mission.
I can't just go!
What about the kids?
- Jack-Jack, who's gonna...
- VIOLET: Mom!
Go. We've got this.
Voyd, come with me.
I'll go shut down
the engine.
I'll try to slow the
ship from the bow.
Wait, someone's missing.
Where's the crusher guy?
Strap in now!
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
It's for your own good.
No!
This is.
(GRUNTS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANING)
- We're too late.
- Get me up to the jet.
(YELPS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(EXHALES IN RELIEF)
(GRUNTS)
Hey, you did this.
Can you undo it?
You want me to un-crush?
What? No one's ever
asked for that?
No. To un-crush is silly.
Why un-crush?
To get into the engine room.
Oh, forget it.
We don't have enough time.
What if I said
to un-punch someone?
What do you do?
Welcome aboard, Elastigirl.
Although
we haven't yet reached
our cruising altitude...
feel free to roam about
the cabin.
- (GROANING)
- Or just relax...
and let the cabin roam
about you.
I can't get
to the engine room!
We gotta do something!
Because trying to
slow it down ain't working.
Hey! What about
turning the boat?
BOTH:
The steering's been destroyed!
- Dash means from the outside!
- Yeah!
If we break off
one of the foils
and turn the rudder...
we can veer the ship
away from the city!
That might work.
I'll turn the front,
you turn the rear.
Using the rudder?
That's underwater.
How am I supposed to get...
All right.
Come on, kids.
Dad, I know
this is going to work.
But if it doesn't,
and we crash...
my shields are probably better
protection than the ship.
I should stay here.
With Jack-Jack.
That's my girl.
Remember, Bob,
we're both turning right!
EVELYN:
You know what's sad?
If it weren't
for your core beliefs...
I think we could have
been good friends.
At least... (GASPING)
I have core beliefs.
We have breaking news...
While there is
still no radio contact,
the ship
has changed direction...
and is heading towards land
at a high rate of speed.
So, Dash...
I am going to the rudder.
Once I turn the ship,
you hit the pull up button.
- Okay, Dad.
- Now lower me down...
(SCREAMS)
The reputations of
superheroes are ruined.
You will never
become legal. Ever.
Never?
(LAUGHS) No.
- Ever?
- No.
Not even a little
smidgee-widgee?
Oh, hypoxia.
When you don't have
enough oxygen,
- things seem really silly.
- (GASPING)
- Things get sillier
and sillier
and then you die.
(LAUGHING)
I don't wanna die.
Ah, nobody does. (GRUNTS)
Really.
(CHUCKLES)
Not such a bad way to go.
(SCREAMING)
(INHALING RAPIDLY)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GASPS)
Everyone, we need to get
to the back of the ship.
All supers,
protect your ambassadors!
Follow.
Dad's been underwater
for too long.
(ALARM BLARING)
We gotta pull him up.
Wait. It's too soon.
(GRUNTS)
I'm gonna press the button!
Not yet!
(METAL CREAKING)
(STRAINING)
It's turning. It's working.
- Now!
- Dash, now!
Save yourself. Make a chute.
- (MR. INCREDIBLE GRUNTS)
- Make a chute. Make a chute.
Make a chute!
- (ELASTIGIRL YELLS)
- (VOYD YELPS)
LUCIUS:
Helen! Brace yourselves!
Crash positions!
(GRUNTING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(ALL SIGHING)
Whoo.
(GASPS)
I missed Jack-Jack's first power?
Actually, you missed
the first 17.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
- ELASTIGIRL: Oh!
(JACK-JACK BABBLING)
(PEOPLE APPLAUDING)
(JACK-JACK GIGGLES)
The fact that you saved me
doesn't make you right.
But it does make you alive.
And I'm grateful
for that.
I'm sorry,
but she'll go to prison.
Well, I'm sorry she's rich
and will probably get no more
than a slap on the wrist.
First of all, Violet,
I like you.
And who knows what the
future may bring...
but I have a good feeling
about all of you.
Hmm. Good feeling.
- Should we be worried?
- (MR. INCREDIBLE CHUCKLES)
You guys got the next shift.
I'm beat. Oh!
I saw what you did back there.
That was incredible!
No pun intended.
VIOLET:
Sorry I had to punch you.
(TYRES SCREECHES)
Yeah, baby! My sweet ride!
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(CHUCKLES)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (ALL CHEERING)
And in recognition
of the extraordinary service
they have demonstrated...
the legal status
of superheroes
is hereby restored.
(ALL CHEERING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING
IN DISTANCE)
You don't know me,
do you?
No, I don't...
Wait.
Are you the girl
with the water?
I'm Violet Parr.
- I'm Tony.
- (CHUCKLING) Okay.
You split up into separate
groups and stuff...
Tony, this is my mom.
Pleased to meet you.
- This is my dad.
- BOB: Oh, we've met.
And this is embarrassing.
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
Charmed, I'm sure.
- My little brother, Dash.
- (TOY SQUEAKS)
VIOLET:
And the baby is Jack-Jack.
I tried to limit it
to one parent.
We're all going to a movie,
too, Tony. Don't mind us.
BOB: We'll be sitting
on the other side
of the theater.
Not watching you.
(LAUGHING) He's kidding.
They are only dropping
us off at the theater.
They have
other things to do.
So, you guys are close,
I guess.
- Yeah, I guess.
- We can get closer.
(LAUGHING) Bob.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Stop! Let us out!
Here, large popcorn,
small soda.
Save me a seat, center,
about eight rows back.
I'll be back before
the previews are over.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Here comes Elastigirl ♪
♪ Stretching her arms
Elastigirl ♪
♪ No one's beyond her reach ♪
♪ Elastigirl ♪
♪ Ah, Elastigirl ♪
♪ Here comes Elastigirl ♪
♪ Stretching her arms
Elastigirl ♪
♪ No one's beyond her reach ♪
♪ Ah, Elastigirl ♪
♪ Who's the cat
who's always chill ♪
♪ When survival odds
are close to nil? ♪
♪ Frozone ♪
♪ Always chill
Always chill ♪
♪ Frozone ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ So chill, So chill ♪
♪ Talk about Frozone ♪
♪ Frozone ♪
♪ Mr. Incredible ♪
♪ Incredible ♪
♪ Catching the bad guys
Pow, pow, pow ♪
♪ Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow ♪
♪ Mr. Incredible ♪
♪ Incredible ♪
♪ Punching the bad guys ♪
♪ Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow ♪