BRANDT: (ON PHONE) Benji?
Benji, do you copy?
Benji?
(BENJI GRUNTS)
- BENJI: Shit.
- BRANDT: Where is Ethan?
Uh, I can't talk right now.
BRANDT: The package is on the plane.
BENJI: Yeah, I know.
We're currently
formulating a plan B.
Although, technically,
it's a plan C.
This isn't going very well.
I am aware of that,
Brandt. You're not helping.
Where's Ethan?
I don't know. We're on radio silence.
That plane cannot take
off with the package on it.
- Do you understand?
- LUTHER: We're working on it.
Luther? What the hell are you doing there?
You're supposed to be on
assignment in Malaysia!
I am in Malaysia. I've been here two days.
- Benji needed my help.
- I didn't need help.
I needed assistance.
It's a different thing.
The package is still on the plane.
BENJI: We understand the
package is on the plane.
We're trying to cripple it remotely.
You can do that?
We can if the pilot left the
satellite uplink switched on.
Which he has.
And how do you access the uplink?
It involves hacking a Russian satellite.
I can't authorize that.
Which is why I didn't ask permission.
We're under investigation for misconduct.
The package is on board.
What do you want me to do?
(AIRPLANE ENGINE STARTING)
Uh, Luther.
BRANDT: I'm reading a heat bloom, Benji.
The engines are starting.
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
But I can't do anything until
I'm connected to the satellite.
Benji, you're connected.
Okay, great.
The package is still on that plane.
LUTHER: Shut down the fuel pump.
BENJI: Uh, the mechanicals are locked down.
What about the electrical system?
Oh, that might work.
Uh, no.
- Hydraulics!
- BENJI: Okay, stand by.
No, they're encrypted.
Benji, the plane!
Yes! The package is on
the plane! We get it!
Can you open the door?
Ethan? Where are you?
ETHAN: I'm by the plane.
Benji, can you open the door?
Uh, can I open the door? Uh, maybe.
Open the door when I tell you!
(GRUNTS)
I'm on the plane. Open the door.
BENJI: How did you get in the plane?
ETHAN: Not in the
plane. I'm on the plane!
Open the door!
Benji! Open the door!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, okay!
(ACCELERATING)
- Benji, open that door right now!
- Yeah, I'm trying!
- Come on, Benji!
- Benji, open that door!
BENJI: Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Yes, got it!
(DOOR OPENING)
That's the wrong door!
Benji, not that door. The other door.
The other door, right! Yes, the other door.
Okay, yes! Sorry, my bad, my bad!
(BEEPING)
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
All right, look, I'm gonna
open the para door! How's that?
(GRUNTS)
(ETHAN PANTING)
Hey! Hey!
Sync by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
We're about to close.
ETHAN: I won't be long.
Are you looking for anything in particular?
Something rare.
Let me guess.
Classical.
- Jazz.
- Sax?
- Coltrane.
- Piano?
Monk.
Shadow Wilson on bass.
Shadow Wilson played drums.
Know why they call him Shadow?
Because he had a light touch.
You're in luck.
I have a first pressing.
It really is you.
I've heard stories.
They can't all be true.
MAN: Good evening, Mr. Hunt.
The weapons you recovered in Belarus
were confirmed to be VX nerve gas
capable of devastating a major city.
The bodies of the
air crew were found
less than 24 hours after
they landed in Damascus.
They were identified as
low-level Chechen separatists
with neither the
access nor the ability
to acquire the weapons
they were transporting.
This would support your suspicion
that a shadow organization is
committed to inciting revolution
by enabling acts of terror in nations
friendly to Western interests.
IMF suspects this to be the
same shadow organization
you have been tracking
for the last year,
also known as the Syndicate.
IMF would be right.
Normally, you and your
team would be tasked
with infiltrating and disrupting
this terrorist network.
But we have taken steps to
ensure that this will not happen.
Because we are the
Syndicate, Mr. Hunt.
And now we know who you are.
Your mission, should
you choose to accept it,
is to face your fate.
Pursue us, you will be caught.
Resist us, you will be killed.
And your precious Secretary
will disavow any
knowledge of your actions.
Good luck, Mr. Hunt.
This message will
self-destruct in five seconds.
(STEAM HISSING)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(GRUNTING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (BULLET CLINKING)
HUNLEY: Mr. Chairman, the
IMF's misadventures date back
to my earliest days at the CIA
when the IMF broke into the CIA
to steal a list of covert operatives.
And now, more recently, a Russian warhead?
Disarmed Russian warhead.
A Russian nuclear warhead...
Rendered safe by the IMF.
HUNLEY: ...clipped the Transamerica Pyramid
before plunging into the San Francisco Bay.
Saving the western hemisphere.
This made possible by IMF agents
who did willingly provide the
launch codes to a known terrorist.
Do I have that right, Agent Brandt?
I can neither confirm nor deny details
of any such operation without
the Secretary's approval.
This was the same week that
the IMF infiltrated the Kremlin.
Here is the Kremlin before
and the Kremlin after.
I can neither confirm nor deny
details of any operation...
Without the Secretary's
approval, yes, we know.
In fact, until this panel
appoints a new Secretary,
you really can't say much of
anything, can you, Agent Brandt?
Well, I didn't write the rules, Mr. Hunley.
HUNLEY: Mr. Chairman, the
so-called Impossible Mission Force
is not just a rogue organization.
It is an outdated one, a throwback
to an era without transparency
- and without oversight.
- Mr. Chairman?
- Time has come to dissolve the IMF...
- BRANDT: Mr. Chairman?
...and transfer their
salvageable assets to the CIA.
Mr. Chairman, the IMF has operated
without oversight for 40 years.
- Mr. Chairman?
- Are its methods unorthodox? Yes.
Are its results less
than perfect? Absolutely.
But without the IMF...
There will be order and stability!
Without the IMF...
This panel recognizes the IMF's
contribution to global security.
But the events laid out
by CIA Director Hunley
also show a pattern of wanton brinksmanship
and a total disregard for protocol.
From where I sit, your unorthodox methods
are indistinguishable from chance.
And your results, perfect or
not, look suspiciously like luck.
I'm afraid today is the day
when the IMF's luck runs out.
(GAVEL BANGS)
(COUGHING)
(STRAINING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
Hmm?
What does he see in you, I wonder?
Who is "he"?
(GRUNTS)
(WHEEZES AND COUGHS)
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
ETHAN: Well, why don't you take
off the cuffs and I'll show you,
Vinter?
You know who I am.
Janik Vinter.
They call you the Bone Doctor.
The funny thing is,
you were officially declared
dead three years ago.
Nice shoes, by the way.
Not his.
Yours.
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
This one's a fighter.
He'll die before you turn him.
Are you worried he's
going to take your place?
(MUFFLED THUDDING AND GRUNTING)
You should go before it gets ugly.
Yeah, he's right. You should go.
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
Janik.
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(BOTH PANTING)
We've never met before, right?
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Follow me.
(BANGING CONTINUES)
Give me the gun!
What are you doing?
I can't leave.
You can't stay. We just killed those men.
We didn't kill them, you
did. (BREATHING SHAKILY)
I tried to stop you. You got away.
Who are you?
You better hurry now. Good luck.
No, wait! Wait!
(MAN SPEAKING SWEDISH)
(WOMAN SPEAKING SWEDISH)
(BEEPING)
Satcom seven.
ETHAN: Western Europe unsecured.
Designator?
Bravo-Echo-1-1.
Connecting.
- This is Brandt.
- ETHAN: Go secure.
Go.
London terminal is compromised.
Repeat, London is compromised.
Agent in place is down.
Request immediate extraction.
What happened? Who breached London?
Do you have anything to go on?
A face.
He wanted something. Not
information. He could've killed me.
But he didn't.
Okay. What do you think it means?
The Syndicate is real.
They know who we are, how we operate.
I think I know why they've
been so hard to find.
Just focus operations on gathering
any available intel regarding
former covert operatives.
It doesn't matter what country
or agency,
just as long as they're dead
or presumed dead.
Start with Janik Vinter.
He's also known as the Bone Doctor.
I can't do that.
What? What are you talking about?
The Committee has shut us down.
Operations have been
handed over to the CIA.
There is no more IMF. I've been
ordered to bring everyone in.
- Ethan...
- I understand.
- I understand, Brandt.
We didn't have this conversation.
I've disappeared in London.
You don't know where I am.
If I'm dead or alive.
This man you saw, can you find him?
I won't stop until I do.
This may very well be
our last mission, Ethan.
Make it count.
- Brandt?
- (LINE DISCONNECTS)
HUNLEY: Since we're going
to be working together,
I want you to choose your
next words very carefully.
Where is Hunt?
- I don't know.
- Don't lie to me, Brandt.
I have no way of contacting
him. He's deep cover.
Last I heard, he's tracking the Syndicate.
Let's cut the bull. You know who we are,
you know what we're capable of.
How come the CIA has never discovered
any actionable intel
regarding this, uh, Syndicate?
What are you implying?
Not implying. Stating.
Leveling an accusation, actually.
Hunt is both arsonist and
fireman at the same time.
I believe that the Syndicate
is a figment of his imagination,
created to justify the IMF's existence.
I am going to find him,
Brandt, and when I do,
he will be called upon to answer for
every wanton act of mayhem
he is responsible for.
Welcome to the CIA.
You'll never find him.
Set your watch, Brandt.
Ethan Hunt is living his
last day as a free man.
(PANTING)
All right, everybody, heads up! This is it.
MAN: (ON SPEAKERPHONE) Alpha
team prepped, standing by.
Execute.
Langley, Brimstone. Go.
I say again, we are go.
(PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HEAVY BREATHING ON PHONE)
MAN: Langley, there's nobody here.
(PRESSES BUTTON)
Langley, Brimstone. Face the north wall.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(CHUCKLING)
(PHONE RINGS)
Dunn.
Is it that time already? Okay.
WOMAN: I will ask you
a series of control questions.
BENJI: I know, and I'm
gonna answer truthfully,
and then you're gonna ask
me to lie intentionally.
State your name.
The King of Norway.
See, that's a lie.
I'm actually third in line to the
throne. My brother was... (CLEARS THROAT)
Has Ethan Hunt contacted you?
Why would he contact me?
HUNLEY: Hunt has resurfaced.
This time in Cuba.
He, uh, left these behind.
Tell me what you make of them.
I don't know. He's taken
up scrapbooking? (CHUCKLES)
Look at the photographs, Dunn.
All of them are either
missing or dead. Every one.
All of them were government agents.
Russian, French, British,
Israeli, you name it.
These are highly classified files and yet
Hunt had no trouble collecting them.
And he always seems to
be a step ahead of us.
I wonder how.
Are you suggesting I'm helping him?
Oh, the thought had crossed my mind.
BENJI: Six months I have been here,
sifting through mountains of metadata
and exabytes of encoded excrement.
I have decrypted, processed,
parsed more data than anyone in my section.
And yet, every week you haul me in here
and you ask me the same
question, just in a different way.
And today you haven't answered it.
You seem to think I have some
kind of obligation to him.
Okay. Nothing could be
further from the truth.
Ethan Hunt is still out there in the field,
and I am stuck here answering for it.
We are not friends.
I owe him nothing.
That'll be all, Dunn.
(SIGHS)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
ETHAN: (THROUGH EARPIECE) Welcome
to Vienna, Benji. Miss me?
Ethan, where are you? Where
the hell have you been?
You know what? Please, don't tell me that.
Because it's just another
thing I'll have to lie about
in my weekly polygraph.
Everything's gonna be
fine. Just keep walking.
But make sure you're
not being followed.
I didn't win those opera tickets, did I?
No, I'm afraid not.
- So, where do we meet?
- We don't.
- For your sake, we shouldn't be seen together.
- (CELL PHONE CHIMES)
You have mail.
- BENJI: Who is he?
- ETHAN: That's what we're here to find out.
What I do know is he's our only
possible link to the Syndicate.
And I have reason to believe
he's going to be here tonight.
But I can't find him
alone. Are you in?
- Uh...
- Are you in?
Yes, of course. Of course. Um...
So what's the play?
Simple. You find him. We tag him.
I follow him wherever he goes.
And after that?
After that, you're on a plane.
Back at work Monday morning.
No one is the wiser.
Wait, that's it?
You're in enough danger as it is.
I didn't want to involve you
this much, but I had no choice.
Well, if you're going
to bring me all this way,
you could at least give me something
a bit more, you know, dramatic.
Benji, we're trying
to keep a low profile.
You want drama, go to the opera.
- (PEOPLE CHATTERING)
- (CAMERAS FLASHING)
(INDISTINCT)
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
ETHAN: Yes, I am.
BENJI: Am I correct in assuming
that is the Chancellor of Austria?
ETHAN: Yes, you are.
BENJI: Did you know he
was going to be here?
No.
Right. Well, we have a
European head of state here
at the same time as we are
looking for a nefarious terrorist.
And I'm sure that the two things
- are completely unrelated.
- Benji.
Meanwhile, I will try and
overlook the fact that
- you're an international fugitive wanted by the CIA!
- Benji.
And that this little
unsanctioned operation
- is tantamount to treason.
- Benji.
Because, as you stated earlier,
I will be back at my
desk on Monday morning,
playing videogames, and no
one will be any the wiser.
- The show's about to start, Benji.
- Right.
Just take your position.
- Tell me what you see.
- Okay.
Nice tux, by the way.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
(REPEATING IN GERMAN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
(BEEPING)
(STATIC)
Join the IMF! See the world!
On a monitor. In a closet.
(ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (APPLAUSE)
- (MUSIC ENDS)
(MUSIC STARTS)
(SINGING OPERA)
Okay, I have eyes.
Searching.
(OPERA CONTINUING)
Talk to me, Benji.
Nothing yet. Stand by.
I know you're here. Where are you?
Uh, Ethan, I might have
something for you. Can't confirm.
- Where?
- Backstage. I'll direct you.
Take the door on your left.
He should be right in front of you.
Benji, do you see that?
See what?
That woman.
What woman? Where are you?
I can't see you.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
- (FEEDBACK)
- Oh! Ah!
Ethan, do you copy? Ethan, come in!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOTH STRAINING)
- (MUSIC ENDS)
- (APPLAUSE)
(MUSIC STARTS)
(SINGING OPERA)
(STATIC CRACKLES)
(CHOKING)
(YELLS)
Ethan, the lighting booth!
Ethan, do you copy?
(APPLAUSE)
(GRUNTING)
(OPERA CONTINUING)
(PANICKED TALKING)
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
(MAN SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
I have a way out. Interested?
Lead the way.
Anything you want to tell me?
Uh, no, not right now.
How's the pace?
Don't wait for me.
What's next?
(SIREN WAILING)
There.
Shoes.
Shoes, please.
(METALS CLANKING AND CREAKING)
Uh...
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SIGHS)
(METAL CLANKING)
(CONVERSING IN GERMAN)
(CRACKLING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Get in!
Go, go, go.
What the... She tried to shoot me!
That doesn't make her a bad person.
I'm going to have to search you.
You have to let me go.
Oh. Not a chance!
I assumed you were deep
cover back in London,
but isn't this taking
the role a little far?
Hang on a minute. Do you know her?
We haven't been formally introduced,
but I'm pretty sure she's
British intelligence?
Ilsa Faust. You're Ethan Hunt.
And that shade is very hard to find.
What were you doing at the opera tonight?
Aside from killing the Chancellor.
Saving your life in London
put me in a tight spot
with some very dangerous people.
I was sent to kill the
Chancellor to regain their trust.
Ah, so you admit that you killed him!
I went through the motions.
That's not the same thing.
You thought you'd put him in the hospital,
take him out of harm's way.
Same thing you tried to do.
BENJI: You're not going
to believe that, are you?
What about the rest of her team?
You mean those other two idiots.
I can only assume they were redundancies.
In case you didn't follow through.
One man to kill the Chancellor,
the other one to kill you.
A test.
Second one I've failed, thanks to you.
And the car bomb was insurance.
Uh, we have a tail.
ETHAN: Who is he?
We're after the same
thing, and I can help you.
If you want to bring down the
Syndicate, you have to let me out.
Uh, they're closing!
This has to look like an escape,
so you just throw me out anywhere.
Tell me who he is.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- Whoa!
Change of plan! Throw her out!
You have everything you need to find me.
HUNLEY: Less than 24 hours after we
interviewed Benji Dunn about Ethan Hunt,
he was on a plane to Vienna
with tickets to the opera.
And within six hours of his
arrival, the Chancellor was dead.
Now, that might be circumstance
to some public defender,
but to the CIA, that is
actionable intelligence.
Consider for the moment
the possibility that
Ethan's investigation led him to the opera,
and that he's the one with
the actionable intelligence!
In any case, finding Hunt
is no longer a pet project.
The Special Activities Division
will now have full discretion.
You mean shoot to kill.
Whether Hunt lives or
dies is entirely up to him.
New identity.
Passport, cash, move map.
There's a change of clothes
in that bag right there.
Everything you need to
make it to D.C. undetected.
Once you're there, you
have to inform on me.
I'm sorry, what?
Just tell the truth.
You came to Vienna believing
you won two tickets to the opera.
I attempted to recruit you into
assassinating the Chancellor.
- You refused.
- That's not the truth!
Your life depends on
them believing you, Benji.
It'll go easier if you tell
them what they want to hear.
Ethan, at least tell me
what this is all about.
You recognize anyone?
Him.
He's former KSA. German intelligence.
Missing, presumed dead.
He was at the opera tonight.
This one, too.
Former Mossad.
Let me guess. Presumed dead.
Tonight, I made it official.
I was looking for him in the Bosphorus.
The same day, a car accident killed
the visiting President of Malawi.
He slipped away again in Jakarta,
hours before a passenger
plane vanished over the Pacific
with 236 passengers.
I just missed him in the Philippines
right before a fire at
a petrochemical plant
gassed a village of 2,000 people.
You're saying these accidents
are somehow connected.
That missing plane was carrying
the Secretary of the World Bank.
That fire bankrupted a
global arms corporation.
That wreck triggered a civil war.
These are no accidents.
They're links in a chain.
The work of a single
organization, the Syndicate.
A rogue nation, trained to do what we do,
imbued with a new sense of purpose.
Destroy the system that created them
regardless of who's in their way.
An anti-IMF.
Since Hunley shut us down,
they've been escalating unchecked.
Killing the Chancellor
tonight was a statement,
the start of a new phase.
Or they could just be a
series of random disasters.
He was there.
Every time.
Just like he was there
tonight, I'm sure of it.
I don't know who he is, where he's from,
how he's funded.
But I know he's the key.
Ethan, this is what I signed up
for. Let me help you find him.
That's why I brought you
here in the first place,
and look what happened!
I can't protect you.
That's why I need you to leave.
That's not your decision to make, Ethan!
I am a field agent. I know the risks.
More than that, I am your friend,
no matter what I tell
the polygraph every week.
Now, you called me
because you needed my help.
And you still do. So I am staying.
And that is all we are
going to say about that.
Okay.
Good.
Where do we start?
Ilsa.
Right. And how do we find her?
She said we have everything we need.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(MAN GROANS)
We had an agreement.
You send me to do a job, I
do it. But my way, not yours.
Where did I deviate?
You put two more gunmen
at the opera tonight.
One of them tried to kill me.
You missed.
I missed because Ethan Hunt
was there looking for you.
Ethan Hunt's in Vienna because you
allowed him to escape in London.
Vinter would have killed him in London,
and that's not what you asked for.
Twice now you've let him slip away.
Curious.
Are you questioning my
loyalty or my ability?
Can't decide.
I've told you before, trust me or kill me.
But if you're going to kill me, be a man.
Do it yourself.
(BULLET CLANKING)
Did he say anything?
He knows about Morocco.
What does he know about Morocco?
He knows about the power plant.
He doesn't know what's in it.
Find him, please.
He'll find me.
I've seen to that.
That's interesting.
- What is it?
- It's a skiff.
A secure computer facility.
Offline, ultra-contained.
It's impossible to hack
into from the outside.
It's essentially a
digital safety deposit box.
Very strange thing for a young lady
to be carrying in her sundries.
Where's it located?
Uh...
Morocco.
(BLEATING)
(COUGHS AND PANTS)
And what brings you
gentlemen to Casablanca?
Good to see you.
What couldn't you tell me over the phone?
The Chancellor of Austria was assassinated.
We believe that Ethan and Benji were there.
Hunley has handed this over to
the Special Activities Division.
We need to find Ethan before they do.
And that's where you come in.
Not interested.
Okay, look, Luther...
Look, man, I know Ethan.
I don't know you.
All I know about you is that
you chose to work for Hunley.
Yeah. All I know about
you is you chose to resign.
(CHUCKLES) You don't have to worry
about Ethan. They'll never catch him.
No, they're not gonna catch him. No.
This is the CIA. This is
Hunley we're talking about.
Things are out of control.
No, they're going to kill him.
They're going to kill Ethan.
They're going to kill Benji.
We have to get to them first.
Are you going to help me?
You need to understand something.
Ethan is my friend.
And if I have one second of
doubt whose side you're on...
Mmm?
I believe you.
- All right.
What do I have to go on?
Not much. And not a lot of time.
ILSA: His name is Solomon Lane.
He created the Syndicate.
Where does he come from?
He's former British intelligence.
Well, if British intelligence
knows the Syndicate exists,
why don't they just tell the CIA?
Because they don't want anyone knowing
the Syndicate was created
by one of their own.
I was sent undercover to earn Lane's trust
and eventually identify the
members of his organization.
And for the first time in two years,
I'm close to knowing who they are.
Lane had a ledger.
It contained the identities of his
operatives, his terrorist associates,
the entire inner workings of the Syndicate.
One of his agents stole
it, hoping to blackmail him,
and kept it in a secure computer
facility for safekeeping.
He died being interrogated
for the access code,
leaving Lane with a serious problem.
So the key to crushing Lane
is sitting in a computer, just
waiting for someone to take it.
So, why hasn't Lane just
sent someone to steal it?
Oh, he has.
He sent me.
And I can tell you
it's impossible.
The facility's hidden beneath a local
power plant under military guard.
And the only way to download the ledger
is through the central computer
terminal, located there.
To reach the terminal, you'll
need to pass the main gate,
access the elevator with
fingerprint recognition,
and open three separate
combination locks.
BENJI: Well, that's easy. We
just impersonate the agent
who stole the ledger in the first
place, and I get to wear a mask!
ILSA: Unfortunately, even
if you could make it through
every other security measure,
you won't beat the last one.
That's because it's
protected by gait analysis.
The step beyond facial recognition.
These cameras actually
know how the agent walks,
how he talks, how he moves.
Right down to his facial tics.
(BUZZES)
(GRUNTING)
BENJI: So, what you're saying
is no mask can beat it.
We're busted before we
even get into the vault,
and I wind up in a Moroccan jail,
playing mummies and daddies
with Ahmad the Strangler.
Okay, I don't get to wear a mask.
And there's no other way
into the computer lab?
ILSA: No other way in.
- Air shaft?
- Six-inch-diameter pipe.
Foundation?
Twelve feet of concrete, top and bottom.
- Electrical conduit.
Bottom line is there's
no way into that terminal
unless your profile is
preinstalled in the security system.
(GROANS)
Profile.
Where are the profiles stored?
All security data is stored
offline in the liquid-cooled array.
Here, inside the torus.
Liquid-cooled. You mean
that thing is underwater?
- Yes.
Okay. So, to get the ledger,
one of us needs to enter the torus
and change the security profile,
so that the other one
can access the computer
without being caught.
That's the only way.
Can I get in through there? What's that?
That's the service hatch. It can
only be opened from the inside.
If you try and open it from the outside,
you'd be hit with 70,000
gallons of pressurized water.
Where does the water come from?
Desalinized seawater
flows through the intake,
in the power plant.
And, before you ask,
the system is designed
to shut down automatically
if any metal enters the intake.
No oxygen tanks.
All right. Well, how long
will it take to free swim
from the intake to the service hatch?
Two minutes, with the
current at full power.
Then you just have to hold
your breath for two minutes.
What about installing the security profile?
Well, that's gonna be,
like, a minute, tops.
So I have to hold my
breath for three minutes.
You can do that.
What I think you're overlooking
is the physical exertion.
The more you exert yourself,
the faster you consume oxygen.
Don't worry about him, all right?
All he has to do is
install the fake profile
before I get to the gait analysis.
You said it yourself, it's the only way.
(CHUCKLES) That doesn't sound impossible.
BRANDT: Satellite overwatch
covering all seven continents.
DNA profiling, facial recognition,
drone surveillance, drone strikes.
So, how are we supposed to find
Ethan and Benji before they do?
I'm not even looking for
them. I'm looking for her.
What do you mean?
These sketches. What do you see?
BRANDT: Ethan's not exactly
sure who this guy is.
But this woman...
He knows her.
He trusts her.
I'm betting that if he's not
already with her, he's on his way.
Find her, find Ethan.
Tell me it's possible to pull
facial recognition off a sketch.
For mere mortals, no.
For me, I could've done this at home.
(CHUCKLES) All right.
- How long is this gonna take?
- LUTHER: Found her.
CCTV picked her up at
the airport in Casablanca.
BRANDT: What the hell?
She's bad news.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
(CONVERSING IN ARABIC)
Sorry.
(WHIRRING)
- (BEEPS)
- (CRACKLING)
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
ETHAN: (THROUGH EARPIECE)
Benji, we're in.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON WALKIE-TALKIE)
(RAPID BEEPS)
(RUMBLING)
One more time. You'll have three minutes.
Two and a half minutes to
switch the security profile.
Thirty seconds to escape
through the service hatch.
Remember, conserve oxygen.
Don't move a muscle if you don't have to.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm in the elevator.
ILSA: That current will
carry you to the torus.
Once you're there, I'll shut it down.
Important note. The profile is in slot 108.
And a slightly more important note.
If you haven't switched that profile
before I reach the gait analysis, I'm dead.
Thank you, Benji.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(ALARM BEEPING)
What's the problem?
The cooling system's rebooting by itself.
(MACHINE POWERING DOWN)
All systems normal.
Cooling system's at full power.
(BEEPING)
No, no, no.
(ALARM BLARING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(RAPID BREATHING)
(GRUNTING)
(WHIRRING)
(COUGHING)
You're all right.
Oh, you're okay.
BENJI: You see? What did I tell you?
Difficult? Absolutely. But certainly not...
Jesus. Is he all right? What happened?
(PANTING)
Okay.
Here.
Hey.
I misjudged you.
Hey, man. You okay? How you doing?
Hey, buddy.
Benji.
Yeah, Benji. You did good.
You take a moment, all
right? Just take a moment.
There's nothing a little
sunshine and fresh air won't fix.
You'll be right as rain.
What are you doing here?
Look, look.
We got it.
I knew we'd get it. (LAUGHING)
Listen, I don't want to
sound ungrateful, okay?
I appreciate everything you do for me,
but one of these days, you're
going to take it too far.
We got it!
- We're gonna nail that...
- (WHIRRING)
- (THUD)
- (GRUNTS)
Wait, wait...
BRANDT: I thought you
said you could find him.
LUTHER: I said I could locate him.
- You have to find him.
- Right.
Where's Hunt?
(FOOTSTEPS)
He's dead.
That really hurts!
- Can you walk?
- Yes.
We have to get to her before Lane does.
(ENGINES REVVING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(GRUNTS)
BENJI: Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Are you okay to drive? A
minute ago you were dead.
What are you talking about?
This is not going to end well.
- There she is!
- (TIRES SQUEALING)
Stairs, stairs, stairs!
Ah! God damn it!
(GRUNTING)
(ENGINES REVVING)
Whoa.
(GLASS BREAKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
We found him.
LUTHER: Oh, come on, man!
Shit!
It's a high-speed chase!
You just had to get the
four-by-four, didn't you?
Don't blame me. You chose the car.
You just had to have it!
Do you want me to drive?
BRANDT: Look at this thing!
LUTHER: Look how slow
you're going. Speed it up!
Who's this guy?
Shit!
Oh!
Ahhh!
Go! Go! Go!
I'm okay! I'm okay! I'm okay!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Here they come! What are we gonna do?
Uh...
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Gun!
Do you have your seatbelt on?
You're asking me that now?
- Hang on!
- (YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
- (BRAKE SCREECHES)
- (BODY THUDDING)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
We good?
Things got a little out of hand.
Ah! Look out!
We're good?
(BIKE APPROACHING)
Oh, hey, boys, what did I miss?
- Ooh, that looks sharp. Careful! Careful!
- (ENGINE STARTING)
(HORN BLARES)
(GUNSHOT)
(GRUNTING)
(COUGHS)
(GROANS)
So what do we do now?
Please tell me you made
a copy of that disk.
Of course I made a copy.
So where are we going?
(BELL TOLLING)
It's a ledger. The Syndicate's
entire infrastructure.
Who they are, the politicians they control,
and where the money comes from.
It's everything you want to know.
What makes you think this
so-called ledger is authentic?
Why would Lane want it so
badly if it wasn't authentic?
Why would he ever let
you have it if it was?
Did you never stop to consider
that he may want me to have it?
Misinformation, manipulation,
it's what he does, Ilsa.
It's what he's trained to do.
Lane lies to you, you
sell these lies to Hunt.
Together, you're both compromised.
That's his ultimate objective.
This may be authentic.
But there's only one person I trust
to verify that information. You.
No.
My orders were to deliver you
information regarding the Syndicate.
Your orders were to
infiltrate the Syndicate
that we may learn more
about them firsthand.
This isn't proof. It's a
test, like everything else.
The only way to pass is to go back.
I can't do that. I've betrayed
Lane's trust too many times.
And in every instance, you
did so on your own volition.
He was going to torture
and kill an American agent.
And you should have let him. Then
you would still have Lane's trust.
This is the trade. Hunt understands that.
I wasn't going to let
him die. He's our ally.
There are no allies in statecraft,
Ilsa, only common interests.
As it stands, Ethan Hunt
is a man without a country.
This makes killing him
decidedly less complicated.
Are you ordering me to kill Hunt?
Good God, no. Nothing so crude as that. No.
Lane will order you.
And to regain his trust,
you will do it.
You sent me to do a job. I did it.
Now you bring me in!
Might I remind you, you are
without a country of your own?
The Director of the CIA called me,
inquiring about you personally.
Of course, to protect
your cover, I had to lie.
So, as far as the Americans are concerned,
you're a rogue assassin,
a target of opportunity.
Precious few people know
about your true identity.
It would be unfortunate if we forgot.
You see, there really is no choice, Ilsa.
You're going back.
Glad to know you're still with us.
ETHAN: What's happening?
LUTHER: I can't open it.
What do you mean, you can't open it?
I mean I can't open it, ever.
That's a red box.
- A what?
- It's a red box.
The British government uses
them to transport state secrets.
Doesn't sound good.
BENJI: Meaning it's triple-encrypted.
You're not getting into that thing
unless you have fingerprints, retinal scan,
and a voice phrase spoken
by a specific individual.
The Prime Minister of
Great Britain himself.
Yes, him.
So what you're saying
is there is no ledger,
which means we have no proof
that the Syndicate even exists.
So we're back to square one, only
now we are all wanted by the CIA.
I'm so proud of us.
BENJI: What I don't understand
is why is there a red box
sat in a private data vault in Morocco?
And why would Lane want
it if he can't open it?
If Lane wants it, you can
bet he has a plan to open it.
And we just helped him steal it.
He's going to take the Prime Minister.
Yes, he is. The question is how.
Well, we have to warn
the British government.
Yeah, MI6.
No, Brandt. Put down the phone.
Let's think about this for a minute.
We have a responsibility to
warn the British government
and not gamble with the
Prime Minister's life, Ethan,
just so you can beat the guy
that has beaten you at every turn.
Is that what you think this is?
Brandt?
I think right now
you're incapable of seeing
that there is another way.
And sometimes Ethan is the only one
capable of seeing the only way.
And if he is wrong, then we
have Vienna all over again!
You don't know him.
If he wants something to happen,
there is no preventing it!
That's why we have to warn the British.
Maybe that's exactly
what he wants us to do.
Are you listening to yourself?
We are going to warn the British.
No. We're going to find
Lane, we're going to get him,
before he takes the Prime Minister.
Okay.
All right, Ethan. We're going to find Lane.
But please tell me how
are we going to do that?
(TABLET CHIMES)
All is forgiven.
That isn't a ledger, is it?
You didn't take a look for yourself?
Of course I did, but
the file was encrypted.
And why would I lie to you?
So that I would lie to Hunt.
But he wouldn't have stolen
it if he knew what it was.
And you wouldn't have helped him.
What is actually on that disk?
I'll be honest with you when
you start being honest with me.
Now, you and I both know why
you've come back. Don't we?
Hmm?
You're still alive because
I believe in your potential.
But I'm growing impatient.
Why do you continue to resist?
Well, if we're being
honest, you're a terrorist.
If that were true, my goal
would be to spread fear.
But my method is far more surgical.
You kill innocent people.
I helped my government kill
many innocent people and more.
So much more.
Killing to keep things as they were.
And now I'm killing to bring about change.
I think Ethan Hunt would disagree.
Ethan Hunt is a gambler. And
one day his luck will run out,
and thousands of innocent
people will pay the price.
Which one of us will be the villain then?
Nothing here. It's empty.
(EXHALING SHARPLY)
I'm interested to see who you blame
for what happens next.
So that's her?
That's her.
I have to say you sure can ride.
- Ethan...
- You were just doing your job.
That's all we're going to say about it.
Atlee said you would understand.
Atlee. Your handler in
British intelligence.
And he didn't bring you in,
even after you gave him the disk.
You knew perfectly well it was blank.
BENJI: (THROUGH EARPIECE)
That's a lie.
The disk she took from me was
an exact copy. I'm sure of it.
Was it in your possession the entire time?
(SIGHS)
They don't care if you live or die.
But you knew I was going to take it to him.
I hoped you would. I hoped
it'd be enough to get you out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. That means Lane
doesn't have the disk. Only we do.
I have a question.
If the disk was blank,
why is she still alive?
Unless, of course, Lane
wanted us to find her.
So who you working for now?
Lane, Atlee, your government, my
government, they're all the same.
We only think we're
fighting for the right side
because that's what we choose to believe.
So where does that leave us?
The way I see it, you have three choices.
One, you hand me and
the disk over to the CIA.
I am proof the Syndicate exists.
Lane becomes their problem
and your work is done.
My thoughts exactly.
Works for me.
But you know they're not gonna believe you.
And you'll all be tried for treason.
Lane goes free.
I'm afraid she has a point.
Two, you let me walk
away to an uncertain fate.
You use the disk as bait to trap Lane.
But some part of you suspects
you've met your match.
And being a gambler, you'll probably
end up handing Lane that disk,
whether you want to or not.
That is entirely possible.
And option three?
Come away with me.
Right now.
Oh, boy.
And what about Lane?
Forget about Lane.
There will always be another Lane.
There will always be
people like us to face him.
We've done our part and
we've been cast aside.
We can be anyone.
We can do anything.
It's only a matter of going.
Lane sent you to deliver
a message, didn't he?
I've saved your life twice. I
won't be able to do it again.
What's the message?
- (HIGH-PITCHED FEEDBACK)
- (GRUNTS)
ETHAN: Benji.
(PHONE RINGING)
Parking garage.
Luther, stay with her!
She's gone. I lost her.
She set us up, Ethan.
No. She delivered a message.
She set us up! She knew this would happen!
Only Lane knows what's going to happen!
(PHONE RINGING)
LANE: I have a job for you, Ethan.
And for the sake of your
friend, you will do it.
I'm listening.
Your mission, should
you choose to accept it,
is to bring me the unlocked
disk by midnight tonight.
Now say the words, please.
I accept.
Yes.
I knew you would.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- (LINE DISCONNECTS)
He wants the disk, unlocked,
by midnight tonight.
Ethan, there's only one person
on Earth who can unlock that disk.
We have to take the Prime Minister.
(LAUGHS) Let's just think
about that for a minute.
It's the only way to get Benji back.
Ethan, that's exactly
what Lane wants you to do.
Which is why it has to happen.
This is how we beat Lane.
This is how we make everything right.
Can you see?
Can't you see it?
(PHONE RINGS AND BEEPS)
William Brandt, sir. He says it's urgent.
I had a feeling you'd come
to your senses, Brandt.
I'm only calling you because
I have no other choice.
I'm trying to prevent a catastrophe.
I can understand
that. Where are you?
(SIGHS)
London.
Reroute us to London now.
Where in London?
I'll tell you when
you land, not before.
I'm not interested in
playing games, Brandt.
And I'm not interested in seeing
my friends get killed either.
So if I'm going to betray them,
we're going do this on my terms
and my terms only. Do you understand?
- Keep your phone on. Instructions will follow.
- (LINE DISCONNECTS)
LUTHER: You should've
been gone by now.
Yeah.
You okay?
We're supposed to take down
the Prime Minister of
Great Britain tonight.
So...
ETHAN: Brandt?
I can't see another way.
Neither can I.
But we do what we have to
do for our friends, right?
(PANTING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Get him ready, please.
You were right to call
me, Brandt. Where is Hunt?
He's on his way. We don't have much time.
What does he intend to do?
What matters is that he's alive.
And I need your reassurance
that he's going to stay that way.
(SIREN BLARING)
Have you informed the British government
that Hunt has targeted the Prime Minister?
I will help you capture
him alive. That is the deal.
You've picked up some terrible
habits from your friend, Brandt,
the worst of them being that you still
believe you can control any outcome.
Stay with him.
Chief Atlee! Chief Atlee.
Director Hunley, how
delightful to see you here.
Last time we spoke, you were
hunting rogue agents in Morocco.
Chief Atlee, I have reason to believe that
the Prime Minister's life is in danger.
I'm listening.
AUCTIONEER: Any advance on 22,000? Anyone?
Going once. Going twice.
Sold to our generous chairwoman.
Sir? Chief Atlee from MI6 needs to see you.
He says it's urgent.
Excuse me.
What's this all about?
It's a matter of national security, sir.
Under no circumstances is anyone to enter.
Yes, sir.
PRIME MINISTER: Help
me to understand.
Who is this man? Why is he after me?
I'm afraid, Prime Minister,
Director Hunley and I
share responsibility for this.
Ethan Hunt was part of a
disgraced intelligence agency
which has since been dissolved.
ATLEE: And he's gone rogue,
unfortunately intent on dismantling
an imaginary terror network.
But new intelligence
suggests he's been manipulated
by one of your own former agents.
Ilsa Faust, Prime Minister.
She disappeared two years ago.
If you don't mind my asking,
what do I have to do
with this phantom network?
Uh, Sir, this is William Brandt,
a former colleague of Hunt's.
He came forward with firsthand
knowledge of the plot against you.
Sir, Hunt is in possession
of a virtual red box
that can only be opened by you.
He believes it is the key
to bring down the Syndicate.
The Syndicate, you say?
BRANDT: Yes, sir. That's what he calls it.
Atlee?
He couldn't possibly be talking about
that Syndicate.
Because you assured me that that
Syndicate was merely an exercise.
And it was, Prime
Minister, I can assure you.
And yet here we have
the Central Intelligence
Agency indicating otherwise.
I don't understand.
Prime Minister, your life is in danger.
I think our first priority is
to move you to a secure location.
Sir, does the name
Solomon Lane ring a bell?
Yes.
Unfortunately, it does.
So there actually is a Syndicate?
It was the hypothetical
brainchild of Chief Atlee.
Recruit former agents from other nations,
supply them with a new identity,
and use them to surgically
remove our enemies,
both at home and abroad.
Its operating budget
was to be hidden offshore
in a virtual red box which
I alone would control.
It would have made me
judge, jury, and executioner,
with zero accountability.
I rejected the proposal, unequivocally.
Furthermore, I was given every assurance
it never passed the planning stage.
Prime Minister, there is no Syndicate.
These men have been duped by Agent Faust.
Atlee! Save it for the public inquiry.
Sir, I urge you not to leave this room.
- Excuse me.
- Please.
Hunt is uniquely trained
and highly motivated.
A specialist without equal,
immune to any countermeasures.
There is no secret he cannot extract.
No security he cannot breach.
No person he cannot become.
He has, most likely, anticipated
this very conversation
and is waiting to strike in
whatever direction we move.
Sir, Hunt is the living
manifestation of destiny.
And he has made you his mission.
ATLEE: Prime Minister?
(SOFT GROAN)
Hunt.
Sir, please step away
from the Prime Minister.
Just relax, sir. Everything's
going to be all right.
Atlee shot me.
Yes, he did, sir.
Hunt, I hope you realize you've set back
US-UK relations to the
American Revolution?
Desperate times, desperate measures, sir.
(PHONE RINGS)
I'm here.
- ETHAN: Stand by to receive.
- Ready.
The Prime Minister's office
asked me to meet him here.
This way, sir.
Scanning.
Retinal scan confirmed.
Mmm.
It's okay. Here you go, sir.
You've got a very warm hand.
LUTHER: Biometric confirmed.
The prompt is "Kipling."
Sir, I'm going to need a
pass-phrase. The prompt is "Kipling."
PRIME MINISTER: Yes, of course.
"If you can keep your head when
"all about you are losing theirs...
"If you can trust yourself
when all men doubt you..."
- You got it?
- LUTHER: I got it.
Oh, man, do I got it.
I'm here to see the Prime Minister.
We were told not to let anybody in.
By whom?
By you, sir.
ATLEE: Hunley? What is this?
Security!
(BODIES THUDDING)
ETHAN: Chief Atlee.
Kind of you to accept our invitation.
Ah.
Do you know who I am?
We know you created the Syndicate.
But Lane went rogue and turned
it against you, didn't he?
And you've been desperately
trying to cover it up.
That's why you erased the disk
when she brought it to you.
That's true.
Now, Director Hunley has some
questions for you regarding Ilsa Faust.
Namely, how you framed her.
That's also true.
It's the antidote.
When the Prime Minister
found out about the Syndicate,
Atlee attacked him.
Yes, that's true.
And then you saved the Prime Minister, sir.
PRIME MINISTER: Did he?
I'm very grateful.
Sir.
(PHONE RINGING)
You're cutting it very close, Ethan.
I have what you want. Where do I go?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Ethan, wait.
If I'm not there in 15
minutes, he'll kill Benji.
The mission is to bring down the Syndicate.
If Lane gets his hands on that money,
we're unleashing a terrorist superpower.
He'll never take me alive.
I'll make sure of it.
(CLEARS THROAT) And what happens,
Ethan, if you can't make it back?
I'll make it back.
Just be ready.
ATLEE: (ON LAPTOP)
Greetings, Prime Minister.
If you are viewing this message,
it means that you have chosen
to activate the Syndicate.
This disk gives you
access to £2.4 billion
in untraceable currency
that will allow the Syndicate to
operate undetected for decades.
Instructions to access
these funds are as follows.
This is the end, Mr. Hunt.
Careful.
BENJI: Two pounds of Semtex.
Five hundred .30 caliber ball bearings.
Your friend is sitting
on a highly sensitive...
...pressure trigger.
So no sudden moves.
Your final test.
When Lane has what he
wants, I kill you and Benji.
If not, everyone dies.
No time to think, Ethan.
LANE: Have a seat, please.
Human nature. My weapon of choice.
From the moment I killed the
young lady in the record shop,
I knew you would...
...stop at nothing to catch me.
I also knew Ilsa wouldn't have a choice.
Whether she broke you that
night you met or let you go,
whether you let her run in Morocco,
whether she went to Atlee or not...
You were certain we'd end
up where we are right now.
Then, again,
so was I.
I know you, Lane.
Somewhere along the line,
you had a crisis of faith.
Human life didn't matter anymore.
Or maybe it never really did.
Either way, you killed
too many innocent people
without ever asking who was
giving the orders or why.
You blame the system for what
you are, instead of yourself.
You wanted revenge, but Rome
wasn't destroyed in a day.
You needed help. You
needed money, a lot of it.
And you'll stop at nothing to get it.
That's how I know I'm
going to put you in a box.
Where's the disk?
Where is the disk?
ETHAN: You like to play games.
I have a game for you.
I'll give you $50 million
to let Benji go.
Where is the disk?
You're looking at it.
I am the disk.
I memorized it. All £2.4
billion in numbered accounts.
If that vest goes off, you get nothing.
Without this money, you're nothing.
Without me, you're nothing.
Right now, you're
thinking it's a bluff.
I'd never let my friends die.
I couldn't possibly
memorize the entire disk.
There's only one way to be sure.
Let Benji go.
(EXHALING)
Take him.
They come one step closer, shoot me.
Stop!
You remember I told you one day
you were going to take things too far?
This is me speaking, by
the way, it's not him.
The only way this ends is you
and me, Lane, face to face.
Only this time, I won't
be locked in a glass box.
You want your money?
The Bone Doctor is going to have
to beat it out of me! (BANGS TABLE)
Now let Benji go.
1-3-9...
- Go.
- Ethan...
Brandt and Luther are waiting. Go.
What do I do?
Kill the woman.
I need Hunt alive.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Go!
- It's Benji. Where am I going?
- They're coming.
- We're not ready.
Then get ready.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HORNS HONKING)
Which way?
(GUNSHOTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
(SPITS)
(CHOKING)
- (GROANS)
- (BODY THUDDING)
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(EXHALING)
Face to face, just as you wished, Ethan.
(GRUNTING)
It hurts, I know.
Gentlemen, this is Solomon Lane.
Mr. Lane,
meet the IMF.
(AIR HISSING)
You're free now.
Where will you go?
I don't know.
I've done my part.
Yeah.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Ethan, we got to go!
You'd better hurry now.
Good luck.
You know how to find me.
CHAIRMAN: Director Hunley?
Director Hunley!
Uh, Mr. Chairman.
CHAIRMAN: Six months ago,
you stood before this panel
and demanded that the IMF be dissolved.
HUNLEY: That is correct, sir.
How do you explain your testimony today?
It's quite simple, really.
We had reason to believe that
the Syndicate had infiltrated our
government at the highest level.
In order for our man to
infiltrate that organization,
his cover had to be absolute.
The whole operation was known
only to myself and a handful of IMF agents.
So the shuttering of the IMF was
all part of an elaborate scheme
to expose the so-called Syndicate.
That is correct, sir.
Which is why you're here today
asking for the IMF to be reinstated.
That is correct, sir.
I'm not sure the Committee approves
of your methods, Director Hunley.
Uh, desperate times, desperate
measures, Mr. Chairman.
And you, Mr. Brandt, how can
you justify this deception?
I can neither confirm nor
deny details of any operation
without the Secretary's approval.
Welcome to the IMF,
Mr. Secretary.
Sync by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com