Go, go!
Approaching.
I think we have touchdown.
Little to the right.
Hello, mum.
Now, push it in.
I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
Pretend it's your dick, man.
How about I pretend it's your dick?
You'll never get in if you did that.
- Here. Let me have a shot.
- Give me a second.
- No, come on. My dick, man.
- Go.
Fucker.
- Got that.
- Yeah.
Here we go.
Oh, look at that.
- Nice 155, huh?
- Yeah.
It's going to
do some fucking damage.
Hey, Eldridge, looks like
we're going to need a charge.
I got that.
Figured four blocks that'll
give us about 20 pounds of bang total.
That blast is going to
roast straight out there.
The shell will probably kick out there,
and most of the shrapnel
is going to shoot straight up
in a beautiful umbrella pattern.
Yep.
We're gonna get some smaller pieces
and shell fragments this way,
but we'll be okay
if we're behind the Humvee.
- Bring the bot back, we'll load it up.
- No problem.
Bot is moving.
Let me know what you got, Eldridge.
Good to go.
All right. Wagon's
set up. Bot moves.
Uh-oh. We got goats, guys.
Goats 12:00. Watch out.
Load them little bastards up.
- Oh, shit.
- Shit.
Oh, fuck.
Wagon's having a bad day, boys.
- You build that?
- No, the U.S. Army did.
All right. Looks like
I'm going down there.
You don't like waiting around
this beautiful neighborhood?
Oh, I love it.
So, if everything looks okay,
when I get down there
I'm just going
to set it up and bip it.
Give these people
something to think about.
Want them to know if they're gonna leave
a bomb on the side of the road for us,
we're just going to blow up
their little fuckin' road.
Sounds good.
Craving a burger; is that strange?
- Not for you.
- No, okay.
Helmet on.
Happy trails.
Blaster One, can you read me?
Roger that, Blaster one.
You're good to go.
You're looking good, Blaster One.
Nice and hot in here.
One fifty.
Roger that, 150 meters
Hi.
- Where are you from?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where are you from?
California?
- Hey, get out of here, man.
- Where?
Hey, this ain't no fuckin' meet
and greet. Now get out of here.
Now.
Go.
You making friends again, Sanborn?
All day long.
Twenty-five.
Twenty-five meters. Roger that.
You are now in the kill zone.
Thanks for reminding me.
That's what I'm here for, baby.
Okay-
The debts look good.
Roger that,
I'm laying on the charge.
Nice and sweet.
We're good to go.
I'm coming back.
- Five meters out.
- Five meters, Roger that.
Hey, Sanborn
- You know what this place needs?
- I'm listening.
Needs grass.
We gonna start our grass business?
That's right, man
I'm going to sell the grass,
you're going to cut it.
It's going to be called
"Sanborn and Sons".
We'll be rich.
I like that, Crabgass.
St. Augustine, man.
I'm a scholar on this shit.
How about this?
You sell it. I fertilize it.
- 25.
- 25 meters. Roger that.
Sanborn!
Butcher shop, 2:00,
dude has a phone!
Why is Eldridge running?
- Make him put it down!
- Put down the phone!
Come on, guys. Talk to me.
Drop the phone!
Drop your phone!
Hey, burn him, Eldridge. Burn him!
- Put down the cell phone!
- Eldridge, burn him!
- Get out of the way.
- Drop your phone!
Make him put it down!
Go get it!
- Come on, Eldridge!
- I can't get him in sight!
Thompson!
Anywhere's good.
- Is that everything?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
Come in,
Sergeant James.
JT Sanborn, my man.
Hey. Hi, how are you? Will.
I'm Will.
Welcome to Bravo Company;
welcome to Camp Victory.
Camp Victory?
I thought this was Camp Liberty.
Oh, no. They changed
that about a week ago.
Victory sounds better.
All right. Well, at least
I'm in the right place, right?
Yeah.
While you're here, can you help me
move this thing real quick?
Yeah, no problem.
Maybe you shouldn't take this down.
We get a lot of mortars at night.
The plywood on the windows help
with the lateral fray coming through.
That's why it's up there.
Yeah, well, it's not going
to stop a mortar round
from coming in through
the roof, you know.
Besides, I like the sunshine.
Hey, I'm sorry to hear about Thompson.
- I know he was a good tech.
- Yeah, he was.
He was a great team leader too.
Yeah, I'm not trying
to fill his shoes or anything.
I'm just...
I'm just going to do my best.
- Appreciate it.
- All right.
Cool.
Home sweet home, right?
Aren't you glad the Army has
all these tanks parked here?
Just in case the Russians come
we have to have a big tank battle.
I'd rather be
on the side with the tanks,
just in case, rather than not have them.
Yeah, but they don't do anything.
Anyone comes alongside
a Humvee we're dead.
Anybody even looks
at you funny we're dead.
Pretty much the bottom line is
if you're in Iraq, you're dead.
How's a fuckin' tank
supposed to stop that?
- Would you shut up, Owen?
- Sorry.
Just trying to scare the new guy.
I saw a little bit in Afghanistan too.
- Get your eyes on the road, Eldridge.
- Copy that.
Move.
Move!
Blaster One, this is Victory Main.
Have you reached your 10-20, yet? Over.
Where the hell are the guys
who called this in?
Victory Main. Victory Main.
this is Blaster Mike.
Interrogative, do you have
an update on position? Over.
Victory Main, figures to follow.
Three-four-five-three is your grid.
Well, that's exactly where the hell I am
and I don't see anybody in fatigues.
Give us a second to confirm.
Watch your feet.
Set visual
is three-four five-three.
Got the Humvee.
Friendly!
Friendly.
Ah, here we go.
They abandoned their vehicle.
We got an empty Humvee
over here, James.
Yeah, I got it.
Let's move.
Friendly.
- Morning, boys.
- Sir.
Don't tell me the bomb's
in here with you guys.
Step out and I'll
show you what's going on.
All right.
Down on that block 20 meters,
this side of the mosque,
east side of the street,
our informant says he saw
a pair of wires
going into a rubble pile.
- It's a possible IED.
- Yeah.
- I trust this guy. I know him.
- Okay.
I'll handle it.
- Do you want to talk him or...
- No.
Good. Keep your boys back.
We'll be good. Thank you.
Specialist, bring up the Humvee.
What's going on?
I'm going to break out the suit.
- What about the bot?
- I'll take care of it.
Don't you want to send the bot down
there to see what it looks like?
I'll handle it.
That's kind of tight down here, James.
Ready?
Good?
You don't have to go down there.
We already have the bot halfway up.
I'll be all right.
First day, figure you want
to take it easy, right?
How's it looking, Eldridge?
- Good to go.
- Let's do it.
- Got two of 'em?
- Got two.
All right. Let's rock and roll, man.
- He's a rowdy boy.
- He's reckless.
Blaster One, what's going on?
Blaster One! What are you doing?
Blaster One, this is Blaster Mike.
What's with the smoke
on the side of the road?
Hey. James, can you hear me?
What's going on with the smoke
on the side of the road? Over.
Creating a diversion
From what? Is there a threat?
Eldridge, get up on the wall. Move!
Tell me what you see, specialist.
All right, I got him.
He's walking down range.
James, the smoke
is killing my visibility.
Where are you
in relationship to the IED?
Are you within 100 meters yet?
Hell, I don't know, but I'll tell you
when I'm standing over it, cowboy.
Take cover!
Oh, no. A car stopped
in front of him, Sanborn
Shit. James! James, come back now.
EOD pulled a nine
on this Haji in a car.
Want me to send backup?
I got it.
- Get here!
- Negative! Negative!
Stand down.
The blast will come up the block.
Stay clear around the corner.
EOD has the situation
under control, over.
Where you going?
Want to back up?
Get out of the car!
- Get out of the car!
- Come on!
What the fuck are you doing?
Back up.
Hello?
Want to get back?
It's that way.
Back.
Taxi's moving.
Get out of the car!
Stop!
Stay down!
Well, if he wasn't an insurgent.
he sure the hell is now.
Roger that. That's real funny.
Got something.
Oh, baby.
Gotcha.
All right.
We're done.
Good to go.
Come down, specialist.
Roger.
Got a wire.
Hang on.
Where are you going?
Secondary.
Shit.
Take cover. Get in the wall.
Get in the wall.
That wasn't so bad. First time working
together. What do you think?
I think us working together means
I talk to you and you talk to me.
- We going on a date, Sanborn?
- No.
We're going on a mission,
and my job is to keep you safe
so we can keep going on missions.
It's combat, buddy.
Hey.
It's just 39 days.
Thirty-eight if we survive today.
Hey, it's "Mr. Be All You Can Be".
What's up, doc?
Not much. How are you?
I'm good.
Got a question about that
song, "Be All You Can Be".
What if all I can be is dead
on the side of an Iraqi road?
I mean, I think it's logical.
This is war. People die
all the time. Why not me?
You got to change
the record in our head.
You gotta start thinking
about other things.
Okay.
Stop obsessing... Right now.
What are you thinking about?
You want to know
what I'm thinking about, doc? Yeah.
This is what I'm thinking about, doc.
Here's Thompson, okay.
He's dead. He's alive.
Here's Thompson.
Yo, what's up, my nigger?
What's up, man? You cool?
Come on. You want the cool shit?
Come on, come on.
It's the tight shit, man.
Wanna buy DVD?
Fuck you.
Come, come, please, please.
New releases. Look.
Hello. Hello.
Want to buy DVDs? Very good. Very good.
How much?
One for five and two for nine.
Three for twelve.
Three for thirteen and I don't
give you tax. Very good, man. Look.
- Look...
- No tax?
All right. What do you got?
What do you got.
You know, you smart shit.
You not like those stupid fucks.
Yeah, I'm the smart guy.
You're a smart kid.
Give me your best one, okay?
- Here, this the best one.
- This is a good one?
- Yeah. The best shit, man.
- Okay.
Here you go,
I'll take one.
- Keep the change.
- Thank you.
Want a cigarette?
Get out of here.
You shouldn't smoke.
Thank you. Take it easy.
I need to talk to you about
something before we go out again.
What's that?
- Yesterday.
- Mm-hmm.
Wasn't cool.
Yeah, I know.
You'll get it, though.
- So, you're a ranger, huh?
- Yeah.
I was in intelligence seven years
before I joined EOD.
We ran missions in every shithole
that you could possibly imagine.
So, I'm pretty sure I can figure out a
piece of redneck trailer trash like you.
Looks like you're on the right track.
We'll see you out there.
Let's go, move!
Shit. Get out of the way. Move.
Hallo.
- Where is it?
- It's behind the wall.
- All right.
- See any wires? Any smoke?
No, I didn't look.
So, how do you know it's a bomb?
Car has been parked illegally.
The suspension is sagging. There's
definitely something heavy in the trunk.
Right. So, why don't you walk over there
and peak inside and tell me what you see.
You want me to go close to it?
Yeah. No-no. I don't. I'm kidding.
Shit.
It's coming from over here!
Blaster One. You there?
Blaster One, you hear me?
Here.
Shit.
Let's go, guys.
Let it go.
I got top cover.
That's a negative, specialist.
Eldridge, you stay with me.
Sanborn, you take top covers.
Shit.
Blaster Mike in position.
What do you got?
I got a through and through to
the chest, but I got him stable.
He's not going to make it.
We're leaving in 15 minutes.
Got a survival wound, sir.
He's not going to make it.
Oh, God.
- What's he doing?
- I don't know.
What are you doing?
There's enough bang in there
to send us all to Jesus.
If I'm going to die,
I'm going to die comfortable.
I need my kit and my cans.
What's going on down there, Eldridge?
I'm getting his kit and his cans.
Cover me, please.
Kit and cans.
Got a lot of deck cord, electrical.
I'm looking for this initiating system.
Well, it's not in the back seat.
I don't think.
All right. It's not in the back seat.
Got a young man on the roof,
your 9:00, keep an eye on him.
Roger that.
It's not in the front seat.
It's not in the door.
Not on the floors.
Not in the glove box.
If you haven't found it yet.
it's probably under the car.
Yeah. No wire leads under... the car.
It's all in here somewhere.
- Hey, Sanborn.
- Yeah.
You got eyes on some guy.
with a video camera?
No. Where?
He's right at my 12:00, you see him?
He's pointing the fucking thing at me.
Shit.
Negative, I don't see him.
Hey, Sanborn. He's right
at my 12:00. Look! 12:00!
Roger that, I got him.
Getting ready to put me on You Tube.
Little shady.
Yeah, he looks shady.
Keep and eye on him.
Okay. So, what's the play?
Be smart. Make a good decision, over
Got more wire.
Leads fucking nowhere.
Fuck!
Hey, James, how you doing?
I'm wonderful. How are you?
You know, we've been here a while.
We need to get out of here soon.
Uh-huh.
We got a lot of eyes on us, James.
We need to get out of here.
Roger that. I'm going
to figure this out.
James, we need to get out of here.
James, do you copy?
Fuck it. I get it.
Fuck me.
Hey, how's it looking in there, soldier?
All clear.
James, the evac
is complete. We can leave.
Let the engineers handle this mess.
- We moving?
- That's affirmative.
Interesting.
What's up with James?
He's not answering.
Yeah, I think he removed his headset.
Well, will you tell him to
put his radio back on, please?
Hey, James!
Sergeant Sanborn is asking if
you'll please put your headset back on.
Uh... that's a negative.
That, yeah, that's not going to happen.
I got eyes on three guys
at the Minaret at 6:00.
- What the hell is he doing?
- I don't know what the fuck he's doing.
Looks like, he's checking the oil.
They're communicating
with your cameraman.
This is real bad man.
Get behind the Jersey barrier.
I can't see James from here.
Get down now!
We can go!
Bastard.
We're done.
Sanborn, let's get out of here.
Woo.
That was good.
- Hey, James.
- What?
Never turn your headset off again.
You the guy in the bomb suit?
No, sir. Sir, that's Sergeant James.
He's right here.
- Hey. James.
- Yeah?
Someone's here to see you.
You the guy in the flaming car,
Sergeant James?
Afternoon, sir.
Uh, yes, sir.
Well, that's just hot shit.
You're a wild man, you know that?
- Uh, yes, sir.
- He's a wild man.
You know that?
I want to shake your hand.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
How many bombs have you disarmed?
Uh, I'm not quite sure.
- Sergeant?
- Yes, sir.
I asked you a question.
Eight hundred seventy-three, sir.
Eight hundred! And seventy-three.
That's just hot shit.
Eight-hundred and seventy-three.
- Counting today, sir, yes.
- That's gotta be a record.
What's the best way to... go about
disarming one of these things?
The way you don't die, sir.
That's a good one.
That's spoken
like a wild man. That's good.
- Hey, what's up, man?
- Oh, hey, wait a minute.
Look who it is.
I want my five bucks back, buddy.
Five dollars for what, man?
You crazy now?
Yeah. The DVD you sold me was crap.
You crazy, man. That's impossible.
It's Hollywood special effects.
No. It was shaky.
It was out of focus, buddy.
- What, you want donkey porn?
- It's crap.
- Girls on dog?
- Gay sex, man?
Anything you want, you get.
I hook you up, man.
All right. What... what's your name?
- Beckham.
- Beckham like the soccer player?
Yeah, man. It's like soccer player.
Now give me my ball.
Are you a soccer player?
Yeah, man. Best of the best.
I'm better than Beckham.
You play goalie?
- Yes, I play goalie.
- Okay.
I'll make you a deal. If you can stop the
ball, I'm going to give you five bucks,
- but if you can't...
- And what if... what if I can't?
Listen to me. If I score,
I'm going to keep your ball.
- Deal?
- Deal.
Get up there.
Go on.
- Let's see what you got hot stuff.
- Are you ready?
On three. Ready?
One, two, three. Aahh!
Shit.
Come on. Where's the five dollars?
Man, come on.
All right, I got ya.
Good job, dude.
Here's five.
You're an EOD, boomala, boomala.
That's right.
It's fun, no?
It's cool? It's gangster.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I think so.
Tell you what, I'm going to buy...
Let me see if I have
enough money, yeah. Five.
I'm going to buy another DVD, okay?
But if it's shakey... look at me...
or out of focus...
or any way not 100%.
I'm going to chop off your goddammed
head with a dull knife.
How do you feel about that?
I'm just kidding.
Here. You're a good kid, man.
You're a good kid, aren't ya?
Owen.
Hi.
- Hi, sir.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- Good.
- What's wrong?
- Brakes are squeaking.
Don't trust the mechanics
around here. You know.
- So, how you doing?
- Good.
I just want to check the oil.
Yeah, it's good to sleep, eating well...
I'm feeling pretty squared
away, actually, doc.
Good to hear it.
So, you getting along with the other
soldiers in your unit?
Yeah. My team's great.
My team leader is inspiring.
- Are you being sarcastic, soldier?
- No.
He's going to get me killed,
almost died yesterday.
At least I'll die in the line
of duty, proud and strong.
You know, this doesn't have
to be a bad time in your life.
Going to war is a- is a once
in a lifetime experience.
It could be fun.
And you know this from your
extensive work in the field, right?
I've done my field duty.
Where's that? Yale?
Look, you don't want me to come around,
I won't come around.
These talks are voluntary.
Look, I'm sorry,
I appreciate
what you're saying, I do.
I appreciate our sessions together,
but you need to come out from
behind the wire, see what we do.
Well,
if this circumstance calls for it,
I will.
Just like every other soldier
Fire in the hole!
Firing now.
Eee, ooh...
- Ready for second det?
- Ready.
Fire in the hole!
Fire in the hole. Fire in the hole.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on a second.
Goddamn it,
I think it forgot my gloves down there.
- What?
- I forgot my gloves.
Hang on.
You know, these detonators
misfire all the time.
What are you doing?
I'm just saying shit happens,
they misfire.
He'd be obliterated to nothing.
His helmet would be left.
You could have that.
Little specs of hair,
charred on the inside.
Yeah. There'd be half
a helmet somewhere,
bits of hair.
Ask for a change
in technique and protocol,
make sure this type of accident
never happen again, you know?
You'd have to write the report.
- Are you serious?
- I can't write it.
No. I mean, are you serious
about killing him?
- Twelve o'clock I see an SUV.
- Roger that.
I got four armed men.
They're in Haji gear.
All right. Go slow and easy.
Careful now.
All right. Careful now, guys.
- Eldridge, you stay on that 50.
- I got 'em.
"Obre... obre..."
put your gun down!
On your knees!
Put your gun down!
- Obre, motherfucker!
- Hold up your hands.
Get down, motherfucker. Obre!
Put your gun down now!
Put your gun down!
Advance, advance...
Hands high.
- Eldridge, cover!
- I got you.
Pistol, off your hip, now.
What you want me to do?
Keep
my hands up or take off the pistol?
- Keep your hands up.
- Okay.
Easy, easy.
Got it!
Can I touch my fucking head now?
Slowly.
We're on the same fucking side, guys.
Jesus.
You guys are wired fucking tight,
you know that?
Well, this is no place for a picnic.
What are you guys doing here?
We have a flat tire.
Can you help us?
Sure, yeah. You got any spares?
We have spares, but
we've used up our wrench.
How do you use up a wrench?
Well, the uh, the guy over there
with the red thing on his head.
He threw it at someone.
- All right.
- Thank you.
That's Chris. This is the wrench man.
Hello, wrench man. That's Jimmy.
You know, you can shoot people here.
You don't have to throw a wrench at 'em.
Fuck off.
Take a look at this.
I picked these guys up in Najaf.
Nine of hearts, that's one.
And the other...
jack of clubs.
- These the same guys?
- Yep. That's them.
Does he need a little help there?
What's the problem
with the tire? Come on.
No good, boss.
This wrench is too small.
All right, solutions? Anyone?
I think there's another wrench in the
back of the Humvee if you want to check.
- I'll give it a try.
- All right. Let's do it.
How long you guys out here?
Specialist, what do we got?
- We have... 23 more days or 22...
- Oh yeah.
No one's counting.
Contact left.
Take cover,
Chris, take the 50, Jimmy,
take that in the Humvee.
- Got it.
- Come on!