Copy that! Over and out.
Gotta get these hinges greased, Mick.
Come on.
The grease isn't the problem.
It's the hinge.
This is a creaky old dinosaur.
This old girl should've
been retired ten years ago.
Yeah. Well, they should've
retired me ten years ago.
Not you, Charlie. You're in your prime.
I should know because we're the same age
and I'm in my prime.
Hey, is that coffee still hot?
Yeah, it's hot enough.
All right, then.
Do me a favor.
You ever thought about
buying a coffee maker?
Coffee maker?
You know, one that's
got that milk froster thing.
Oh, yeah. Frother. I got you.
Yeah
that way you can, uh... thanks.
You know, make your own cappuccino.
Oh, goddamn.
I thought you said this coffee was hot.
What is this?
Dude, it's typical. What's our time?
I don't know,
but this truck needs to get moving.
The game's gonna be starting soon.
The freeway's gonna be backed up.
Oh, fuck! Shit! Reverse!
- The fuck are we supposed to do now?
- You know what to do, follow protocol.
What the fuck!
- Dispatch, come in!
- They're cutting the fucking door!
We're being hit by armed assailants.
Repeat, armed robbery in progress.
Coming in!
They're cutting the door.
Hands up! Hands up in the air.
Let's go, move it.
Get the fuck out.
Keep your hands away from your weapons.
Hands away from your weapons.
Come on, let's go.
- Fortico 1377, alarm raised...
- Move!
Fuck me.
- Alarm registered.
- Clear!
Do what we say
and you fucking live.
Two black-and-whites en route.
Approximately two minutes away.
Two minutes dispatched.
Incoming eta two minutes.
Two minutes.
Bravo, can you hear me?
- Fuck!
- Please respond.
What the fuck is going on out there?
He shot two fucking guards, Elvis.
He shot two fucking guards.
- Number one, are we good?
- Bravo, come in.
- Are we good, number one?
- We're good.
What's happening there?
Number one just
shot a fucking kid.
He shot a fucking...
- What do you see?
- Incoming. Incoming.
- Elvis, what's the play?
- Incoming!
- I'm on him.
- Take the legs.
Fuck!
- Oh, my god. What the fuck?
- I said the fucking legs.
Okay, we've got one minute.
Let's go.
- Come on!
- Exit west. We gotta go. Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
Fortico security specialize in armed guard
cash pick-up trucks and deliveries across L.A.
Our clients are made up
of large scale retail department stores,
marijuana dispensaries, cash vaults,
casinos, private banks.
Can I get another one”?
Thank you.
We're not federal.
We're essentially middle men.
Hundreds of millions
shifting through here every week.
We got 12 trucks,
two or three guards in each.
A driver, a messenger and a guard.
Each moving up to 15 mil a day
and sometimes more,
which can attract unwanted attention.
I won't lie, it can be dangerous.
Which is why we train you properly
and pay the premium rates.
So we can all sleep better at night.
Thanks.
Now your background checks
came back fine.
And your reference from
orange delta security was impressive.
That was a good company.
I'm sorry to hear it went bust.
Family? Married
- divorced.
- No one else?
No
Good. Stay focused. I like it.
But just so you know,
we lost a couple of guards a while back.
Killed on the job, a civilian too.
A fucking tragedy.
And they still haven't
found the scum who did it.
And that's why we've upped our game.
Sixty hours of firearms training.
Patrick?
Are you Patrick hill?
Yeah, no, please, don't get up.
Good to meet you.
Let's see, hill, hill.
H. I'm gonna call you h,
if that's okay.
They call me bullet.
Which is ironic
because I certainly don't move like one.
- Are you ready for target practice?
- Ready.
I saw you had your pistol license already.
So this is the pre-assignment
training course.
We got eight hours together.
Popping cans off walls and the like.
You need to hit the 70% pass Mark.
There's some fitness which, by the looks
of it, shouldn't be a problem for you.
We just need to see
how you are under pressure.
Shall we get started?
Whatever you say, bullet.
That's quite enough of that.
Been a while, huh?
Little practice, I'm sure you'll get there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, too far, too far.
Pull it up a little. Pull it up.
I ook at that: 70%.
You just slipped in.
Any less, we'd be doing this again.
You won't be joining a formula 1 team
any time soon,
but you'll do for this job.
Let's get you suited.
How many we've got coming?
In that case I'll get three pounds of ribs
and a bucket of wings for the kids.
Cough up, bullet.
- Dude, I'm on the phone.
- I don't care. Thirty dollars.
- How much?
- Thirty bucks.
- Wait for it. Wait for it.
- Change.
- Suplex!
- I want that money.
- There you go, buddy.
- Give me the dollar, dollar.
- Forty-one...
- Thank you.
Forty-two's not gonna beat me.
- Fuck off, Dana.
- Come on.
You're not supposed to be here, anyway.
No, I think it's you who's
in the wrong change room, Stuart.
Come on, let's
look lively, people.
Chop-chop, show me your money.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a new addition.
- Here you go, Shirley.
- May I introduce h.
Yeah, she'll do.
Put 'em down, Dana.
Come on. I'll show you your locker.
This one is yours.
You good? Yeah.
Why, don't I look it?
No, buddy, you look like
a shrink-wrapped Rolls-Royce
in contrast to this car crash.
Meet hollow Bob and boy sweat Dave.
You look like you could do
some pull ups.
I put a 50 on you beating boy sweat here.
What's the matter with him?
He looks good for it.
Yeah, that's what boy sweat thinks.
But he's also a cock.
- Who's a cock?
- You're a cock, Dave.
I reckon our man here
could pull yours right off.
He looks like he could handle a cock.
Yeah small hands.
Makes me very popular
and you look good.
What's that?
I said, uh...
I'm sure you'd win.
At what?
The pull ups.
Oh, charming.
One of yours?
I've been looking for him.
- I'll put him back in the collection.
- Glad I could help.
You're making friends already.
It's worth getting to know Dave.
He's quite entertaining
in an unintentional kind of way.
Yeah. He once killed a hamster
because he squeezed it too tight.
He can't write
without sticking his tongue out.
This is your temporary side arm.
Just till you get your own.
I need you to love it, respect it,
and bring it back in one piece.
They want us back in one piece too?
- Do you have a problem?
- I don't know, do 1?
What happens if we're pulling pistols
in a machine-gun fight?
Then you retort
with a positive mental attitude.
- Name?
- He's h.
H.
I ike the bomb or like Jesus h.
Well, if you can mushroom cloud
or walk on water,
what you worried about machine guns for?
It's the rock star's first day.
All right. Lucky I got a soft drop then.
Try to keep your piece strapped,
like he should have done on prom night.
You're just unhappy I'm happy.
Yeah, only man I know that married
the first woman he banged.
You're a cynical old dog, supe.
But I still got plenty of bitches.
Of course he does.
Oh, that's nice.
- Who's your pal?
- I'll explain later.
Jesus Christ,
at least try to look busy, Shirley.
You're gonna love who your new partner is.
Just tell me it ain't the limey.
Commando doof himself
fuck!
Boy sweat, you'll be happy to hear
that h is replacing sticky John.
- Thank you, Stuart.
- Got it, bullet.
Stay out from under my feet
and we'll get along just fine.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous this job can be?
Somewhat do, yeah.
No, you have no idea.
We ain't the predators, we're the prey.
Ooh.
Boy sweat's up front.
You jump in there with him.
Whatever you say, boss.
Hear about the guards that
were murdered? It happened down there.
Come on, Dave, it's his first day.
What? He needs to hear this.
Don't engage.
He'll forget what he said in a moment.
I heard.
It's a tragedy.
What you didn't hear is that I was
meant to be driving the truck that day.
Why wasn't you?
- I was sick.
- Hungover.
Sick! All holes.
The last thing I needed
was the feds in my face
trying to make out if I was involved.
Lucky you had a strong alibi.
Fuck you, bullet.
He was staying at his mom's.
She knows how I like my eggs.
This is a $2 million pick up
for bank of the us.
Dave will stay in the truck.
H, you're coming with me.
You get to meet the lovely ladies
who work the tills.
Just be wary of hot Betty.
If you're lucky,
she'll only take your fucking arm off.
Godfrey, h. H, Godfrey.
- H.
- Godfrey.
X marks the spot.
Godfrey, as always, a pleasure.
I like the way you handle that cart.
Where did you learn that technique?
Spent a lot of time in supermarkets.
Shopping.
I can picture it now.
A paragon of modern man on a wild sojourn,
stalking down the aisles,
hunting for pop-tarts.
Pop-tarts are not really my poison, bullet.
I prefer to lose myself in the dizzy food
coma of synthetic cheese and impossible meat.
What has the world come to?
A direct line of evolution.
From paleolithic man...
To a diabetic house husband.
- Harsh.
- But true.
How'd your boy do”?
Did he survive the hostile territory
of hot Betty and the menopausal milfs?
Did you make poo-poo
or is your diaper still clean?
He did just fine.
Hot Betty almost slid off her seat.
So there's juice in the old raisin yet.
Wakey, wakey, sticky.
2411. Clear to proceed.
Pull in slowly this time, boy sweat.
Base, this is gamma. Reporting back.
Copy that, gamma.
Who's that boyfriend of yours?
They always gotta see the driver
and messenger,
otherwise, you ain't getting in.
Okay, gamma. You're clear.
At least your boy didn't fuck that up.
I still prefer sticky John.
- Everyone prefers sticky John.
- Mm_
You're gonna love him, Dave.
He's got that exotic European thing
working for him.
It'll take you a while to dial in.
Hasn't taken me very long.
I don't care what you guys think.
That man's a dark horse.
What do you mean by that?
That cat's overqualified for this game.
He's got history.
We're all overqualified for this game.
And we all got history.
Beer and pool? Your first day is over.
It's a tradition.
Sure. Give me two minutes.
- Point of the game is to get the ball in the hole.
- Point of a woman is to shut the fuck up, Dana.
Well, that Ivy league education
is really working for you, boy sweat.
Pretty soon, you'll all be working for me.
Power is in this big head here.
It's definitely not in your little head,
or you still blaming the beer?
Yo, you gonna take your shot or what?
At least I'll still be here next week
to take a shot.
What's that supposed to mean?
He's already got your road job.
Word around the pool table is
boss has eyes for the new boy.
What, flat-footed limey? I'd shit him.
Maybe you should say that to his face.
Maybe I will.
I spy with my little eye that I smell fear.
That doesn't make any sense.
Hey, John.
You're an idiot
fucking assholes.
Here comes the walk of shame.
Yo, action man, can I buy you a beer?
No
Sorry...
You mind?
So where did you work before then?
Orange delta security, Europe.
Jolly exciting, was it, mate?
Yeah, spectacular.
You ain't much for talking,
are you, Mary poppins?
Uh, no, I can talk.
I just don't want to talk to you.
Let me buy you a beer.
Just make sure you drink it over there.
Anything else?
I gotta give it to you, h.
You're a real social magician.
First, you take his job...
And then you make him cry in his beer.
What is taking him so long?
It's a 10-grand drop. He should have
been back five minutes ago.
Hey, bullet, what's taking you so long?
Bullet, unless you found
some beautiful, blue-eyed latino boy,
you should be back by now.
Fucking fuck!
Don't fucking look at me...
Dave.
They're gonna fucking kill me.
Now listen to me, ladies,
if you want to see your girlfriend again,
you'll do exactly as I say.
Um
Um, I have to call this... no, uh...
There's a protocol for this.
We have to drive away.
Sorry?
They don't want his 10 grand.
The money is in the truck. We have
2.5 million dollars. If we take it away,
they're not gonna hurt him.
Dave
you need to pull yourself together.
You need to reconsider this.
Reconsider? That's why they have
the fucking policy!
You don't want to do this?
Get out of the truck now.
But we're not leaving him behind.
He's one of us. It's only money.
In short, I'm getting him back.
Stop fucking around.
You have one minute before she dies.
Now turn the key and drive
and I will tell you when to stop.
Are you gonna drive or you getting out?
Oh, shit.
This is such a bad idea
Take the next left.
Now stop the truck.
All right. All right.
We got your fucking friend,
he don't mean shit to us.
They're serious.
Shut the fuck up.
Open the fucking doors
and pick up the money
and throw it in the flatbed.
You open up, they're just gonna kill us
and take the money, anyway.
Dave, you just worry about putting
your asshole back in your asshole.
And leave this to me.
Fuck!
- Fuck.
- This guy's fucking around.
- He's throwing bags on the floor.
- Goddamn it.
Listen up, fuckboy.
I said throw the money
in the fucking flatbed.
Try to get clever again and old boy's
getting a face full of shit.
Don't be fucking slick.
Just do what he says.
These guys are fucking serious.
Get it in the truck next time,
you fuck nut.
Sorry, pal.
Fuck!
Fuck
put the gun down... take the money!
Please, stop!
Give them the fucking money!
Are you fucking insane?
Fuck!
Bullet! Bullet!
Who is this fucking lunatic?
Fuck!
Who do you work for?
Suck my fucking dick.
What did you say?
I said suck my fucking dick.
Suck your own dick.
You all right, Dave?
Did you make poo-poo?
Thank you.
Last but not least, Mr. hill.
Well, you're all
sticking to the same story.
That's what happened.
What I don't understand
is how you managed to take down six men
without even so much as a scratch.
You gotta admit it's impressive.
He saved his partner's life.
What about your firearms experience”?
Your shooting
was unambiguously precise yet...
Your training scores
were decidedly average.
Barely even passed.
Kill or be killed.
Seemed to focus the mind.
All right. Well, there's something else.
I'd like you to take a look at this video.
This is security footage from the raid
on the fortico cash truck before,
when the guards were killed.
- I can't watch this again.
- Step outside, by all means.
We just want you to let us know
if you think there's any connection
between this robbery
and the men you encountered before.
You all right to keep watching?
Yeah
I'm all right.
Mr. hill?
Anything ringing a bell?
Any connection, Mr. hill? No.
You sure?
I'm sure.
All right, Mr. hill,
we'll pick this up another day.
- Are we done”?
- Yeah, we'll be in touch.
Visit the therapist. Rest up.
Thank you, Mr. hill.
Patrick, can I have a word?
We have a policy.
The shrinks advise that employees
be taken off the front line
for a month following violent incidents,
and longer if lives are lost.
So we're gonna transfer you to desk duty
in case of PTSD.
Do I look disturbed?
No, you don't, but then
these things take time to manifest,
to percolate.
It's with your best interests at heart.
You hired me to do a job, did a job.
No, we hired you to move money.
You hired me to protect money.
Mr. hill”?
Hey, I'm Blake halls. I own fortico.
I wanted to congratulate you for yesterday
and to thank you in person.
What you did deserves credit.
You're a real hero,
and that's not wasted on me.
Take the rest of the day off
while Terry and I discuss
your promising future.
Terry, we need that guy in the field.
If we'd had him last year,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
He's exactly what we need.
And the publicity for fortico
has been very positive.
Plus, have you heard the crews talking?
They're inspired.
So don't punish him, promote him.
- Well?
- Yes, it was him.
It had him written all over it.
Question is, what was he doing there?
I think we know
what he was doing there, boss.
Clever fucking you, Hubbard.
It's called sarcasm.
What do you want us to do?
Not a fucking thing, let the painter paint.
Do you have any idea
what would happen to us
if anyone found out that
we let the fox in the fucking hen house?
The bureau's been trying
to catch this man for 25 years.
We're just gonna let him
sit on hundreds of millions?
Money doesn't mean a thing to him.
Listen, there's a reason
why I chose you two,
because we have the same priorities.
Now listen to me very carefully.
As far as you're concerned, he's just
a reqular guard doing a good job.
Do we understand each other?
I oud and clear.
"Let the painter paint"?
What the fuck does that look like?
Fortico personnel files.
Pictures of Dana's family.
And... the autopsy report.
Show me your fucking ass.
Face down on the ground right now.
Face on the fucking ground.
Seems you can walk on water after all.
Keep up the good work, soldier.
Nice one, man.
Be my guest.
All right, brother.
Good job, man. Let's go.
Jump on up, big boy.
We should get takeout from the blossom.
The noodle soup at Neptune's is the bomb.
I prefer the blossom.
All right.
You're gonna call the order in?
I'm busy.
I can see that.
Who's this joker?
What the hell is going on?
- Move! Get the fuck back.
- Get back!
- Reverse. Reverse.
- I can't fucking see.
Gamma to base, we have a code red.
Gamma, this is base.
What's your location, over?
Take cover!
Chinatown, Broadway and hill.
Repeat, code red in progress.
Just follow procedures.
Stay in the truck, over.
- Get out of the fucking truck!
- Police were dispatched.
Come on, get out of there.
Get out of the truck.
They're coming.
On the ground.
Open the fucking doors.
(Set down!
Get down on the ground.
You got three seconds.
So let me get this straight.
They just walked away.
Get in the fucking Van! Move it!
Let's fucking go now!
Doors were open.
What the fuck was it, Mike?
It was the...
Yeah
turned back around and left
no, I'm sorry.
But what Terry is trying to say
is that you're a legend.
And if you keep this up,
you won't just be employee of the month.
You'll have your own calendar
and merchandise.
Now get out there and keep crushing it.
Why are you so cynical?
I'm starting to think he's a psychopath.
I hear h is for hero.
Drink?
It doesn't feel right.
It was as if he recognized h.
Like he saw a dark spirit.
What are you saying?
I don't know what I'm saying.
He's not a cop.
Doesn't smell like a cop.
But if he's not a cop, what is he?
He's a dark fucking spirit.
Put that on.
Meet me next door.
I told you that first day.
I don't trust him.
What the hell are you doing?
Sit down.
I'm not sitting down.
I want to go back to bed.
Dana, sit down.
You've got ten seconds to explain this.
I'm not telling you anything.
Dana, it's very important...
That you take my inquiry seriously.
I take it very seriously
that you think you can interrogate me
in my own fucking house.
Jesus. Fuck! Jesus Christ.
It's my savings, all right?
The fuck has it got to do with you?
You're not listening.
Fuck. All right. Okay, please, stop.
Sit down.
I found it.
Okay, it was being signed for one day
by the staff at crown liquor.
They missed it, it was in the trolley.
- You stole it?
- Yeah, I fucking stole it.
It's 125,000.
It's my retirement fund.
Working with anyone on the inside?
No, what the fuck...?
Think carefully
before you answer the question.
No
The retirement fund is yours.
But if it comes to light that you're not
telling me something that I need to know...
I want you to understand
how resourceful and serious I am.
On the table's a picture of your parents.
Had it taken last week.
I know who you love.
And I do bear a grudge.
Do we understand each other?
(00d.
They're saying that climate change
is a natural phenomenon
rather than an artificial phenomenon.
So how do you explain global warming,
the ice caps melting?
Well, what melts up there
reforms down there.
Know why they call the arctic "the arctic,”
and the antarctic "the antarctic"?
No, Dougie, I don't.
That's why I pay for you
to go to good schools.
Arktos means "bear" in Greek,
ant means "without."
Hence, antarktos: "Without bears."
Up with, down without.
Good news for ice cubes,
bad news for polar bears.
- What time's the game start?
- Six-thirty. We've got ages.
- What do you want to do?
- I don't know, grab some food?
Sure. Hello?
- Hi, sir.
- What is it, Mike?
Dougie, go get a coat, will you?
It's not gonna rain.
Dougie, coat.
- But why?
- Because I'm your dad.
And I said so.
(Set someone else to do it.
I can't, boss, there is no one else.
It's gotta be you.
Joe, two fucking minutes.
I'm with my son, Mike.
You know Dougie is over here on holiday
and it's the only time I get to see him.
It's your fucking job, you do it.
Understood.
Brendan was on it but he got knocked off
his bike by a drunk driver.
Make sure the boss knows it's not my fault.
It's a drunk driver.
He's with the police now
making a statement,
otherwise he'd find a way to be there.
There is no one else.
I'm out of town,
mogqgy's surveilling the depot.
I'd help if I could, Mike,
but my eyeballs are on the depot.
Then postpone it.
We can do that if you want but it's
gonna set us back three months of recon.
We need to know the route.
If they turn left or right,
that's all you have to witness.
And there's no danger to it at all.
You can stand back a thousand yards.
Didn't you put trackers on the truck?
They scan the trucks every time
they return to the base.
We can't do it digitally.
We've gotta put eyes on it.
And boss.
I'm tracking on your phone right now,
you're blocks away, 10 minutes.
And I repeat, no danger.
Dad.
- Happy?
- Happy.
I'm starving, fancy a burrito?
You don't even like burritos.
I know, but I'm starving.
Sure.
I'll be two minutes, okay?
- Keep the doors locked, don't go anywhere.
- All right.
- Yes, sir?
- Two burritos, please, sir.
You got it.
Go ahead, Mike.
I can see you there.
Now, is that some gates on your left side?
Yeah
now in a minute,
those said gates are gonna open.
And that said minute is how.
All I need to know from you
is if that truck is turning left or right.
Right turn.
You know, make your own cappuccino.
Oh, goddamn. Who is this?
Yo! Out of the
fucking car, come on.
Don't fucking look at me!
Out of the fucking car.
All right, Mike. Is my day done?
You're call
has been forwarded to...
Do you hear me? Out of the fucking car!
Face down, come on!
Show me your fucking hands!
Face down on the ground right now.
- There you go.
- I do what we say and you'll live.
Face to the fucking ground.
Thank you.
Fuck!
Dougie?
Try not to move too quickly.
You're in a hospital.
You were in an accident, you were shot at.
Six bullets removed.
Three operations.
Two lifesaving.
You lost a fifth of your blood.
You've got a warrior spirit.
What about my son?
Dougie?
My beautiful boy.
And now he's gone.
He looked up to you.
Was obsessed with you.
It wasn't my work, Jane.
You killed our son.
And still you have nothing to say.
You are a cold, cold cunt.
My condolences for your loss.
Before you ask,
we have no leads on this thing.
Which is kind of strange
for a job this big.
Somebody knows something.
Somebody always knows something.
It's just I'm not allowed
to ask the hard questions.
Here's the shit list
knock yourself out.
Need any of them to live?
I don't miss anyone
that your boys have buried so far.
Then you need to let me do this my way.
I can do in two weeks
what you only wish
you could do in 20 years.
If their names are on that list,
you can do your worst.
Just be mindful
that I can only look confused for so long.
The floor is yours.
Brendan.
You need to quit that.
I can hardly breathe here.
It wasn't your fault.
It was a drunk driver.
It's easy for you to say.
It's his son, moggy. His only son.
Hey, we all fucked up.
So let's accept the responsibility
and not turn on each other in there.
Brendan, retain your dignity.
It's a fucking tragedy, boss.
We all love Dougie.
And our sympathies run deep.
It's more my fault than anyone's.
And we'll do anything
to find who's responsible.
I need to know who pulled the trigger.
I need a face.
Of course.
And we've been on nothing else
trying to get answers.
It's not any of the usual suspects.
You're gonna tell us what we want to know.
This is your last chance.
The tree has been shook.
And it's been shook hard.
I want a name.
Anyone with a skill set, with a form.
We've run out of names.
We've deployed large amounts of time,
money and effort
in the search for justice.
It was a long list.
Not good enough.
Understood.
But we've scorched earth
no, it's not understood.
You started by saying
you'd do anything.
But what I'm hearing is
you think you've done everything.
Understood.
I I hear the train a comin' j
j it's rolling round the bend j
> and I ain't seen the sunshine j
> since I don't know when j
j I'm stuck in folsom prison j
j and time keeps draggin' on j
j but that train keeps a-rollin' j
j on down to San antone j
j when I was just a baby j
j my mama told me, "son" j
- what the fuck?
- Make a sound and you're dead.
J "always be a good boy j
j don't ever play with guns”
all right, Jerome, what do you think?
It's getting late. We all got places to go.
Why don't you save us a lot of time
and you a lot of trouble
and tell us what we need to know?
Trouble”? You motherfuckers got no idea
how much trouble you're in.
Do you know who the fuck I am?
Yeah, I know exactly who you are
and that's why you're here.
So I can see it's gonna be a long night.
Let's get started.
Bag him.
No! Fuck you all!
J it's rolling round the bend j
> and I ain't seen the sunshine j
> since I don't know when j
j when I was just a baby j
j my mama told me, "son j
j always be a good boy j
j don't ever play with guns”
All right, take it off.
I don't think he knows anything.
We'll see about that.
I hear you're a tough
lad and a hard worker.
Good for you.
But you're still gonna give me a name.
If not for your life, for hers.
What the fuck! Don't touch her!
I said don't touch her.
Don't fucking touch her!
- Leave her out of this!
- Bag her.
- No.
- No!
All right! The only fucking name.
Jackson brothers.
If it's anyone, it's them.
Home invasions,
he's talked about these cash trucks too.
But you did not hear this from me,
and if you did...
Kill me now.
Give him 200 grand. Leave
the keys in the car.
Pass me the water.
You all right?
No, I'm not.
It's a shit show.
Fucking reptiles.
There's kids involved.
Got a feeling I'm gonna
be cleaning up all day.
Mike.
Here you go, sweetheart. Drink some water.
There's a good qirl.
How much is in the pot?
I'd say 2.5.
So what do you think?
I think
it isn't them.
You've got to tell the boss.
They're filthy fucks.
And they have done trucks.
But they ain't our men.
That job was above them.
They're more about the smash and grab.
Looks like there's two and a half mil,
which they confessed to.
But, uh...
What do you want me to do?
Don't want you to do anything, mogqgy.
How old are these girls?
Not old enough.
Give the girls the cash.
And let 'em go.
Can I speak candidly, boss?
I don't think we should do this again.
Understandably, you're...
You're not in your right
mind just now, and...
You need a break.
But we can't continue
to handle business this way.
Otherwise, some fuckers are gonna come
for us before we can get to them.
The truth? We need a different approach.
It's gotta be an inside job.
You're right, Mike.
I shouldn't have got you involved.
I'm gonna go back to London for a while.
- Patrick.
- Patrick. I'm a brit, not a Mick.
So your mom's Irish.
Usual fare, this time you're
Patrick hill from lewisham.
You've got a driver's license, passport,
IRS papers with a full tax history,
and medical records.
All your criminal checks are clean.
You've got 25 years' worth of employment.
With references working in Europe
and the same for the
previous addresses too.
Your employment history has been inserted
into the delta orange security system.
So, should anyone check,
you've worked there for 11 years.
You even finished college,
and have held the same gym membership
since 2011.
As requested, you have your pistol license.
And finally, the hotel has been arranged.
It's another brand new youl.
Kirsty, one more thing.
Give me a copy of the coroner's report.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
“Just do it.
And your reference from orange delta
security was impressive.
- Family?
- Married. Divorced.
Anyone else? No.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Mr. hill.
You ain't much for talking, are you,
Mary poppins?
Let me buy you a beer.
Just make sure you drink it over there.
The autopsy report.
Show me your fucking hands!
Face down, on the ground, right now!
Face to the fucking ground!
How you holding up, Sam?
What's to say?
Wake up late, watch TV.
Drink a beer and watch more TV.
Maybe convince ma to give me a few bucks
so I can buy more beer.
Watch TV until I'm drunk
enough to fall asleep.
Did I mention I watch TV?
You're awfully quiet, Brad.
I'm not quiet.
I'm bored.
- Bored of what?
- Of not fucking working.
I'm built for combat, not daytime TV.
The afghanis treated us
better than our own.
I wish I was back in the unit.
Boredom is more dangerous than bullets.
Give me an enemy I can fucking see.
How about you, are you working, boss?
Still part-time at the mall.
Costing more than I'm making.
If it wasn't for Amy's parents,
we'd be on the street.
Seems like Carlos is the only one
who landed on his feet with the oil tycoon.
So I'm there from 6:00 in the morning
until 12:00 at night,
this motherfucker is dripping in gold,
and I haven't seen a dollar
in overtime yet.
One minute we're killing arabs,
the next minute we're wiping their ass.
Afghanis aren't arabs.
They're not? What are they?
Clue's in the name.
Afghanis.
Whatever. They're not Americans.
Do you know what I want to do?
I wanna lift one of those
precious ornaments
until I get my motherfucking overtime pay.
And why don't you?
Why don't I what?
Make them pay.
They owe us.
Why are you asking me?
Ask sarge.
Do they keep cash?
What's that?
That is it.
That's fucking what?
That is what is left
after we've washed it through the system.
What's on the table?
Hundred ten.
Two Rolexes, patek.
Six-carat ring chains, 40 grand cash.
Wait a minute. I got hit over the head
and lost my job for, like, 18g's a piece?
Thought we worked out
over half a million in solids?
We did the leg work.
- We made the calls...
- Number one.
- Go ahead, four.
- Incoming.
We spent the sweat,
we dealt with the fence,
that's what we get.
Salaam-alaikum.
Even split.
We're not the mafia we're soldiers.
Nah, something ain't right here.
- You're trying to say something, jan?
- Fuck off, jan.
Go find another bone to chew,
vou'll break your teeth on this one.
And stand up when the boss is talking.
We could change it though,
cut out the middleman.
What does that mean?
We want cash...
We go after cash.
We've got a guy on the inside.
Inside of what?
Cash trucks.
We took in 1.18 million.
That's three years' worth of work
in one payday.
$168,571 each.
That's a lot of paper right there.
- Hold on, that's seven ways, not six?
- Thirty seconds.
There might not be a middleman,
but there is a man on the inside,
he needs a slice.
And who is this inside man?
You don't need to know.
Uh-uh. Yes, motherfuckers, these are
guns and we'll not hesitate to kill you.
Don't be a hero, it's not your money.
- Show me your hands.
- Put your hands behind your back.
What's your driver's name?
If you lie to me, I'll fucking kill you.
- Chad.
- Chad fucking what?
- Chad Reed.
- Horrible name.
Gentlemen, we have found our opportunity
to stand tall again.
After years of taking it,
staring at our laces.
Don't quit your day job just yet.
Rhythm as normal, be smart.
Don't go buying anything flashy.
Just what you absolutely need,
do you hear me, jan?
Oh, yeah, loud and clear, boss.
Groceries, good.
Sports cars, bad.
This isn't retirement money,
but if we play it right, it could be.
Yo, Dave, come in.
Come in, Dave.
Just checking everything's as it should be.
All good here, Chad.
Be out in two.
Did that just go as smooth
as I thought it did?
Don't count your chickens just yet.
Hold on.
Gentlemen, if I can just
get your signatures.
- How's it going?
- All right.
- Fantastic.
- Thank you.
I'm telling you now,
there's more gold in these hills.
Yeah. We haven't even tapped into
our skill set.
Monkeys could've done that job.
- So let's push ourselves then.
- Easy, boys.
Walking before running.
Yeah, I don't know about you guys,
but, uh, I feel like I've been walking
for a long fucking time.
J happy birthday to you j
j happy birthday, dear Jack j
happy birthday!
J happy birthday to you j
yeah!
Whoa.
It's getting harder and harder.
I know it is my birthday, but...
I've got a present for you.
- What are you sitting on, old man?
- More work.
But with a significant bump.
It's another truck.
This time there's gonna be
at least six mil inside.
Now, we're talking.
Well, it's a lot more profitable
than killing arabs.
And it makes my blood flow.
Sweetheart, what about the kids?
Yeah, feed them first. Bad animals, bad.
- I'm sorry.
- Here, let me help you with...
Is the intel good?
We've got a good inside man.
He's one of us,
served under me back in the day.
Well, I'm in.
I just want to get back in the field.
I like the money but I
fucking love a mission.
Yeah, what's the downside?
We're gonna be way more exposed.
And it will warrant significant planning.
There will be six weeks
of training and recon.
Three minutes.
Who the fuck are these clowns?
- Is it gonna be a problem?
- I don't think so.
Five, on the car. Handle fit.
On it
time to go to work, boys.
Gotta get these hinges greased, man.
What is this?
- Freeway's gonna be backed up.
- Oh, fuck! Shit!
Still no response.
Thirty seconds.
Yo! Out of the fucking car, come on.
Don't fucking look at me!
Out of the fucking car.
Let's go, motherfucker.
- Fortico 1377, alarm raised.
- Alarm registered.
Face the fucking ground!
- Tires now.
- Move!
Do what we say and you fucking live.
Bravo, two black-and-whites,
en route, two minutes away.
Two units dispatched.
Don't do it.
Eta two minutes. “Two minutes.
No!
Fuck!
He shot two fucking guards, Elvis.
- He shot two fucking guards.
- Number one, are we good?
Are we good, number one?
We're good.
Number one just shot a fucking kid!
He shot a fucking kid!
Dougie!
- Incoming! Incoming on the right!
- It's fine! Incoming!
- I'm on it.
- Take the legs.
What the fuck did you just do?
I said the fucking legs.
Three, take his gun.
Okay, we've got one minute. Let's go!
- Move.
- Exit west. We've got to go! Come on!
- Let's go.
- Move! Move! Move!
Let's go! Let's go!
I'll tell you, man,
I'm surprised to hear from you.
(Glad we could all make it.
I'm glad that shit blew over.
You put us in a tight spot, jan.
I'm not sure it has all blown over.
You're lucky you still got
a seat at this table.
Ggot it.
I think we all know we're gonna need
a pension fund.
I can't say I wasn't pleased to have
this meeting. I was starting to itch.
As we are aware, the bigger the reward,
the bigger the risk.
- Everything comes with a price.
- Are you ready for that?
'Cause there is no guarantee of success
ohn this one.
None of this was ever really guaranteed,
was it, sarge?
We've been through worse.
Yeah, so lay it on us.
We're dying to find out.
We do this right,
we'll never have to work again.
- Neither will our kids.
- If we get it wrong?
It's game over.
So, what is it?
We're not hitting a cash truck,
we're hitting them all.
How is that possible?
The depot, black Friday.
How much?
North of 150 million.
Ooh
we've got eight weeks
of recon and planning.
- Base, this is gamma reporting.
- Come in, over.
This way.
That's 160 million divided seven ways.
We have every Avenue covered.
- Coming, Mr. rossi.
- Thank you, Mr. hill.
- Signing in.
- This is our best plan.
Yeah. All this is for nothing
if our guy doesn't come through.
Why does this room always smell so good?
Maybe, one day,
my garden can smell like this.
I hope you're not planning anything, Dave.
Well, it's black Friday tomorrow,
so, you'll have to wait and see.
If I thought you were serious,
I'd have to report you.
Of course I'm not serious. Or am I?
Anyway, it's action man
you got to look out for, not me.
Yeah, colder than a reptile.
Something's not right.
Well, why do I get the feeling
your money's never been safer, Mr. rossi?
You don't need to worry.
He's greedier than you, Tom.
He'll come through.
Okay, let's run through it one more time.
Have anyone see my clutch?
- Your... your what?
- My purse, sweetheart.
There's a green one on the landing.
- Thank you.
- Oh, yeah.
Come on.
- What are you doing today, dad?
- I got work.
- At the mall?
- That's right.
Will you come to my game after?
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Love you, dad.
- Bye, love you.
- I love you.
- Love you, honey.
- I come on.
- Bye.
- I'm gonna be late for work.
- I love you.
Hurry up, mom!
Okay, bye.
Come on, kids. Get in the car.
We're all set on our end.
I'm on my way to pick up jan.
Now it's all up to you.
Remember, take different
routes there and back.
Even a sniff of anything untoward,
you call it in.
This is black Friday.
The tills will keep ringing.
So don't take no chances.
We got close to 180 million
coming in here today.
Have you got it?
Yes, sir. Got it
I want everything and everyone back.
Safe and sound.
Let's get going, h.
What? You don't like it?
How does someone like you
afford a place like this?
And a $28,000 bike?
Credit card.
Calm down, it's not in my name.
Return it.
Put the beers down.
Grab your gear and let's go.
Let's go.
That's the last drop off.
What is it?
You know I like you, right, h?
Well, there's something
I need to tell you...
About me.
I've got some friends...
I help them out.
They help me out from time to time.
My pals...
I helped them get into
the cash truck game...
In a manner of speaking...
With me on the inside.
You get me?
No, bullet.
I don't.
I tell them which trucks to hit
and they hit them.
The two guards being killed was necessary.
The boy was unfortunate.
But we're a winning team.
Militarily precise.
Are you with me now?
Yeah
I'm with you, 100 percent.
Continue.
For starters, there are
no bullets in your gun.
Secondly, I have to tell you,
they will kill you if you don't comply.
So do as I say and you won't get hurt.
Why do you need me?
We need something super-sized,
so we can walk away for good.
We want the jackpot.
The depot.
You want me to get you in?
Then you can look the other way.
When, bullet?
Today.
There's no turning back.
What's in it for me?
Your life
Do we have a deal?
Yeah we have a deal.
We're on. Eta, two minutes.
Covers.
Gamma, this is base.
Do you copy? Over.
Base, this is gamma, we copy. Over.
Gamma, I lost camera signal in your truck.
What's happening there? Over.
There's nothing
to worry about, base.
I'm fixing it as we speak.
Copy that, gamma.
Keep me updated, this ain't the day for
this shit. Do you understand me? Over.
Loud and clear.
I'll be in touch as soon as. Over.
We're set.
Cameras are disarmed.
We meet here at point a.
Warn our hero not to get clever.
We'll need him to get inside.
After that, if he twitches, kill him.
Just let them do their jobs, okay?
Let me talk to him.
Hey, handsome.
Today is not the day to be a hero.
There will be no other warnings.
Am I clear?
Show me your hands.
Play the game, h.
If you're a good boy today...
You'll see tomorrow.
Then we divide.
You, Brad, Carlos and jan
are in the truck.
Me and Sam follow in the escalade.
Be cool, h.
2411, returning.
Gamma, this is base. Go, over.
- All good?
- Yeah, except the traffic.
- Dana, come give me a hand.
- No problem.
Right. Let's relieve you of your burden.
Base, this is gamma, reporting.
All clear, gamma.
- Are you ready?
- Ready.
Gamma 2411 inside.
That's the last one for today.
Once we get pass the gates, it's only a
question of time before we're compromised.
There's too many guards
that we can't control.
So we keep it quiet as long as possible.
The men must be stealthy.
The longer they're stealthed,
the longer we live without drama.
Hey, bullet.
- All good?
- All good here, supe.
Move, move, now. Move. Go.
- Whoa.
- Uh-uh-uh.
Don't you make a sound.
Down on the ground.
Move.
- Kneel down.
- Tip toe, tip toe, tip toe.
We secure the safe first.
That's Carlos and jan's job.
Okay, Dave,
that's all good and accounted for...
Hands in the motherfucking air.
Place your weapons on the ground.
Slowly, slowly.
- Do what he says.
- Take that weapon out, slide it over.
Get over there. Get on the fucking ground.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Grab your gun, put it on the ground
and kick it to me, motherfucker.
Do you wanna be a hero today?
I'll put you on the front page of every
fucking newspaper in America. Try me.
Get on the ground.
All the way.
Get your fucking ass on the ground.
Tie his ass up.
Behave yourself.
Hey. What's up?
I need you to sign this birthday card
for the boss.
Bring it up here and have a look at this.
This will make you laugh.
You, jan and Brad
will take the control room.
Bullet is hostage and shield.
If that doesn't work, we blow our way in.
Keep it fucking quiet.
Open the gate.
Bob, what the fuck is going on?
The keypad will
present a challenge.
The men that operate the armory
are hard-boiled.
They will not be scared
of pulling the trigger.
At some point, they'll resist.
Open the gate.
Or I'll blow his fucking head off.
You have three seconds.
One! Two!
- Three!
- Okay!
- Putting the gun down.
- Open the gate.
The keypad is out there.
You use the keypad.
It's on security lockdown.
You use the fucking keypad.
The rabbits have run, number one.
Two, breach the gate.
At some point, we're gonna come under fire.
They've got long guns, they'll use them.
Here you go. Take this.
So we'll need ballistic plates.
This is your last chance.
I'll blow his head off.
Bob, open the gate,
or they're gonna fucking kill me.
Bullet, get down!
Shit.
Set!
Nobody fucking move.
Number three, what's going on?
Don't do it!
Jesus fucking Christ.
Now!
Move, now, move!
Where are you hit? Where are you hit”?
Four is down. I repeat, four is down.
Oh, no, no, no!
No, please, sweet Mary and Joseph,
I swear to god.
Look at this little piggy.
Please don't. I got kids, please.
- Yeah...
- Please, don't hurt me. Please.
Enough of that.
Elvis, come and play.
- One, sweep the rest of the building.
- Copy.
- Five, are we good?
- Clear, Elvis, move in.
Welcome to the party.
These three are hog tied.
The block is in there,
and another three guards in the back.
SWAT have been alerted.
SWAT have been notified.
All units please respond.
Once the alarm sounds,
black-and-whites will be
on scene within minutes.
But they cannot enter the building.
Even if they could, they wouldn't dare.
However, they are not our problem.
We will have eight minutes
until SWAT arrives.
We can punch through the black-and-whites
with an 18-ton cash truck,
but the SWAT truck's a different story.
We cannot get pinned down.
We gotta get out
before they seal the exit.
We're eight minutes out. Eight minutes out.
We have men down. Send back
up right now. This is an emergency.
They have heavy assault weapons
and they have body armor.
- Men are down.
- Hold your position.
They have...
- Get in, get in.
- We're calling SWAT.
I'm not waiting for SWAT.
We have protocol. We wait for SWAT.
No, we gotta go now. “Wait!
Two, wait until we're loaded.
Then join three in the truck.
Nose to the fucking ground.
Did I stutter?
Load the Van, three.
I'll get five.
What the fuck
is going on out there?
There's a guard out here.
Someone shoot this fucker.
Please!
Shots have been fired.
Seven minutes out.
Fuck!
Clear.
Fuck this, I'm going out.
Listen, the alarm's gone,
we should just wait for help.
What do you want us to do?
You can do whatever you fucking like.
David, no, listen to me. They got
body armor. That gun will do nothing.
And this is not your money. Let's go.
Fucking go. Go, go!
We're six minutes out.
One, four is down. I repeat, four
is down. Do you have eyes on three?
Three respond.
Who's firing?
Copy that, all units...
Three is down.
We've got a rat on the loose.
Elvis is leaving the building.
David, just put
the gun down and hide.
- The SWAT team, they're on their way.
- If something goes down in the hallway,
- I'm gonna shoot them, Terry.
- There's no need.
Making my way to you now, Elvis.
Fuck!
Come on out, and you won't get hurt.
Come on, come here.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- Move!
- Some SWAT, some choppers, bring someone in.
Here, take this.
Man down.
Stay down.
Four minutes out.
“We're four minutes out.
Help!
Dave, are you all right?
SWAT team are
three minutes away, find cover.
We're sitting ducks here.
Give me a gun.
Fucking...
Give me a gun!
- Thank you.
- Bullet, what the...
- Clear.
- We gotta move.
Come on, get up. Move.
We got two minutes
until SWAT is here.
Clear!
Stay with me, stay with me.
Come on, come on.
Four is down!
Hey, boy sweat! It's bullet!
Bullet?
Come give me a hand.
Bullet! What the...
You're good?
We're good. Let's go.
Once the truck is loaded and we're all in,
we punch through the black-and-whites.
Exit right.
They and the choppers will be in pursuit,
but there's nothing they can do to stop us.
Fuck!
From here it's two klicks to meet
at rendez point to enter building d.
The gates here will stop
any immediate intrusion.
Heading south on 408. We have
visual. We have four birds in the sky.
It doesn't change a thing.
You stick to the plan.
Get ready.
We will have five
minutes until SWAT breaches.
They'll think we're trapped, shoot to kill,
but we won't be there.
There's no way they can know about
this access tunnel underneath the basement.
This doesn't come up on any blueprints.
They stopped printing this back in '57.
We have them
surrounded. SWAT has arrived on scene.
A-team, let's go. Into position.
How are you doing, sarge?
If I don't make it,
get back there and finish the job.
We are stationary and setting
up a blockade. Awaiting further orders.
(50.
That's the last of it let's move.
- All units you are clear to fire.
- Roger, dispatch.
Okay, I'll get the boss.
Whoa, whoa.
You're not gonna need that, sarge.
We all understand the risks.
Some of us won't make it.
If there is a last man standing,
it's his job to take care of the families.
I wish I was confident
that will happen, but...
My only concern is jan.
Strange things happen to men
when they smell that much cash.
He's a soldier.
In the end, he'll follow orders.
- Where's the sarge?
- He's not coming.
- What do you mean he's not coming?
- He's fucking dead, bullet.
From here, we load the can-am quads,
ride three more klicks
to the silver prius, load
the cash undercover.
And whoever's left
takes the construction pickup.
Uh-uh-uh. Too fucking slow.
All right, team.
Move in. Weapons ready.
- Copy.
- Suspects still in vehicle. Moving in.
- Move!
- Go.
What the fuck...
We got one dead suspect.
The others are fucking gone.
We need more bodies down here.
Shit
- there's tunnel's everywhere,
- Captain.
There's a network of underground tunnels.
It's like a fucking rabbit Warren down there.
3737, we do not have
visual. We need more eyes in the sky.
Copy that. Additional air
units covering long beach dock.
We're entering industrial unit
on terminal way.
We need more choppers up here.
There are tunnels coming out everywhere.
Aren't you gonna answer it?
What do you want?
You here for the money?
I don't want the money.
I want you to read this.
"Bullets a1 and a2 enter the right lung
causing collapse"?
"Bullet b1 penetrated the liver.
B2 ruptured the spleen.
Bullets c1 and c2 lacerated the heart.
Cause of death. Blood loss and trauma.
Manner of death, homicide."
In summary...
The liver...
The lungs, the spleen and the heart.
What the fuck do you want?
I want your liver.
Fuck you.
The lungs...
Spleen...
By the way...
His name was Dougie.
Are we done?
We're done.